[
  {
    "level": 1,
    "question": "389,389,647,647",
    "answer": "风风火火",
    "explain": "风风火火"
  },
  {
    "level": 2,
    "question": "433,382,451,367",
    "answer": "守株待兔",
    "explain": "守株待兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3,
    "question": "412,412,407,407",
    "answer": "马马虎虎",
    "explain": "马马虎虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 4,
    "question": "367,746,746,746",
    "answer": "狡兔三窟",
    "explain": "狡兔三窟"
  },
  {
    "level": 5,
    "question": "394,513,605,23",
    "answer": "归心似箭",
    "explain": "归心似箭"
  },
  {
    "level": 6,
    "question": "90,6,2,2",
    "answer": "信誓旦旦",
    "explain": "信誓旦旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 7,
    "question": "3,653,3,412",
    "answer": "单枪匹马",
    "explain": "单枪匹马"
  },
  {
    "level": 8,
    "question": "5,509,4,3",
    "answer": "三心二意",
    "explain": "三心二意"
  },
  {
    "level": 9,
    "question": "495,389,384,46",
    "answer": "针锋相对",
    "explain": "针锋相对"
  },
  {
    "level": 10,
    "question": "365,117,235,202",
    "answer": "虎落平阳",
    "explain": "虎落平阳"
  },
  {
    "level": 11,
    "question": "801,524,412,369",
    "answer": "车水马龙",
    "explain": "车水马龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 12,
    "question": "4,4,5,5",
    "answer": "接二连三",
    "explain": "接二连三"
  },
  {
    "level": 13,
    "question": "704,428,213,647",
    "answer": "喜上眉梢",
    "explain": "喜上眉梢"
  },
  {
    "level": 14,
    "question": "709,481,486,483",
    "answer": "妖魔鬼怪",
    "explain": "妖魔鬼怪"
  },
  {
    "level": 15,
    "question": "392,323,172,246",
    "answer": "余音绕梁",
    "explain": "余音绕梁"
  },
  {
    "level": 16,
    "question": "754,472,773,384",
    "answer": "盲人摸象",
    "explain": "盲人摸象"
  },
  {
    "level": 17,
    "question": "379,778,271,650",
    "answer": "鸡飞蛋打",
    "explain": "鸡飞蛋打"
  },
  {
    "level": 18,
    "question": "511,519,422,584",
    "answer": "心照不宣",
    "explain": "心照不宣"
  },
  {
    "level": 19,
    "question": "472,336,273,77",
    "answer": "人走茶凉",
    "explain": "人走茶凉"
  },
  {
    "level": 20,
    "question": "87,72,777,93",
    "answer": "刀光剑影",
    "explain": "刀光剑影"
  },
  {
    "level": 21,
    "question": "289,426,430,373",
    "answer": "七嘴八舌",
    "explain": "七嘴八舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 22,
    "question": "338,295,766,352",
    "answer": "悲喜交加",
    "explain": "悲喜交加"
  },
  {
    "level": 23,
    "question": "521,522,495,424",
    "answer": "雷声震耳",
    "explain": "雷声震耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 24,
    "question": "373,380,11,471",
    "answer": "舍己救人",
    "explain": "舍己救人"
  },
  {
    "level": 25,
    "question": "213,423,426,501",
    "answer": "眉目传情",
    "explain": "眉目传情"
  },
  {
    "level": 26,
    "question": "382,465,414,465",
    "answer": "猪朋狗友",
    "explain": "猪朋狗友"
  },
  {
    "level": 27,
    "question": "443,495,777,77",
    "answer": "一针见血",
    "explain": "一针见血"
  },
  {
    "level": 28,
    "question": "721,212,496,463",
    "answer": "愁眉苦脸",
    "explain": "愁眉苦脸"
  },
  {
    "level": 29,
    "question": "491,462,580,295",
    "answer": "指腹为婚",
    "explain": "指腹为婚"
  },
  {
    "level": 30,
    "question": "49,437,380,446",
    "answer": "一拍即合",
    "explain": "一拍即合"
  },
  {
    "level": 31,
    "question": "211,437,197,124",
    "answer": "花好月圆",
    "explain": "花好月圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 32,
    "question": "147,365,460,429",
    "answer": "骑虎难下",
    "explain": "骑虎难下"
  },
  {
    "level": 33,
    "question": "7,287,527,714",
    "answer": "五光十色",
    "explain": "五光十色"
  },
  {
    "level": 34,
    "question": "831,412,423,212",
    "answer": "走马观花",
    "explain": "走马观花"
  },
  {
    "level": 35,
    "question": "203,203,384,103",
    "answer": "心心相惜",
    "explain": "心心相惜"
  },
  {
    "level": 36,
    "question": "338,525,789,141",
    "answer": "杯水车薪",
    "explain": "杯水车薪"
  },
  {
    "level": 37,
    "question": "746,705,766,170",
    "answer": "哭笑不得",
    "explain": "哭笑不得"
  },
  {
    "level": 38,
    "question": "156,147,766,457",
    "answer": "美中不足",
    "explain": "美中不足"
  },
  {
    "level": 39,
    "question": "218,209,210,488",
    "answer": "草木皆兵",
    "explain": "草木皆兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 40,
    "question": "309,373,531,457",
    "answer": "画蛇添足",
    "explain": "画蛇添足"
  },
  {
    "level": 41,
    "question": "177,5,197,6",
    "answer": "朝三暮四",
    "explain": "朝三暮四"
  },
  {
    "level": 42,
    "question": "438,343,423,696",
    "answer": "开门见山",
    "explain": "开门见山"
  },
  {
    "level": 43,
    "question": "380,103,395,322",
    "answer": "鸡同鸭讲",
    "explain": "鸡同鸭讲"
  },
  {
    "level": 44,
    "question": "443,246,462,463",
    "answer": "衣食父母",
    "explain": "衣食父母"
  },
  {
    "level": 45,
    "question": "391,423,172,382",
    "answer": "鱼目混珠",
    "explain": "鱼目混珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 46,
    "question": "460,460,527,218",
    "answer": "头头是道",
    "explain": "头头是道"
  },
  {
    "level": 47,
    "question": "766,746,268,35",
    "answer": "病入膏肓",
    "explain": "病入膏肓"
  },
  {
    "level": 48,
    "question": "248,392,6,486",
    "answer": "面如死灰",
    "explain": "面如死灰"
  },
  {
    "level": 49,
    "question": "469,77,254,103",
    "answer": "霜雪交错",
    "explain": "霜雪交错"
  },
  {
    "level": 50,
    "question": "423,336,426,752",
    "answer": "目瞪口呆",
    "explain": "目瞪口呆"
  },
  {
    "level": 51,
    "question": "443,442,579,87",
    "answer": "衣衫不整",
    "explain": "衣衫不整"
  },
  {
    "level": 52,
    "question": "3,526,754,103",
    "answer": "一气呵成",
    "explain": "一气呵成"
  },
  {
    "level": 53,
    "question": "415,117,113,182",
    "answer": "珠沉沧海",
    "explain": "珠沉沧海"
  },
  {
    "level": 54,
    "question": "379,89,414,336",
    "answer": "鸡飞狗跳",
    "explain": "鸡飞狗跳"
  },
  {
    "level": 55,
    "question": "373,378,3,67",
    "answer": "蛇鼠一窝",
    "explain": "蛇鼠一窝"
  },
  {
    "level": 56,
    "question": "497,579,88,514",
    "answer": "口不对心",
    "explain": "口不对心"
  },
  {
    "level": 57,
    "question": "831,672,80,120",
    "answer": "过时不候",
    "explain": "过时不候"
  },
  {
    "level": 58,
    "question": "73,176,500,734",
    "answer": "珠光宝气",
    "explain": "珠光宝气"
  },
  {
    "level": 59,
    "question": "705,497,444,438",
    "answer": "笑口常开",
    "explain": "笑口常开"
  },
  {
    "level": 60,
    "question": "812,7,578,279",
    "answer": "不舞之鹤",
    "explain": "不舞之鹤"
  },
  {
    "level": 61,
    "question": "520,647,130,647",
    "answer": "怒火中烧",
    "explain": "怒火中烧"
  },
  {
    "level": 62,
    "question": "746,406,278,248",
    "answer": "泪流满面",
    "explain": "泪流满面"
  },
  {
    "level": 63,
    "question": "508,351,396,351",
    "answer": "心无旁骛",
    "explain": "心无旁骛"
  },
  {
    "level": 64,
    "question": "606,606,103,425",
    "answer": "默默无闻",
    "explain": "默默无闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 65,
    "question": "842,746,103,524",
    "answer": "欲哭无泪",
    "explain": "欲哭无泪"
  },
  {
    "level": 66,
    "question": "406,486,412,248",
    "answer": "牛头马面",
    "explain": "牛头马面"
  },
  {
    "level": 67,
    "question": "360,423,434,287",
    "answer": "鼠目寸光",
    "explain": "鼠目寸光"
  },
  {
    "level": 68,
    "question": "212,534,197,120",
    "answer": "花前月下",
    "explain": "花前月下"
  },
  {
    "level": 69,
    "question": "527,432,527,489",
    "answer": "十全十美",
    "explain": "十全十美"
  },
  {
    "level": 70,
    "question": "584,578,842,591",
    "answer": "呼之欲出",
    "explain": "呼之欲出"
  },
  {
    "level": 71,
    "question": "170,509,398,92",
    "answer": "得心应手",
    "explain": "得心应手"
  },
  {
    "level": 72,
    "question": "7,287,527,714",
    "answer": "五光十色",
    "explain": "五光十色"
  },
  {
    "level": 73,
    "question": "507,507,384,306",
    "answer": "心心相印",
    "explain": "心心相印"
  },
  {
    "level": 74,
    "question": "460,461,474,476",
    "answer": "男女老少",
    "explain": "男女老少"
  },
  {
    "level": 75,
    "question": "3,423,750,507",
    "answer": "一见倾心",
    "explain": "一见倾心"
  },
  {
    "level": 76,
    "question": "773,489,457,272",
    "answer": "手舞足蹈",
    "explain": "手舞足蹈"
  },
  {
    "level": 77,
    "question": "506,506,234,121",
    "answer": "岁岁平安",
    "explain": "岁岁平安"
  },
  {
    "level": 78,
    "question": "746,130,544,705",
    "answer": "苦中作乐",
    "explain": "苦中作乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 79,
    "question": "424,618,318,465",
    "answer": "耳听八方",
    "explain": "耳听八方"
  },
  {
    "level": 80,
    "question": "432,514,432,428",
    "answer": "全心全意",
    "explain": "全心全意"
  },
  {
    "level": 81,
    "question": "130,655,628,394",
    "answer": "众望所归",
    "explain": "众望所归"
  },
  {
    "level": 82,
    "question": "618,369,647,407",
    "answer": "生龙活虎",
    "explain": "生龙活虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 83,
    "question": "123,233,818,330",
    "answer": "星罗棋布",
    "explain": "星罗棋布"
  },
  {
    "level": 84,
    "question": "413,819,225,182",
    "answer": "侯门似海",
    "explain": "侯门似海"
  },
  {
    "level": 85,
    "question": "180,460,220,461",
    "answer": "红男绿女",
    "explain": "红男绿女"
  },
  {
    "level": 86,
    "question": "534,305,378,489",
    "answer": "前歌后舞",
    "explain": "前歌后舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 87,
    "question": "572,232,819,466",
    "answer": "书香门第",
    "explain": "书香门第"
  },
  {
    "level": 88,
    "question": "233,44,777,202",
    "answer": "拔云见日",
    "explain": "拔云见日"
  },
  {
    "level": 89,
    "question": "246,365,394,696",
    "answer": "放虎归山",
    "explain": "放虎归山"
  },
  {
    "level": 90,
    "question": "89,398,428,478",
    "answer": "飞鸟伊人",
    "explain": "飞鸟伊人"
  },
  {
    "level": 91,
    "question": "182,746,183,333",
    "answer": "海枯石烂",
    "explain": "海枯石烂"
  },
  {
    "level": 92,
    "question": "246,474,634,476",
    "answer": "返老还童",
    "explain": "返老还童"
  },
  {
    "level": 93,
    "question": "534,305,378,234",
    "answer": "前因后果",
    "explain": "前因后果"
  },
  {
    "level": 94,
    "question": "497,225,514,89",
    "answer": "口是心非",
    "explain": "口是心非"
  },
  {
    "level": 95,
    "question": "96,362,328,329",
    "answer": "对牛弹琴",
    "explain": "对牛弹琴"
  },
  {
    "level": 96,
    "question": "69,834,104,649",
    "answer": "坐立不安",
    "explain": "坐立不安"
  },
  {
    "level": 97,
    "question": "73,554,74,572",
    "answer": "白纸黑字",
    "explain": "白纸黑字"
  },
  {
    "level": 98,
    "question": "7,7,7,464",
    "answer": "三五成群",
    "explain": "三五成群"
  },
  {
    "level": 99,
    "question": "322,365,236,696",
    "answer": "调虎离山",
    "explain": "调虎离山"
  },
  {
    "level": 100,
    "question": "3,222,257,813",
    "answer": "一叶扁舟",
    "explain": "一叶扁舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 101,
    "question": "94,369,530,423",
    "answer": "画龙点睛",
    "explain": "画龙点睛"
  },
  {
    "level": 102,
    "question": "500,506,184,411",
    "answer": "石破天惊",
    "explain": "石破天惊"
  },
  {
    "level": 103,
    "question": "392,404,369,819",
    "answer": "鱼跃龙门",
    "explain": "鱼跃龙门"
  },
  {
    "level": 104,
    "question": "376,376,170,388",
    "answer": "羊羊得意",
    "explain": "羊羊得意"
  },
  {
    "level": 105,
    "question": "3,84,389,782",
    "answer": "一帆风顺",
    "explain": "一帆风顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 106,
    "question": "533,653,533,96",
    "answer": "百发百中",
    "explain": "百发百中"
  },
  {
    "level": 107,
    "question": "218,813,499,316",
    "answer": "草船借箭",
    "explain": "草船借箭"
  },
  {
    "level": 108,
    "question": "443,218,443,207",
    "answer": "一草一木",
    "explain": "一草一木"
  },
  {
    "level": 109,
    "question": "327,383,437,374",
    "answer": "吹牛拍马",
    "explain": "吹牛拍马"
  },
  {
    "level": 110,
    "question": "519,108,278,99",
    "answer": "灯红酒绿",
    "explain": "灯红酒绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 111,
    "question": "276,197,373,313",
    "answer": "杯弓蛇影",
    "explain": "杯弓蛇影"
  },
  {
    "level": 112,
    "question": "495,424,842,373",
    "answer": "震耳欲聋",
    "explain": "震耳欲聋"
  },
  {
    "level": 113,
    "question": "610,472,611,424",
    "answer": "交头接耳",
    "explain": "交头接耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 114,
    "question": "197,429,474,475",
    "answer": "月下老人",
    "explain": "月下老人"
  },
  {
    "level": 115,
    "question": "652,696,647,811",
    "answer": "刀山火海",
    "explain": "刀山火海"
  },
  {
    "level": 116,
    "question": "367,6,381,647",
    "answer": "兔死狗烹",
    "explain": "兔死狗烹"
  },
  {
    "level": 117,
    "question": "6,374,462,831",
    "answer": "驷马难追",
    "explain": "驷马难追"
  },
  {
    "level": 118,
    "question": "507,343,379,63",
    "answer": "爱屋及乌",
    "explain": "爱屋及乌"
  },
  {
    "level": 119,
    "question": "229,258,236,120",
    "answer": "瓜田李下",
    "explain": "瓜田李下"
  },
  {
    "level": 120,
    "question": "10,439,564,379",
    "answer": "霸王别姬",
    "explain": "霸王别姬"
  },
  {
    "level": 121,
    "question": "92,497,384,274",
    "answer": "守口如瓶",
    "explain": "守口如瓶"
  },
  {
    "level": 122,
    "question": "369,369,701,415",
    "answer": "双龙戏珠",
    "explain": "双龙戏珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 123,
    "question": "212,214,220,220",
    "answer": "花花草草",
    "explain": "花花草草"
  },
  {
    "level": 124,
    "question": "438,438,65,65",
    "answer": "开开心心",
    "explain": "开开心心"
  },
  {
    "level": 125,
    "question": "429,379,829,489",
    "answer": "闻鸡起舞",
    "explain": "闻鸡起舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 126,
    "question": "103,5,103,5",
    "answer": "不三不四",
    "explain": "不三不四"
  },
  {
    "level": 127,
    "question": "679,159,831,821",
    "answer": "渺无人烟",
    "explain": "渺无人烟"
  },
  {
    "level": 128,
    "question": "177,465,176,465",
    "answer": "早出晚归",
    "explain": "早出晚归"
  },
  {
    "level": 129,
    "question": "424,423,3,141",
    "answer": "耳目一新",
    "explain": "耳目一新"
  },
  {
    "level": 130,
    "question": "399,380,456,531",
    "answer": "鹰击长空",
    "explain": "鹰击长空"
  },
  {
    "level": 131,
    "question": "489,400,415,412",
    "answer": "群雄逐鹿",
    "explain": "群雄逐鹿"
  },
  {
    "level": 132,
    "question": "533,395,342,398",
    "answer": "百鸟朝凤",
    "explain": "百鸟朝凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 133,
    "question": "49,412,113,374",
    "answer": "指鹿为马",
    "explain": "指鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 134,
    "question": "277,273,578,279",
    "answer": "饮鸩止渴",
    "explain": "饮鸩止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 135,
    "question": "73,209,333,392",
    "answer": "缘木求鱼",
    "explain": "缘木求鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 136,
    "question": "3,89,655,531",
    "answer": "一飞冲天",
    "explain": "一飞冲天"
  },
  {
    "level": 137,
    "question": "3,176,411,458",
    "answer": "一鸣惊人",
    "explain": "一鸣惊人"
  },
  {
    "level": 138,
    "question": "415,412,147,73",
    "answer": "逐鹿中原",
    "explain": "逐鹿中原"
  },
  {
    "level": 139,
    "question": "120,392,117,399",
    "answer": "沉鱼落雁",
    "explain": "沉鱼落雁"
  },
  {
    "level": 140,
    "question": "411,197,578,399",
    "answer": "惊弓之鸟",
    "explain": "惊弓之鸟"
  },
  {
    "level": 141,
    "question": "3,527,4,399",
    "answer": "一石二鸟",
    "explain": "一石二鸟"
  },
  {
    "level": 142,
    "question": "4,409,4,414",
    "answer": "阿猫阿狗",
    "explain": "阿猫阿狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 143,
    "question": "9,119,10,120",
    "answer": "七上八下",
    "explain": "七上八下"
  },
  {
    "level": 144,
    "question": "3,509,3,3",
    "answer": "一心一意",
    "explain": "一心一意"
  },
  {
    "level": 145,
    "question": "11,406,3,114",
    "answer": "九牛一毛",
    "explain": "九牛一毛"
  },
  {
    "level": 146,
    "question": "11,527,3,515",
    "answer": "九死一生",
    "explain": "九死一生"
  },
  {
    "level": 147,
    "question": "7,812,6,811",
    "answer": "五湖四海",
    "explain": "五湖四海"
  },
  {
    "level": 148,
    "question": "9,2,10,120",
    "answer": "七零八落",
    "explain": "七零八落"
  },
  {
    "level": 149,
    "question": "11,11,394,3",
    "answer": "九九归一",
    "explain": "九九归一"
  },
  {
    "level": 150,
    "question": "7,212,10,343",
    "answer": "五花八门",
    "explain": "五花八门"
  },
  {
    "level": 151,
    "question": "8,125,7,415",
    "answer": "六神无主",
    "explain": "六神无主"
  },
  {
    "level": 152,
    "question": "10,358,831,182",
    "answer": "八仙过海",
    "explain": "八仙过海"
  },
  {
    "level": 153,
    "question": "6,248,10,35",
    "answer": "四面八方",
    "explain": "四面八方"
  },
  {
    "level": 154,
    "question": "384,392,170,342",
    "answer": "如鱼得水",
    "explain": "如鱼得水"
  },
  {
    "level": 155,
    "question": "398,368,412,819",
    "answer": "引狼入室",
    "explain": "引狼入室"
  },
  {
    "level": 156,
    "question": "362,468,571,470",
    "answer": "牛郎织女",
    "explain": "牛郎织女"
  },
  {
    "level": 157,
    "question": "471,471,471,407",
    "answer": "三人成虎",
    "explain": "三人成虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 158,
    "question": "369,495,365,251",
    "answer": "龙争虎斗",
    "explain": "龙争虎斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 159,
    "question": "398,47,211,232",
    "answer": "鸟语花香",
    "explain": "鸟语花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 160,
    "question": "11,819,407,366",
    "answer": "九关虎豹",
    "explain": "九关虎豹"
  },
  {
    "level": 161,
    "question": "413,3,374,197",
    "answer": "猴年马月",
    "explain": "猴年马月"
  },
  {
    "level": 162,
    "question": "407,406,373,114",
    "answer": "虎头蛇尾",
    "explain": "虎头蛇尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 163,
    "question": "106,377,573,374",
    "answer": "问羊知马",
    "explain": "问羊知马"
  },
  {
    "level": 164,
    "question": "397,381,89,288",
    "answer": "鸡犬升天",
    "explain": "鸡犬升天"
  },
  {
    "level": 165,
    "question": "519,409,309,407",
    "answer": "照猫画虎",
    "explain": "照猫画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 166,
    "question": "44,369,391,443",
    "answer": "白龙鱼服",
    "explain": "白龙鱼服"
  },
  {
    "level": 167,
    "question": "412,6,525,92",
    "answer": "鹿死谁手",
    "explain": "鹿死谁手"
  },
  {
    "level": 168,
    "question": "391,274,424,270",
    "answer": "鱼贯而入",
    "explain": "鱼贯而入"
  },
  {
    "level": 169,
    "question": "399,28,197,566",
    "answer": "鸟尽弓藏",
    "explain": "鸟尽弓藏"
  },
  {
    "level": 170,
    "question": "381,65,368,89",
    "answer": "狼心狗肺",
    "explain": "狼心狗肺"
  },
  {
    "level": 171,
    "question": "232,477,506,424",
    "answer": "焦头烂额",
    "explain": "焦头烂额"
  },
  {
    "level": 172,
    "question": "399,653,611,831",
    "answer": "鸟枪换炮",
    "explain": "鸟枪换炮"
  },
  {
    "level": 173,
    "question": "389,832,424,380",
    "answer": "蜂拥而至",
    "explain": "蜂拥而至"
  },
  {
    "level": 174,
    "question": "399,387,705,379",
    "answer": "雕虫小技",
    "explain": "雕虫小技"
  },
  {
    "level": 175,
    "question": "103,489,379,259",
    "answer": "不舞之鹤",
    "explain": "不舞之鹤"
  },
  {
    "level": 176,
    "question": "379,189,499,2",
    "answer": "鸡鸣戒旦",
    "explain": "鸡鸣戒旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 177,
    "question": "533,205,489,3",
    "answer": "百里挑一",
    "explain": "百里挑一"
  },
  {
    "level": 178,
    "question": "5,5,4,4",
    "answer": "三三两两",
    "explain": "三三两两"
  },
  {
    "level": 179,
    "question": "65,342,65,4",
    "answer": "自由自在",
    "explain": "自由自在"
  },
  {
    "level": 180,
    "question": "309,365,579,7",
    "answer": "画虎不成",
    "explain": "画虎不成"
  },
  {
    "level": 181,
    "question": "381,821,6,9",
    "answer": "狼烟四起",
    "explain": "狼烟四起"
  },
  {
    "level": 182,
    "question": "503,503,10,10",
    "answer": "结结巴巴",
    "explain": "结结巴巴"
  },
  {
    "level": 183,
    "question": "9,9,10,10",
    "answer": "七七八八",
    "explain": "七七八八"
  },
  {
    "level": 184,
    "question": "302,302,10,10",
    "answer": "摇摇摆摆",
    "explain": "摇摇摆摆"
  },
  {
    "level": 185,
    "question": "12,109,821,11",
    "answer": "喜新厌旧",
    "explain": "喜新厌旧"
  },
  {
    "level": 186,
    "question": "819,414,412,30",
    "answer": "墙头马上",
    "explain": "墙头马上"
  },
  {
    "level": 187,
    "question": "534,534,31,31",
    "answer": "忐忐忑忑",
    "explain": "忐忐忑忑"
  },
  {
    "level": 188,
    "question": "339,365,333,31",
    "answer": "骑虎难下",
    "explain": "骑虎难下"
  },
  {
    "level": 189,
    "question": "392,392,36,36",
    "answer": "条条框框",
    "explain": "条条框框"
  },
  {
    "level": 190,
    "question": "533,212,9,39",
    "answer": "百花齐放",
    "explain": "百花齐放"
  },
  {
    "level": 191,
    "question": "801,412,295,41",
    "answer": "车马骈阗",
    "explain": "车马骈阗"
  },
  {
    "level": 192,
    "question": "464,47,236,44",
    "answer": "杏雨梨云",
    "explain": "杏雨梨云"
  },
  {
    "level": 193,
    "question": "249,522,389,44",
    "answer": "叱咤风云",
    "explain": "叱咤风云"
  },
  {
    "level": 194,
    "question": "389,373,566,44",
    "answer": "风卷残云",
    "explain": "风卷残云"
  },
  {
    "level": 195,
    "question": "45,205,431,45",
    "answer": "话里有话",
    "explain": "话里有话"
  },
  {
    "level": 196,
    "question": "5,821,4,47",
    "answer": "三言两语",
    "explain": "三言两语"
  },
  {
    "level": 197,
    "question": "389,389,47,47",
    "answer": "风风雨雨",
    "explain": "风风雨雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 198,
    "question": "653,2,328,47",
    "answer": "枪林弹雨",
    "explain": "枪林弹雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 199,
    "question": "369,497,398,47",
    "answer": "龙言凤语",
    "explain": "龙言凤语"
  },
  {
    "level": 200,
    "question": "540,514,3,66",
    "answer": "万紫千红",
    "explain": "万紫千红"
  },
  {
    "level": 201,
    "question": "540,412,336,67",
    "answer": "万马奔腾",
    "explain": "万马奔腾"
  },
  {
    "level": 202,
    "question": "365,110,365,72",
    "answer": "狐假虎威",
    "explain": "狐假虎威"
  },
  {
    "level": 203,
    "question": "361,423,434,72",
    "answer": "鼠目寸光",
    "explain": "鼠目寸光"
  },
  {
    "level": 204,
    "question": "189,189,73,73",
    "answer": "明明白白",
    "explain": "明明白白"
  },
  {
    "level": 205,
    "question": "96,96,89,89",
    "answer": "是是非非",
    "explain": "是是非非"
  },
  {
    "level": 206,
    "question": "492,342,89,89",
    "answer": "想入非非",
    "explain": "想入非非"
  },
  {
    "level": 207,
    "question": "110,379,205,89",
    "answer": "家鸡野鹜",
    "explain": "家鸡野鹜"
  },
  {
    "level": 208,
    "question": "486,772,369,89",
    "answer": "尸居龙见",
    "explain": "尸居龙见"
  },
  {
    "level": 209,
    "question": "500,362,457,89",
    "answer": "钻牛角尖",
    "explain": "钻牛角尖"
  },
  {
    "level": 210,
    "question": "647,369,502,89",
    "answer": "活龙鲜健",
    "explain": "活龙鲜健"
  },
  {
    "level": 211,
    "question": "362,652,120,91",
    "answer": "牛刀小试",
    "explain": "牛刀小试"
  },
  {
    "level": 212,
    "question": "821,821,93,93",
    "answer": "抽抽噎噎",
    "explain": "抽抽噎噎"
  },
  {
    "level": 213,
    "question": "542,821,831,94",
    "answer": "飞檐走壁",
    "explain": "飞檐走壁"
  },
  {
    "level": 214,
    "question": "142,47,446,97",
    "answer": "未雨绸缪",
    "explain": "未雨绸缪"
  },
  {
    "level": 215,
    "question": "480,647,480,97",
    "answer": "如火如荼",
    "explain": "如火如荼"
  },
  {
    "level": 216,
    "question": "333,287,399,101",
    "answer": "囊萤映雪",
    "explain": "囊萤映雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 217,
    "question": "104,819,834,101",
    "answer": "程门立雪",
    "explain": "程门立雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 218,
    "question": "495,365,14,109",
    "answer": "众虎同心",
    "explain": "众虎同心"
  },
  {
    "level": 219,
    "question": "457,457,72,109",
    "answer": "步步惊心",
    "explain": "步步惊心"
  },
  {
    "level": 220,
    "question": "381,831,368,109",
    "answer": "狗行狼心",
    "explain": "狗行狼心"
  },
  {
    "level": 221,
    "question": "384,501,384,109",
    "answer": "相亲相爱",
    "explain": "相亲相爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 222,
    "question": "526,101,232,110",
    "answer": "风雪交加",
    "explain": "风雪交加"
  },
  {
    "level": 223,
    "question": "442,489,442,110",
    "answer": "一五一十",
    "explain": "一五一十"
  },
  {
    "level": 224,
    "question": "6,182,580,110",
    "answer": "四海为家",
    "explain": "四海为家"
  },
  {
    "level": 225,
    "question": "2,2,111,111",
    "answer": "林林总总",
    "explain": "林林总总"
  },
  {
    "level": 226,
    "question": "496,218,766,112",
    "answer": "药到病除",
    "explain": "药到病除"
  },
  {
    "level": 227,
    "question": "178,178,117,117",
    "answer": "昏昏沉沉",
    "explain": "昏昏沉沉"
  },
  {
    "level": 228,
    "question": "389,465,424,119",
    "answer": "蜂拥而上",
    "explain": "蜂拥而上"
  },
  {
    "level": 229,
    "question": "381,412,507,127",
    "answer": "犬马恋主",
    "explain": "犬马恋主"
  },
  {
    "level": 230,
    "question": "121,121,161,161",
    "answer": "安安静静",
    "explain": "安安静静"
  },
  {
    "level": 231,
    "question": "389,212,101,166",
    "answer": "风花雪月",
    "explain": "风花雪月"
  },
  {
    "level": 232,
    "question": "521,362,813,166",
    "answer": "吴牛喘月",
    "explain": "吴牛喘月"
  },
  {
    "level": 233,
    "question": "424,5,9,170",
    "answer": "二三其德",
    "explain": "二三其德"
  },
  {
    "level": 234,
    "question": "333,554,820,170",
    "answer": "求之不得",
    "explain": "求之不得"
  },
  {
    "level": 235,
    "question": "3,497,11,173",
    "answer": "一言九鼎",
    "explain": "一言九鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 236,
    "question": "89,369,4,175",
    "answer": "飞龙在天",
    "explain": "飞龙在天"
  },
  {
    "level": 237,
    "question": "342,342,175,175",
    "answer": "朝朝暮暮",
    "explain": "朝朝暮暮"
  },
  {
    "level": 238,
    "question": "202,202,175,175",
    "answer": "日日夜夜",
    "explain": "日日夜夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 239,
    "question": "3,92,357,175",
    "answer": "一手遮天",
    "explain": "一手遮天"
  },
  {
    "level": 240,
    "question": "468,831,468,175",
    "answer": "人来人往",
    "explain": "人来人往"
  },
  {
    "level": 241,
    "question": "3,457,696,175",
    "answer": "一步登天",
    "explain": "一步登天"
  },
  {
    "level": 242,
    "question": "122,323,122,180",
    "answer": "绘声绘色",
    "explain": "绘声绘色"
  },
  {
    "level": 243,
    "question": "469,469,180,180",
    "answer": "形形色色",
    "explain": "形形色色"
  },
  {
    "level": 244,
    "question": "369,374,398,180",
    "answer": "龙章凤彩",
    "explain": "龙章凤彩"
  },
  {
    "level": 245,
    "question": "466,183,466,182",
    "answer": "人山人海",
    "explain": "人山人海"
  },
  {
    "level": 246,
    "question": "104,389,506,182",
    "answer": "乘风破浪",
    "explain": "乘风破浪"
  },
  {
    "level": 247,
    "question": "182,746,696,182",
    "answer": "海枯石烂",
    "explain": "海枯石烂"
  },
  {
    "level": 248,
    "question": "177,177,184,184",
    "answer": "勤勤恳恳",
    "explain": "勤勤恳恳"
  },
  {
    "level": 249,
    "question": "5,5,6,6",
    "answer": "三三四四",
    "explain": "三三四四"
  },
  {
    "level": 250,
    "question": "7,465,431,184",
    "answer": "杞人忧天",
    "explain": "杞人忧天"
  },
  {
    "level": 251,
    "question": "5,5,7,7",
    "answer": "三三五五",
    "explain": "三三五五"
  },
  {
    "level": 252,
    "question": "579,338,579,184",
    "answer": "不卑不亢",
    "explain": "不卑不亢"
  },
  {
    "level": 253,
    "question": "175,412,831,184",
    "answer": "天马行空",
    "explain": "天马行空"
  },
  {
    "level": 254,
    "question": "3,295,3,185",
    "answer": "一生一世",
    "explain": "一生一世"
  },
  {
    "level": 255,
    "question": "295,295,185,185",
    "answer": "生生世世",
    "explain": "生生世世"
  },
  {
    "level": 256,
    "question": "193,295,193,185",
    "answer": "今生今世",
    "explain": "今生今世"
  },
  {
    "level": 257,
    "question": "365,368,569,186",
    "answer": "虎狼之势",
    "explain": "虎狼之势"
  },
  {
    "level": 258,
    "question": "389,8,78,187",
    "answer": "风流韵事",
    "explain": "风流韵事"
  },
  {
    "level": 259,
    "question": "3,831,3,193",
    "answer": "一诺千金",
    "explain": "一诺千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 260,
    "question": "3,497,333,193",
    "answer": "一言难尽",
    "explain": "一言难尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 261,
    "question": "696,250,525,193",
    "answer": "山穷水尽",
    "explain": "山穷水尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 262,
    "question": "3,604,650,193",
    "answer": "一网打尽",
    "explain": "一网打尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 263,
    "question": "209,209,194,194",
    "answer": "恓恓惶惶",
    "explain": "恓恓惶惶"
  },
  {
    "level": 264,
    "question": "207,207,194,194",
    "answer": "栖栖遑遑",
    "explain": "栖栖遑遑"
  },
  {
    "level": 265,
    "question": "402,402,197,197",
    "answer": "落落穆穆",
    "explain": "落落穆穆"
  },
  {
    "level": 266,
    "question": "335,412,197,197",
    "answer": "跃马弯弓",
    "explain": "跃马弯弓"
  },
  {
    "level": 267,
    "question": "47,831,175,202",
    "answer": "雨过天晴",
    "explain": "雨过天晴"
  },
  {
    "level": 268,
    "question": "538,175,611,202",
    "answer": "偷天换日",
    "explain": "偷天换日"
  },
  {
    "level": 269,
    "question": "392,392,205,205",
    "answer": "郁郁葱葱",
    "explain": "郁郁葱葱"
  },
  {
    "level": 270,
    "question": "521,521,205,205",
    "answer": "战战栗栗",
    "explain": "战战栗栗"
  },
  {
    "level": 271,
    "question": "212,212,210,210",
    "answer": "花花绿绿",
    "explain": "花花绿绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 272,
    "question": "373,373,210,210",
    "answer": "蝎蝎螫螫",
    "explain": "蝎蝎螫螫"
  },
  {
    "level": 273,
    "question": "219,369,193,215",
    "answer": "青龙金匮",
    "explain": "青龙金匮"
  },
  {
    "level": 274,
    "question": "5,412,14,218",
    "answer": "三马同槽",
    "explain": "三马同槽"
  },
  {
    "level": 275,
    "question": "3,95,3,193",
    "answer": "一字千金",
    "explain": "一字千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 276,
    "question": "209,379,381,218",
    "answer": "木鸡养到",
    "explain": "木鸡养到"
  },
  {
    "level": 277,
    "question": "717,309,384,218",
    "answer": "虚怀若谷",
    "explain": "虚怀若谷"
  },
  {
    "level": 278,
    "question": "65,73,65,219",
    "answer": "自怨自艾",
    "explain": "自怨自艾"
  },
  {
    "level": 279,
    "question": "32,32,219,219",
    "answer": "期期艾艾",
    "explain": "期期艾艾"
  },
  {
    "level": 280,
    "question": "369,489,398,220",
    "answer": "龙姿凤采",
    "explain": "龙姿凤采"
  },
  {
    "level": 281,
    "question": "3,202,5,222",
    "answer": "一日三秋",
    "explain": "一日三秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 282,
    "question": "47,365,767,232",
    "answer": "与虎谋皮",
    "explain": "与虎谋皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 283,
    "question": "3,409,579,233",
    "answer": "一毛不拔",
    "explain": "一毛不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 284,
    "question": "3,497,3,236",
    "answer": "一言千里",
    "explain": "一言千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 285,
    "question": "4,503,4,236",
    "answer": "再接再厉",
    "explain": "再接再厉"
  },
  {
    "level": 286,
    "question": "202,175,72,236",
    "answer": "晴天霹雳",
    "explain": "晴天霹雳"
  },
  {
    "level": 287,
    "question": "376,376,236,236",
    "answer": "洋洋纚纚",
    "explain": "洋洋纚纚"
  },
  {
    "level": 288,
    "question": "389,323,279,236",
    "answer": "风声鹤唳",
    "explain": "风声鹤唳"
  },
  {
    "level": 289,
    "question": "286,381,412,236",
    "answer": "效犬马力",
    "explain": "效犬马力"
  },
  {
    "level": 290,
    "question": "705,705,237,237",
    "answer": "乐乐陶陶",
    "explain": "乐乐陶陶"
  },
  {
    "level": 291,
    "question": "373,248,193,246",
    "answer": "蛇食鲸吞",
    "explain": "蛇食鲸吞"
  },
  {
    "level": 292,
    "question": "717,717,246,246",
    "answer": "虚虚实实",
    "explain": "虚虚实实"
  },
  {
    "level": 293,
    "question": "437,437,248,248",
    "answer": "浩浩汤汤",
    "explain": "浩浩汤汤"
  },
  {
    "level": 294,
    "question": "361,462,379,248",
    "answer": "鼠腹鸡肠",
    "explain": "鼠腹鸡肠"
  },
  {
    "level": 295,
    "question": "813,31,362,251",
    "answer": "床下牛斗",
    "explain": "床下牛斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 296,
    "question": "369,495,365,251",
    "answer": "龙争虎斗",
    "explain": "龙争虎斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 297,
    "question": "6,162,423,267",
    "answer": "司空见惯",
    "explain": "司空见惯"
  },
  {
    "level": 298,
    "question": "248,412,8,275",
    "answer": "食马留肝",
    "explain": "食马留肝"
  },
  {
    "level": 299,
    "question": "362,375,328,275",
    "answer": "牵羊担酒",
    "explain": "牵羊担酒"
  },
  {
    "level": 300,
    "question": "579,572,412,275",
    "answer": "不识马肝",
    "explain": "不识马肝"
  },
  {
    "level": 301,
    "question": "324,324,279,279",
    "answer": "拉拉杂杂",
    "explain": "拉拉杂杂"
  },
  {
    "level": 302,
    "question": "189,189,279,279",
    "answer": "明明赫赫",
    "explain": "明明赫赫"
  },
  {
    "level": 303,
    "question": "369,295,11,280",
    "answer": "龙生九子",
    "explain": "龙生九子"
  },
  {
    "level": 304,
    "question": "311,311,292,292",
    "answer": "营营逐逐",
    "explain": "营营逐逐"
  },
  {
    "level": 305,
    "question": "193,412,47,295",
    "answer": "金马玉堂",
    "explain": "金马玉堂"
  },
  {
    "level": 306,
    "question": "443,443,295,295",
    "answer": "服服贴贴",
    "explain": "服服贴贴"
  },
  {
    "level": 307,
    "question": "362,457,573,295",
    "answer": "牛角书生",
    "explain": "牛角书生"
  },
  {
    "level": 308,
    "question": "437,437,777,295",
    "answer": "好好先生",
    "explain": "好好先生"
  },
  {
    "level": 309,
    "question": "3,412,572,302",
    "answer": "匹马只轮",
    "explain": "匹马只轮"
  },
  {
    "level": 310,
    "question": "223,223,305,305",
    "answer": "纷纷攘攘",
    "explain": "纷纷攘攘"
  },
  {
    "level": 311,
    "question": "176,176,305,305",
    "answer": "熙熙攘攘",
    "explain": "熙熙攘攘"
  },
  {
    "level": 312,
    "question": "767,298,361,305",
    "answer": "貊乡鼠壤",
    "explain": "貊乡鼠壤"
  },
  {
    "level": 313,
    "question": "369,343,398,305",
    "answer": "龙楼凤阁",
    "explain": "龙楼凤阁"
  },
  {
    "level": 314,
    "question": "362,457,569,305",
    "answer": "牛角之歌",
    "explain": "牛角之歌"
  },
  {
    "level": 315,
    "question": "489,302,489,309",
    "answer": "美轮美奂",
    "explain": "美轮美奂"
  },
  {
    "level": 316,
    "question": "326,9,572,309",
    "answer": "琴棋书画",
    "explain": "琴棋书画"
  },
  {
    "level": 317,
    "question": "338,197,373,312",
    "answer": "杯弓蛇影",
    "explain": "杯弓蛇影"
  },
  {
    "level": 318,
    "question": "44,564,369,314",
    "answer": "云蒸龙变",
    "explain": "云蒸龙变"
  },
  {
    "level": 319,
    "question": "3,497,580,316",
    "answer": "一言为定",
    "explain": "一言为定"
  },
  {
    "level": 320,
    "question": "121,121,319,319",
    "answer": "安安稳稳",
    "explain": "安安稳稳"
  },
  {
    "level": 321,
    "question": "497,497,323,323",
    "answer": "口口声声",
    "explain": "口口声声"
  },
  {
    "level": 322,
    "question": "442,423,32,326",
    "answer": "一见钟情",
    "explain": "一见钟情"
  },
  {
    "level": 323,
    "question": "437,437,328,328",
    "answer": "浩浩荡荡",
    "explain": "浩浩荡荡"
  },
  {
    "level": 324,
    "question": "398,398,328,328",
    "answer": "袅袅娜娜",
    "explain": "袅袅娜娜"
  },
  {
    "level": 325,
    "question": "831,831,328,328",
    "answer": "悠悠荡荡",
    "explain": "悠悠荡荡"
  },
  {
    "level": 326,
    "question": "437,437,333,333",
    "answer": "鼓鼓囊囊",
    "explain": "鼓鼓囊囊"
  },
  {
    "level": 327,
    "question": "398,398,335,335",
    "answer": "袅袅娉娉",
    "explain": "袅袅娉娉"
  },
  {
    "level": 328,
    "question": "369,332,365,335",
    "answer": "龙翔虎跃",
    "explain": "龙翔虎跃"
  },
  {
    "level": 329,
    "question": "442,705,424,336",
    "answer": "一笑而过",
    "explain": "一笑而过"
  },
  {
    "level": 330,
    "question": "89,426,413,337",
    "answer": "尖嘴猴腮",
    "explain": "尖嘴猴腮"
  },
  {
    "level": 331,
    "question": "215,215,215,338",
    "answer": "欣欣向荣",
    "explain": "欣欣向荣"
  },
  {
    "level": 332,
    "question": "9,812,338,362",
    "answer": "蹊田夺牛",
    "explain": "蹊田夺牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 333,
    "question": "366,562,503,362",
    "answer": "庖丁解牛",
    "explain": "庖丁解牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 334,
    "question": "365,367,569,338",
    "answer": "狐兔之悲",
    "explain": "狐兔之悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 335,
    "question": "112,112,339,339",
    "answer": "楚楚谡谡",
    "explain": "楚楚谡谡"
  },
  {
    "level": 336,
    "question": "469,439,373,362",
    "answer": "齐王舍牛",
    "explain": "齐王舍牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 337,
    "question": "379,89,381,339",
    "answer": "鸡飞狗跳",
    "explain": "鸡飞狗跳"
  },
  {
    "level": 338,
    "question": "469,469,831,339",
    "answer": "姗姗来迟",
    "explain": "姗姗来迟"
  },
  {
    "level": 339,
    "question": "159,184,579,342",
    "answer": "无孔不入",
    "explain": "无孔不入"
  },
  {
    "level": 340,
    "question": "648,409,309,365",
    "answer": "照猫画虎",
    "explain": "照猫画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 341,
    "question": "6,182,442,343",
    "answer": "四海一家",
    "explain": "四海一家"
  },
  {
    "level": 342,
    "question": "524,362,336,345",
    "answer": "汗牛充栋",
    "explain": "汗牛充栋"
  },
  {
    "level": 343,
    "question": "228,228,345,345",
    "answer": "密密层层",
    "explain": "密密层层"
  },
  {
    "level": 344,
    "question": "369,772,44,360",
    "answer": "龙举云属",
    "explain": "龙举云属"
  },
  {
    "level": 345,
    "question": "209,236,304,361",
    "answer": "以狸饵鼠",
    "explain": "以狸饵鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 346,
    "question": "381,626,474,361",
    "answer": "狗逮老鼠",
    "explain": "狗逮老鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 347,
    "question": "328,120,480,361",
    "answer": "胆小如鼠",
    "explain": "胆小如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 348,
    "question": "423,72,480,361",
    "answer": "目光如鼠",
    "explain": "目光如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 349,
    "question": "409,361,14,362",
    "answer": "猫鼠同乳",
    "explain": "猫鼠同乳"
  },
  {
    "level": 350,
    "question": "289,655,251,362",
    "answer": "气冲斗牛",
    "explain": "气冲斗牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 351,
    "question": "540,89,540,362",
    "answer": "卖剑买牛",
    "explain": "卖剑买牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 352,
    "question": "5,468,7,365",
    "answer": "三人成虎",
    "explain": "三人成虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 353,
    "question": "369,831,173,365",
    "answer": "龙去鼎湖",
    "explain": "龙去鼎湖"
  },
  {
    "level": 354,
    "question": "775,369,309,365",
    "answer": "乔龙画虎",
    "explain": "乔龙画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 355,
    "question": "110,110,365,365",
    "answer": "家家户户",
    "explain": "家家户户"
  },
  {
    "level": 356,
    "question": "412,412,365,365",
    "answer": "马马虎虎",
    "explain": "马马虎虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 357,
    "question": "831,831,365,365",
    "answer": "悠悠忽忽",
    "explain": "悠悠忽忽"
  },
  {
    "level": 358,
    "question": "650,486,474,365",
    "answer": "打死老虎",
    "explain": "打死老虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 359,
    "question": "220,471,437,369",
    "answer": "叶公好龙",
    "explain": "叶公好龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 360,
    "question": "31,369,768,365",
    "answer": "降龙伏虎",
    "explain": "降龙伏虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 361,
    "question": "11,178,365,366",
    "answer": "九阍虎豹",
    "explain": "九阍虎豹"
  },
  {
    "level": 362,
    "question": "432,365,566,369",
    "answer": "卧虎藏龙",
    "explain": "卧虎藏龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 363,
    "question": "433,206,451,367",
    "answer": "守株待兔",
    "explain": "守株待兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 364,
    "question": "767,480,456,367",
    "answer": "动如脱兔",
    "explain": "动如脱兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 365,
    "question": "3,399,465,367",
    "answer": "一雕双兔",
    "explain": "一雕双兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 366,
    "question": "101,101,368,368",
    "answer": "炳炳烺烺",
    "explain": "炳炳烺烺"
  },
  {
    "level": 367,
    "question": "369,398,7,369",
    "answer": "龙凤呈祥",
    "explain": "龙凤呈祥"
  },
  {
    "level": 368,
    "question": "111,580,194,369",
    "answer": "直捣黄龙",
    "explain": "直捣黄龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 369,
    "question": "275,365,571,369",
    "answer": "酒虎诗龙",
    "explain": "酒虎诗龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 370,
    "question": "650,218,193,373",
    "answer": "打草惊蛇",
    "explain": "打草惊蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 371,
    "question": "197,312,338,373",
    "answer": "弓影杯蛇",
    "explain": "弓影杯蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 372,
    "question": "94,476,369,373",
    "answer": "笔底龙蛇",
    "explain": "笔底龙蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 373,
    "question": "365,772,369,373",
    "answer": "虎踞龙盘",
    "explain": "虎踞龙盘"
  },
  {
    "level": 374,
    "question": "568,568,579,373",
    "answer": "孜孜不倦",
    "explain": "孜孜不倦"
  },
  {
    "level": 375,
    "question": "750,369,831,373",
    "answer": "骇龙走蛇",
    "explain": "骇龙走蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 376,
    "question": "389,92,362,375",
    "answer": "顺手牵羊",
    "explain": "顺手牵羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 377,
    "question": "489,365,399,369",
    "answer": "绣虎雕龙",
    "explain": "绣虎雕龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 378,
    "question": "414,414,377,377",
    "answer": "沸沸扬扬",
    "explain": "沸沸扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 379,
    "question": "249,375,468,368",
    "answer": "使羊将狼",
    "explain": "使羊将狼"
  },
  {
    "level": 380,
    "question": "292,173,705,412",
    "answer": "悬崖勒马",
    "explain": "悬崖勒马"
  },
  {
    "level": 381,
    "question": "365,414,373,378",
    "answer": "虎头蛇尾",
    "explain": "虎头蛇尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 382,
    "question": "536,373,753,378",
    "answer": "贪蛇忘尾",
    "explain": "贪蛇忘尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 383,
    "question": "159,566,159,379",
    "answer": "无边无际",
    "explain": "无边无际"
  },
  {
    "level": 384,
    "question": "101,101,379,379",
    "answer": "彬彬济济",
    "explain": "彬彬济济"
  },
  {
    "level": 385,
    "question": "737,737,379,379",
    "answer": "哼哼唧唧",
    "explain": "哼哼唧唧"
  },
  {
    "level": 386,
    "question": "568,568,379,379",
    "answer": "孜孜汲汲",
    "explain": "孜孜汲汲"
  },
  {
    "level": 387,
    "question": "189,338,437,379",
    "answer": "名胜古迹",
    "explain": "名胜古迹"
  },
  {
    "level": 388,
    "question": "207,361,569,379",
    "answer": "梧鼠之技",
    "explain": "梧鼠之技"
  },
  {
    "level": 389,
    "question": "251,275,572,379",
    "answer": "斗酒只鸡",
    "explain": "斗酒只鸡"
  },
  {
    "level": 390,
    "question": "641,274,647,380",
    "answer": "十万火急",
    "explain": "十万火急"
  },
  {
    "level": 391,
    "question": "110,381,106,381",
    "answer": "嫁狗随狗",
    "explain": "嫁狗随狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 392,
    "question": "311,311,381,381",
    "answer": "营营苟苟",
    "explain": "营营苟苟"
  },
  {
    "level": 393,
    "question": "491,379,412,381",
    "answer": "指鸡骂狗",
    "explain": "指鸡骂狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 394,
    "question": "73,44,566,381",
    "answer": "白云苍狗",
    "explain": "白云苍狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 395,
    "question": "89,367,755,381",
    "answer": "见兔顾犬",
    "explain": "见兔顾犬"
  },
  {
    "level": 396,
    "question": "109,554,628,384",
    "answer": "心之所向",
    "explain": "心之所向"
  },
  {
    "level": 397,
    "question": "480,365,295,389",
    "answer": "如虎添翼",
    "explain": "如虎添翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 398,
    "question": "120,109,389,389",
    "answer": "小心翼翼",
    "explain": "小心翼翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 399,
    "question": "3,84,389,389",
    "answer": "一帆风顺",
    "explain": "一帆风顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 400,
    "question": "3,418,389,389",
    "answer": "一路顺风",
    "explain": "一路顺风"
  },
  {
    "level": 401,
    "question": "750,445,569,412",
    "answer": "害群之马",
    "explain": "害群之马"
  },
  {
    "level": 402,
    "question": "184,495,831,389",
    "answer": "空穴来风",
    "explain": "空穴来风"
  },
  {
    "level": 403,
    "question": "9,326,8,391",
    "answer": "七情六欲",
    "explain": "七情六欲"
  },
  {
    "level": 404,
    "question": "434,434,391,391",
    "answer": "嗫嗫嚅嚅",
    "explain": "嗫嗫嚅嚅"
  },
  {
    "level": 405,
    "question": "159,343,96,394",
    "answer": "无家可归",
    "explain": "无家可归"
  },
  {
    "level": 406,
    "question": "412,831,412,394",
    "answer": "马去马归",
    "explain": "马去马归"
  },
  {
    "level": 407,
    "question": "392,392,396,396",
    "answer": "鱼鱼雅雅",
    "explain": "鱼鱼雅雅"
  },
  {
    "level": 408,
    "question": "442,396,533,396",
    "answer": "一了百了",
    "explain": "一了百了"
  },
  {
    "level": 409,
    "question": "580,580,398,398",
    "answer": "唯唯否否",
    "explain": "唯唯否否"
  },
  {
    "level": 410,
    "question": "209,418,580,412",
    "answer": "以鹿为马",
    "explain": "以鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 411,
    "question": "393,295,746,412",
    "answer": "塞翁失马",
    "explain": "塞翁失马"
  },
  {
    "level": 412,
    "question": "3,365,533,398",
    "answer": "一呼百应",
    "explain": "一呼百应"
  },
  {
    "level": 413,
    "question": "381,637,193,399",
    "answer": "狗续金貂",
    "explain": "狗续金貂"
  },
  {
    "level": 414,
    "question": "3,89,465,399",
    "answer": "一箭双雕",
    "explain": "一箭双雕"
  },
  {
    "level": 415,
    "question": "620,620,402,402",
    "answer": "大大落落",
    "explain": "大大落落"
  },
  {
    "level": 416,
    "question": "491,418,580,412",
    "answer": "指鹿为马",
    "explain": "指鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 417,
    "question": "72,72,402,402",
    "answer": "磊磊落落",
    "explain": "磊磊落落"
  },
  {
    "level": 418,
    "question": "468,468,403,403",
    "answer": "委委佗佗",
    "explain": "委委佗佗"
  },
  {
    "level": 419,
    "question": "389,309,495,409",
    "answer": "风华正茂",
    "explain": "风华正茂"
  },
  {
    "level": 420,
    "question": "193,305,650,412",
    "answer": "金戈铁马",
    "explain": "金戈铁马"
  },
  {
    "level": 421,
    "question": "486,486,410,410",
    "answer": "嘟嘟哝哝",
    "explain": "嘟嘟哝哝"
  },
  {
    "level": 422,
    "question": "10,248,630,410",
    "answer": "八面玲珑",
    "explain": "八面玲珑"
  },
  {
    "level": 423,
    "question": "379,381,5,412",
    "answer": "鸡犬桑麻",
    "explain": "鸡犬桑麻"
  },
  {
    "level": 424,
    "question": "122,801,87,412",
    "answer": "毁车杀马",
    "explain": "毁车杀马"
  },
  {
    "level": 425,
    "question": "219,213,292,412",
    "answer": "青梅竹马",
    "explain": "青梅竹马"
  },
  {
    "level": 426,
    "question": "3,488,540,412",
    "answer": "千兵万马",
    "explain": "千兵万马"
  },
  {
    "level": 427,
    "question": "3,468,540,412",
    "answer": "千军万马",
    "explain": "千军万马"
  },
  {
    "level": 428,
    "question": "479,369,89,413",
    "answer": "神龙见首",
    "explain": "神龙见首"
  },
  {
    "level": 429,
    "question": "445,369,159,413",
    "answer": "群龙无首",
    "explain": "群龙无首"
  },
  {
    "level": 430,
    "question": "87,379,161,413",
    "answer": "杀鸡儆猴",
    "explain": "杀鸡儆猴"
  },
  {
    "level": 431,
    "question": "369,189,366,413",
    "answer": "龙鸣狮吼",
    "explain": "龙鸣狮吼"
  },
  {
    "level": 432,
    "question": "323,180,381,412",
    "answer": "声色犬马",
    "explain": "声色犬马"
  },
  {
    "level": 433,
    "question": "841,362,394,412",
    "answer": "休牛归马",
    "explain": "休牛归马"
  },
  {
    "level": 434,
    "question": "194,194,412,412",
    "answer": "慌慌张张",
    "explain": "慌慌张张"
  },
  {
    "level": 435,
    "question": "209,409,435,412",
    "answer": "以毛相马",
    "explain": "以毛相马"
  },
  {
    "level": 436,
    "question": "572,94,474,412",
    "answer": "识涂老马",
    "explain": "识涂老马"
  },
  {
    "level": 437,
    "question": "398,343,369,414",
    "answer": "凤楼龙阙",
    "explain": "凤楼龙阙"
  },
  {
    "level": 438,
    "question": "379,189,381,414",
    "answer": "鸡鸣狗吠",
    "explain": "鸡鸣狗吠"
  },
  {
    "level": 439,
    "question": "379,189,381,414",
    "answer": "鸡鸣犬吠",
    "explain": "鸡鸣犬吠"
  },
  {
    "level": 440,
    "question": "133,652,384,415",
    "answer": "拔刀相助",
    "explain": "拔刀相助"
  },
  {
    "level": 441,
    "question": "476,362,457,412",
    "answer": "童牛角马",
    "explain": "童牛角马"
  },
  {
    "level": 442,
    "question": "73,73,415,415",
    "answer": "白白朱朱",
    "explain": "白白朱朱"
  },
  {
    "level": 443,
    "question": "44,369,193,416",
    "answer": "云龙井蛙",
    "explain": "云龙井蛙"
  },
  {
    "level": 444,
    "question": "32,32,418,418",
    "answer": "忙忙碌碌",
    "explain": "忙忙碌碌"
  },
  {
    "level": 445,
    "question": "342,342,418,418",
    "answer": "庸庸碌碌",
    "explain": "庸庸碌碌"
  },
  {
    "level": 446,
    "question": "486,373,750,419",
    "answer": "毒蛇猛兽",
    "explain": "毒蛇猛兽"
  },
  {
    "level": 447,
    "question": "3,220,220,423",
    "answer": "一叶障目",
    "explain": "一叶障目"
  },
  {
    "level": 448,
    "question": "538,213,361,423",
    "answer": "贼眉鼠眼",
    "explain": "贼眉鼠眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 449,
    "question": "514,514,423,423",
    "answer": "伈伈睍睍",
    "explain": "伈伈睍睍"
  },
  {
    "level": 450,
    "question": "220,220,424,424",
    "answer": "卿卿我我",
    "explain": "卿卿我我"
  },
  {
    "level": 451,
    "question": "418,426,412,426",
    "answer": "驴唇马嘴",
    "explain": "驴唇马嘴"
  },
  {
    "level": 452,
    "question": "442,426,5,427",
    "answer": "一口三舌",
    "explain": "一口三舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 453,
    "question": "534,460,628,430",
    "answer": "千夫所指",
    "explain": "千夫所指"
  },
  {
    "level": 454,
    "question": "469,469,434,434",
    "answer": "扭扭捏捏",
    "explain": "扭扭捏捏"
  },
  {
    "level": 455,
    "question": "314,314,434,434",
    "answer": "隐隐约约",
    "explain": "隐隐约约"
  },
  {
    "level": 456,
    "question": "176,176,439,439",
    "answer": "熙熙融融",
    "explain": "熙熙融融"
  },
  {
    "level": 457,
    "question": "474,431,628,442",
    "answer": "老有所依",
    "explain": "老有所依"
  },
  {
    "level": 458,
    "question": "73,369,392,443",
    "answer": "白龙鱼服",
    "explain": "白龙鱼服"
  },
  {
    "level": 459,
    "question": "389,309,373,451",
    "answer": "风华绝代",
    "explain": "风华绝代"
  },
  {
    "level": 460,
    "question": "185,185,451,451",
    "answer": "世世代代",
    "explain": "世世代代"
  },
  {
    "level": 461,
    "question": "9,433,10,457",
    "answer": "七手八脚",
    "explain": "七手八脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 462,
    "question": "309,373,295,457",
    "answer": "画蛇添足",
    "explain": "画蛇添足"
  },
  {
    "level": 463,
    "question": "2,375,296,457",
    "answer": "羚羊挂角",
    "explain": "羚羊挂角"
  },
  {
    "level": 464,
    "question": "580,373,309,457",
    "answer": "为蛇画足",
    "explain": "为蛇画足"
  },
  {
    "level": 465,
    "question": "562,562,457,457",
    "answer": "铮铮佼佼",
    "explain": "铮铮佼佼"
  },
  {
    "level": 466,
    "question": "104,369,336,460",
    "answer": "乘龙快婿",
    "explain": "乘龙快婿"
  },
  {
    "level": 467,
    "question": "362,182,575,461",
    "answer": "牛郎织女",
    "explain": "牛郎织女"
  },
  {
    "level": 468,
    "question": "202,457,369,464",
    "answer": "日角龙庭",
    "explain": "日角龙庭"
  },
  {
    "level": 469,
    "question": "540,394,159,468",
    "answer": "万寿无疆",
    "explain": "万寿无疆"
  },
  {
    "level": 470,
    "question": "205,412,159,468",
    "answer": "野马无缰",
    "explain": "野马无缰"
  },
  {
    "level": 471,
    "question": "533,49,209,468",
    "answer": "百年树人",
    "explain": "百年树人"
  },
  {
    "level": 472,
    "question": "72,72,540,468",
    "answer": "雷霆万钧",
    "explain": "雷霆万钧"
  },
  {
    "level": 473,
    "question": "475,412,575,468",
    "answer": "善马熟人",
    "explain": "善马熟人"
  },
  {
    "level": 474,
    "question": "412,418,279,469",
    "answer": "马鹿异形",
    "explain": "马鹿异形"
  },
  {
    "level": 475,
    "question": "365,390,420,469",
    "answer": "虎背熊腰",
    "explain": "虎背熊腰"
  },
  {
    "level": 476,
    "question": "412,218,7,471",
    "answer": "马到成功",
    "explain": "马到成功"
  },
  {
    "level": 477,
    "question": "486,443,479,471",
    "answer": "鬼斧神工",
    "explain": "鬼斧神工"
  },
  {
    "level": 478,
    "question": "524,412,569,471",
    "answer": "汗马之功",
    "explain": "汗马之功"
  },
  {
    "level": 479,
    "question": "506,375,49,474",
    "answer": "亡羊补牢",
    "explain": "亡羊补牢"
  },
  {
    "level": 480,
    "question": "381,414,468,474",
    "answer": "狗头军师",
    "explain": "狗头军师"
  },
  {
    "level": 481,
    "question": "524,412,471,474",
    "answer": "汗马功劳",
    "explain": "汗马功劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 482,
    "question": "333,466,333,476",
    "answer": "难兄难弟",
    "explain": "难兄难弟"
  },
  {
    "level": 483,
    "question": "3,362,413,476",
    "answer": "一牛吼地",
    "explain": "一牛吼地"
  },
  {
    "level": 484,
    "question": "193,175,767,476",
    "answer": "惊天动地",
    "explain": "惊天动地"
  },
  {
    "level": 485,
    "question": "639,175,834,476",
    "answer": "顶天立地",
    "explain": "顶天立地"
  },
  {
    "level": 486,
    "question": "369,412,193,479",
    "answer": "龙马精神",
    "explain": "龙马精神"
  },
  {
    "level": 487,
    "question": "295,295,486,486",
    "answer": "生生死死",
    "explain": "生生死死"
  },
  {
    "level": 488,
    "question": "237,569,486,486",
    "answer": "桃之夭夭",
    "explain": "桃之夭夭"
  },
  {
    "level": 489,
    "question": "7,412,506,486",
    "answer": "五马分尸",
    "explain": "五马分尸"
  },
  {
    "level": 490,
    "question": "1,1,113,489",
    "answer": "井井有条",
    "explain": "井井有条"
  },
  {
    "level": 491,
    "question": "312,312,489,489",
    "answer": "影影绰绰",
    "explain": "影影绰绰"
  },
  {
    "level": 492,
    "question": "445,479,526,489",
    "answer": "群魔乱舞",
    "explain": "群魔乱舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 493,
    "question": "101,212,542,489",
    "answer": "雪花飞舞",
    "explain": "雪花飞舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 494,
    "question": "584,379,818,489",
    "answer": "闻鸡起舞",
    "explain": "闻鸡起舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 495,
    "question": "457,367,5,495",
    "answer": "狡兔三穴",
    "explain": "狡兔三穴"
  },
  {
    "level": 496,
    "question": "549,549,571,571",
    "answer": "原原本本",
    "explain": "原原本本"
  },
  {
    "level": 497,
    "question": "4,361,251,495",
    "answer": "两鼠斗穴",
    "explain": "两鼠斗穴"
  },
  {
    "level": 498,
    "question": "295,295,495,495",
    "answer": "堂堂正正",
    "explain": "堂堂正正"
  },
  {
    "level": 499,
    "question": "381,232,268,496",
    "answer": "狗皮膏药",
    "explain": "狗皮膏药"
  },
  {
    "level": 500,
    "question": "412,456,89,497",
    "answer": "马踏飞燕",
    "explain": "马踏飞燕"
  },
  {
    "level": 501,
    "question": "375,402,365,497",
    "answer": "羊落虎口",
    "explain": "羊落虎口"
  },
  {
    "level": 502,
    "question": "193,47,565,497",
    "answer": "金玉良言",
    "explain": "金玉良言"
  },
  {
    "level": 503,
    "question": "9,9,522,522",
    "answer": "嘁嘁喳喳",
    "explain": "嘁嘁喳喳"
  },
  {
    "level": 504,
    "question": "212,212,185,503",
    "answer": "花花世界",
    "explain": "花花世界"
  },
  {
    "level": 505,
    "question": "369,369,387,503",
    "answer": "龙蟠虬结",
    "explain": "龙蟠虬结"
  },
  {
    "level": 506,
    "question": "43,43,503,503",
    "answer": "煦煦孑孑",
    "explain": "煦煦孑孑"
  },
  {
    "level": 507,
    "question": "464,464,507,507",
    "answer": "恩恩爱爱",
    "explain": "恩恩爱爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 508,
    "question": "237,662,219,512",
    "answer": "桃红柳绿",
    "explain": "桃红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 509,
    "question": "489,218,526,519",
    "answer": "五谷丰登",
    "explain": "五谷丰登"
  },
  {
    "level": 510,
    "question": "474,412,507,521",
    "answer": "老马恋栈",
    "explain": "老马恋栈"
  },
  {
    "level": 511,
    "question": "775,775,522,522",
    "answer": "啛啛喳喳",
    "explain": "啛啛喳喳"
  },
  {
    "level": 512,
    "question": "178,178,522,522",
    "answer": "浑浑噩噩",
    "explain": "浑浑噩噩"
  },
  {
    "level": 513,
    "question": "376,376,524,524",
    "answer": "洋洋洒洒",
    "explain": "洋洋洒洒"
  },
  {
    "level": 514,
    "question": "4,369,480,525",
    "answer": "二龙戏珠",
    "explain": "二龙戏珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 515,
    "question": "412,30,524,525",
    "answer": "马前泼水",
    "explain": "马前泼水"
  },
  {
    "level": 516,
    "question": "369,339,365,526",
    "answer": "龙驰虎骤",
    "explain": "龙驰虎骤"
  },
  {
    "level": 517,
    "question": "289,474,10,527",
    "answer": "七老八十",
    "explain": "七老八十"
  },
  {
    "level": 518,
    "question": "533,274,419,527",
    "answer": "百万雄师",
    "explain": "百万雄师"
  },
  {
    "level": 519,
    "question": "5,460,8,528",
    "answer": "三头六臂",
    "explain": "三头六臂"
  },
  {
    "level": 520,
    "question": "2,2,529,529",
    "answer": "零零星星",
    "explain": "零零星星"
  },
  {
    "level": 521,
    "question": "572,579,110,530",
    "answer": "文不加点",
    "explain": "文不加点"
  },
  {
    "level": 522,
    "question": "364,364,530,530",
    "answer": "斑斑点点",
    "explain": "斑斑点点"
  },
  {
    "level": 523,
    "question": "529,529,530,530",
    "answer": "星星点点",
    "explain": "星星点点"
  },
  {
    "level": 524,
    "question": "368,246,365,531",
    "answer": "狼吞虎咽",
    "explain": "狼吞虎咽"
  },
  {
    "level": 525,
    "question": "373,369,569,531",
    "answer": "盘龙之癖",
    "explain": "盘龙之癖"
  },
  {
    "level": 526,
    "question": "442,26,471,534",
    "answer": "一表人才",
    "explain": "一表人才"
  },
  {
    "level": 527,
    "question": "338,525,801,534",
    "answer": "杯水车薪",
    "explain": "杯水车薪"
  },
  {
    "level": 528,
    "question": "111,476,821,534",
    "answer": "釜底抽薪",
    "explain": "釜底抽薪"
  },
  {
    "level": 529,
    "question": "367,215,497,540",
    "answer": "兔葵燕麦",
    "explain": "兔葵燕麦"
  },
  {
    "level": 530,
    "question": "3,3,540,540",
    "answer": "千千万万",
    "explain": "千千万万"
  },
  {
    "level": 531,
    "question": "529,647,647,549",
    "answer": "星火燎原",
    "explain": "星火燎原"
  },
  {
    "level": 532,
    "question": "212,423,212,552",
    "answer": "花见花开",
    "explain": "花见花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 533,
    "question": "209,412,9,554",
    "answer": "倚马七纸",
    "explain": "倚马七纸"
  },
  {
    "level": 534,
    "question": "384,113,65,558",
    "answer": "相由心生",
    "explain": "相由心生"
  },
  {
    "level": 535,
    "question": "193,193,521,521",
    "answer": "兢兢战战",
    "explain": "兢兢战战"
  },
  {
    "level": 536,
    "question": "365,314,369,564",
    "answer": "虎变龙蒸",
    "explain": "虎变龙蒸"
  },
  {
    "level": 537,
    "question": "389,389,647,647",
    "answer": "风风火火",
    "explain": "风风火火"
  },
  {
    "level": 538,
    "question": "336,412,110,566",
    "answer": "快马加鞭",
    "explain": "快马加鞭"
  },
  {
    "level": 539,
    "question": "392,392,566,566",
    "answer": "郁郁苍苍",
    "explain": "郁郁苍苍"
  },
  {
    "level": 540,
    "question": "550,550,571,571",
    "answer": "源源本本",
    "explain": "源源本本"
  },
  {
    "level": 541,
    "question": "366,366,572,572",
    "answer": "斯斯文文",
    "explain": "斯斯文文"
  },
  {
    "level": 542,
    "question": "362,457,296,573",
    "answer": "牛角挂书",
    "explain": "牛角挂书"
  },
  {
    "level": 543,
    "question": "193,193,576,576",
    "answer": "兢兢业业",
    "explain": "兢兢业业"
  },
  {
    "level": 544,
    "question": "87,379,580,576",
    "answer": "杀鸡为黍",
    "explain": "杀鸡为黍"
  },
  {
    "level": 545,
    "question": "290,290,580,580",
    "answer": "絮絮叨叨",
    "explain": "絮絮叨叨"
  },
  {
    "level": 546,
    "question": "223,223,584,584",
    "answer": "纷纷扰扰",
    "explain": "纷纷扰扰"
  },
  {
    "level": 547,
    "question": "97,170,9,628",
    "answer": "不得其所",
    "explain": "不得其所"
  },
  {
    "level": 548,
    "question": "770,424,652,630",
    "answer": "掩耳盗铃",
    "explain": "掩耳盗铃"
  },
  {
    "level": 549,
    "question": "369,213,366,631",
    "answer": "龙眉豹颈",
    "explain": "龙眉豹颈"
  },
  {
    "level": 550,
    "question": "533,159,442,641",
    "answer": "百无一失",
    "explain": "百无一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 551,
    "question": "369,374,398,645",
    "answer": "龙章凤函",
    "explain": "龙章凤函"
  },
  {
    "level": 552,
    "question": "232,43,6,647",
    "answer": "骄阳似火",
    "explain": "骄阳似火"
  },
  {
    "level": 553,
    "question": "279,279,647,647",
    "answer": "赫赫炎炎",
    "explain": "赫赫炎炎"
  },
  {
    "level": 554,
    "question": "89,389,768,647",
    "answer": "飞蛾扑火",
    "explain": "飞蛾扑火"
  },
  {
    "level": 555,
    "question": "818,369,569,650",
    "answer": "祖龙之虐",
    "explain": "祖龙之虐"
  },
  {
    "level": 556,
    "question": "327,327,650,650",
    "answer": "吹吹打打",
    "explain": "吹吹打打"
  },
  {
    "level": 557,
    "question": "93,248,5,652",
    "answer": "两面三刀",
    "explain": "两面三刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 558,
    "question": "316,412,341,652",
    "answer": "驽马铅刀",
    "explain": "驽马铅刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 559,
    "question": "274,159,442,641",
    "answer": "万无一失",
    "explain": "万无一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 560,
    "question": "93,746,622,652",
    "answer": "两肋插刀",
    "explain": "两肋插刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 561,
    "question": "279,492,175,653",
    "answer": "异想天开",
    "explain": "异想天开"
  },
  {
    "level": 562,
    "question": "392,369,32,654",
    "answer": "鱼龙曼衍",
    "explain": "鱼龙曼衍"
  },
  {
    "level": 563,
    "question": "285,413,424,659",
    "answer": "沐猴而冠",
    "explain": "沐猴而冠"
  },
  {
    "level": 564,
    "question": "412,246,31,696",
    "answer": "马放南山",
    "explain": "马放南山"
  },
  {
    "level": 565,
    "question": "391,365,236,696",
    "answer": "调虎离山",
    "explain": "调虎离山"
  },
  {
    "level": 566,
    "question": "750,365,465,696",
    "answer": "猛虎出山",
    "explain": "猛虎出山"
  },
  {
    "level": 567,
    "question": "442,94,96,705",
    "answer": "一笔勾销",
    "explain": "一笔勾销"
  },
  {
    "level": 568,
    "question": "213,144,213,705",
    "answer": "没完没了",
    "explain": "没完没了"
  },
  {
    "level": 569,
    "question": "475,475,723,723",
    "answer": "善善恶恶",
    "explain": "善善恶恶"
  },
  {
    "level": 570,
    "question": "43,380,199,746",
    "answer": "日积月累",
    "explain": "日积月累"
  },
  {
    "level": 571,
    "question": "365,486,367,746",
    "answer": "狐死兔泣",
    "explain": "狐死兔泣"
  },
  {
    "level": 572,
    "question": "611,170,611,746",
    "answer": "患得患失",
    "explain": "患得患失"
  },
  {
    "level": 573,
    "question": "746,746,746,746",
    "answer": "哭哭啼啼",
    "explain": "哭哭啼啼"
  },
  {
    "level": 574,
    "question": "568,568,746,746",
    "answer": "孜孜矻矻",
    "explain": "孜孜矻矻"
  },
  {
    "level": 575,
    "question": "412,579,828,746",
    "answer": "马不停蹄",
    "explain": "马不停蹄"
  },
  {
    "level": 576,
    "question": "821,47,750,750",
    "answer": "烟雨蒙蒙",
    "explain": "烟雨蒙蒙"
  },
  {
    "level": 577,
    "question": "374,412,30,767",
    "answer": "驷马仰秣",
    "explain": "驷马仰秣"
  },
  {
    "level": 578,
    "question": "750,750,767,767",
    "answer": "懵懵懂懂",
    "explain": "懵懵懂懂"
  },
  {
    "level": 579,
    "question": "538,538,767,767",
    "answer": "偷偷摸摸",
    "explain": "偷偷摸摸"
  },
  {
    "level": 580,
    "question": "486,486,768,768",
    "answer": "鬼鬼祟祟",
    "explain": "鬼鬼祟祟"
  },
  {
    "level": 581,
    "question": "831,831,768,768",
    "answer": "踉踉跄跄",
    "explain": "踉踉跄跄"
  },
  {
    "level": 582,
    "question": "361,275,387,772",
    "answer": "鼠肝虫臂",
    "explain": "鼠肝虫臂"
  },
  {
    "level": 583,
    "question": "369,705,398,772",
    "answer": "龙兴凤举",
    "explain": "龙兴凤举"
  },
  {
    "level": 584,
    "question": "570,570,772,772",
    "answer": "支支吾吾",
    "explain": "支支吾吾"
  },
  {
    "level": 585,
    "question": "480,362,111,780",
    "answer": "如牛负重",
    "explain": "如牛负重"
  },
  {
    "level": 586,
    "question": "620,620,780,780",
    "answer": "大大咧咧",
    "explain": "大大咧咧"
  },
  {
    "level": 587,
    "question": "521,521,780,780",
    "answer": "轰轰烈烈",
    "explain": "轰轰烈烈"
  },
  {
    "level": 588,
    "question": "821,821,788,788",
    "answer": "抽抽搭搭",
    "explain": "抽抽搭搭"
  },
  {
    "level": 589,
    "question": "389,339,72,801",
    "answer": "风驰电掣",
    "explain": "风驰电掣"
  },
  {
    "level": 590,
    "question": "324,324,801,801",
    "answer": "拉拉扯扯",
    "explain": "拉拉扯扯"
  },
  {
    "level": 591,
    "question": "497,384,292,812",
    "answer": "口若悬河",
    "explain": "口若悬河"
  },
  {
    "level": 592,
    "question": "3,365,579,812",
    "answer": "一虎不河",
    "explain": "一虎不河"
  },
  {
    "level": 593,
    "question": "801,412,39,819",
    "answer": "车马填门",
    "explain": "车马填门"
  },
  {
    "level": 594,
    "question": "374,412,268,819",
    "answer": "驷马高盖",
    "explain": "驷马高盖"
  },
  {
    "level": 595,
    "question": "398,398,820,820",
    "answer": "袅袅婷婷",
    "explain": "袅袅婷婷"
  },
  {
    "level": 596,
    "question": "374,412,333,829",
    "answer": "驷马难追",
    "explain": "驷马难追"
  },
  {
    "level": 597,
    "question": "173,7,369,831",
    "answer": "鼎成龙去",
    "explain": "鼎成龙去"
  },
  {
    "level": 598,
    "question": "251,506,373,831",
    "answer": "斗折蛇行",
    "explain": "斗折蛇行"
  },
  {
    "level": 599,
    "question": "457,47,373,831",
    "answer": "膝语蛇行",
    "explain": "膝语蛇行"
  },
  {
    "level": 600,
    "question": "580,580,831,831",
    "answer": "唯唯诺诺",
    "explain": "唯唯诺诺"
  },
  {
    "level": 601,
    "question": "389,812,202,834",
    "answer": "风和日丽",
    "explain": "风和日丽"
  },
  {
    "level": 602,
    "question": "193,379,458,834",
    "answer": "金鸡独立",
    "explain": "金鸡独立"
  },
  {
    "level": 603,
    "question": "238,238,503,834",
    "answer": "茕茕孑立",
    "explain": "茕茕孑立"
  },
  {
    "level": 604,
    "question": "178,178,838,838",
    "answer": "浑浑沌沌",
    "explain": "浑浑沌沌"
  },
  {
    "level": 605,
    "question": "3,248,553,73",
    "answer": "一面之缘",
    "explain": "一面之缘"
  },
  {
    "level": 606,
    "question": "553,262,9,280",
    "answer": "自取其辱",
    "explain": "自取其辱"
  },
  {
    "level": 607,
    "question": "553,73,9,584",
    "answer": "自圆其说",
    "explain": "自圆其说"
  },
  {
    "level": 608,
    "question": "630,831,768,134",
    "answer": "令人作呕",
    "explain": "令人作呕"
  },
  {
    "level": 609,
    "question": "65,280,652,168",
    "answer": "心如刀割",
    "explain": "心如刀割"
  },
  {
    "level": 610,
    "question": "624,650,773,433",
    "answer": "大打出手",
    "explain": "大打出手"
  },
  {
    "level": 611,
    "question": "205,336,471,336",
    "answer": "你追我赶",
    "explain": "你追我赶"
  },
  {
    "level": 612,
    "question": "7,171,526,771",
    "answer": "无可奉告",
    "explain": "无可奉告"
  },
  {
    "level": 613,
    "question": "241,460,174,493",
    "answer": "披头散发",
    "explain": "披头散发"
  },
  {
    "level": 614,
    "question": "476,750,526,4",
    "answer": "饱经风霜",
    "explain": "饱经风霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 615,
    "question": "399,460,461,821",
    "answer": "鹤发童颜",
    "explain": "鹤发童颜"
  },
  {
    "level": 616,
    "question": "248,513,380,433",
    "answer": "面黄肌瘦",
    "explain": "面黄肌瘦"
  },
  {
    "level": 617,
    "question": "482,653,236,528",
    "answer": "身强力壮",
    "explain": "身强力壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 618,
    "question": "213,326,423,425",
    "answer": "眉清目秀",
    "explain": "眉清目秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 619,
    "question": "176,423,435,702",
    "answer": "明眸皓齿",
    "explain": "明眸皓齿"
  },
  {
    "level": 620,
    "question": "213,236,280,309",
    "answer": "眉目如画",
    "explain": "眉目如画"
  },
  {
    "level": 621,
    "question": "442,183,511,512",
    "answer": "衣衫褴褛",
    "explain": "衣衫褴褛"
  },
  {
    "level": 622,
    "question": "624,295,527,527",
    "answer": "大腹便便",
    "explain": "大腹便便"
  },
  {
    "level": 623,
    "question": "224,433,280,534",
    "answer": "骨瘦如柴",
    "explain": "骨瘦如柴"
  },
  {
    "level": 624,
    "question": "75,43,326,399",
    "answer": "体态轻盈",
    "explain": "体态轻盈"
  },
  {
    "level": 625,
    "question": "9,528,3,442",
    "answer": "奇装异服",
    "explain": "奇装异服"
  },
  {
    "level": 626,
    "question": "73,236,460,662",
    "answer": "白里透红",
    "explain": "白里透红"
  },
  {
    "level": 627,
    "question": "248,766,96,760",
    "answer": "面不改色",
    "explain": "面不改色"
  },
  {
    "level": 628,
    "question": "562,213,183,423",
    "answer": "慈眉善目",
    "explain": "慈眉善目"
  },
  {
    "level": 629,
    "question": "113,647,553,170",
    "answer": "悠然自得",
    "explain": "悠然自得"
  },
  {
    "level": 630,
    "question": "489,750,650,422",
    "answer": "无精打采",
    "explain": "无精打采"
  },
  {
    "level": 631,
    "question": "164,766,750,109",
    "answer": "漫不经心",
    "explain": "漫不经心"
  },
  {
    "level": 632,
    "question": "650,460,532,289",
    "answer": "垂头丧气",
    "explain": "垂头丧气"
  },
  {
    "level": 633,
    "question": "182,482,602,415",
    "answer": "全神贯注",
    "explain": "全神贯注"
  },
  {
    "level": 634,
    "question": "482,422,89,401",
    "answer": "神采飞扬",
    "explain": "神采飞扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 635,
    "question": "482,43,553,756",
    "answer": "神态自若",
    "explain": "神态自若"
  },
  {
    "level": 636,
    "question": "170,442,423,109",
    "answer": "得意忘形",
    "explain": "得意忘形"
  },
  {
    "level": 637,
    "question": "423,519,426,752",
    "answer": "目瞪口呆",
    "explain": "目瞪口呆"
  },
  {
    "level": 638,
    "question": "553,584,289,401",
    "answer": "趾高气扬",
    "explain": "趾高气扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 639,
    "question": "131,395,164,553",
    "answer": "踌躇满志",
    "explain": "踌躇满志"
  },
  {
    "level": 640,
    "question": "624,600,705,479",
    "answer": "大惊小怪",
    "explain": "大惊小怪"
  },
  {
    "level": 641,
    "question": "43,647,553,756",
    "answer": "泰然自若",
    "explain": "泰然自若"
  },
  {
    "level": 642,
    "question": "624,750,527,760",
    "answer": "大惊失色",
    "explain": "大惊失色"
  },
  {
    "level": 643,
    "question": "387,410,766,475",
    "answer": "从容不迫",
    "explain": "从容不迫"
  },
  {
    "level": 644,
    "question": "112,554,43,647",
    "answer": "处之泰然",
    "explain": "处之泰然"
  },
  {
    "level": 645,
    "question": "768,236,766,723",
    "answer": "坐立不安",
    "explain": "坐立不安"
  },
  {
    "level": 646,
    "question": "647,524,5,474",
    "answer": "火冒三丈",
    "explain": "火冒三丈"
  },
  {
    "level": 647,
    "question": "821,424,165,590",
    "answer": "言而有信",
    "explain": "言而有信"
  },
  {
    "level": 648,
    "question": "442,821,278,562",
    "answer": "一言九鼎",
    "explain": "一言九鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 649,
    "question": "3,647,70,647",
    "answer": "毅然决然",
    "explain": "毅然决然"
  },
  {
    "level": 650,
    "question": "630,380,236,506",
    "answer": "当机立断",
    "explain": "当机立断"
  },
  {
    "level": 651,
    "question": "72,236,526,590",
    "answer": "雷厉风行",
    "explain": "雷厉风行"
  },
  {
    "level": 652,
    "question": "113,391,766,70",
    "answer": "犹豫不决",
    "explain": "犹豫不决"
  },
  {
    "level": 653,
    "question": "112,424,246,424",
    "answer": "出尔反尔",
    "explain": "出尔反尔"
  },
  {
    "level": 654,
    "question": "821,647,443,701",
    "answer": "嫣然一笑",
    "explain": "嫣然一笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 655,
    "question": "735,364,164,248",
    "answer": "泪流满面",
    "explain": "泪流满面"
  },
  {
    "level": 656,
    "question": "735,280,391,429",
    "answer": "泪如雨下",
    "explain": "泪如雨下"
  },
  {
    "level": 657,
    "question": "735,423,414,414",
    "answer": "泪眼汪汪",
    "explain": "泪眼汪汪"
  },
  {
    "level": 658,
    "question": "435,182,624,746",
    "answer": "嚎啕大哭",
    "explain": "嚎啕大哭"
  },
  {
    "level": 659,
    "question": "705,702,423,552",
    "answer": "喜笑颜开",
    "explain": "喜笑颜开"
  },
  {
    "level": 660,
    "question": "213,552,423,702",
    "answer": "眉开眼笑",
    "explain": "眉开眼笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 661,
    "question": "705,705,624,702",
    "answer": "哈哈大笑",
    "explain": "哈哈大笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 662,
    "question": "654,654,443,702",
    "answer": "微微一笑",
    "explain": "微微一笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 663,
    "question": "553,428,584,488",
    "answer": "纸上谈兵",
    "explain": "纸上谈兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 664,
    "question": "753,65,305,271",
    "answer": "卧薪尝胆",
    "explain": "卧薪尝胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 665,
    "question": "5,474,8,248",
    "answer": "三头六面",
    "explain": "三头六面"
  },
  {
    "level": 666,
    "question": "474,474,6,652",
    "answer": "头头是道",
    "explain": "头头是道"
  },
  {
    "level": 667,
    "question": "423,248,424,289",
    "answer": "掩面而泣",
    "explain": "掩面而泣"
  },
  {
    "level": 668,
    "question": "6,182,654,343",
    "answer": "四海为家",
    "explain": "四海为家"
  },
  {
    "level": 669,
    "question": "533,236,489,443",
    "answer": "百里挑一",
    "explain": "百里挑一"
  },
  {
    "level": 670,
    "question": "278,362,3,409",
    "answer": "九牛一毛",
    "explain": "九牛一毛"
  },
  {
    "level": 671,
    "question": "443,409,766,462",
    "answer": "一毛不拔",
    "explain": "一毛不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 672,
    "question": "438,489,457,652",
    "answer": "手舞足蹈",
    "explain": "手舞足蹈"
  },
  {
    "level": 673,
    "question": "289,438,10,456",
    "answer": "七手八脚",
    "explain": "七手八脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 674,
    "question": "171,812,75,652",
    "answer": "刻舟求剑",
    "explain": "刻舟求剑"
  },
  {
    "level": 675,
    "question": "248,248,772,652",
    "answer": "面面俱到",
    "explain": "面面俱到"
  },
  {
    "level": 676,
    "question": "410,821,526,526",
    "answer": "浓烟滚滚",
    "explain": "浓烟滚滚"
  },
  {
    "level": 677,
    "question": "538,821,274,391",
    "answer": "千言万语",
    "explain": "千言万语"
  },
  {
    "level": 678,
    "question": "6,457,206,184",
    "answer": "四脚朝天",
    "explain": "四脚朝天"
  },
  {
    "level": 679,
    "question": "768,1,423,44",
    "answer": "坐井观天",
    "explain": "坐井观天"
  },
  {
    "level": 680,
    "question": "280,43,32,44",
    "answer": "如日中天",
    "explain": "如日中天"
  },
  {
    "level": 681,
    "question": "230,534,428,274",
    "answer": "成千上万",
    "explain": "成千上万"
  },
  {
    "level": 682,
    "question": "624,45,705,232",
    "answer": "大呼小叫",
    "explain": "大呼小叫"
  },
  {
    "level": 683,
    "question": "474,705,492,534",
    "answer": "恭喜发财",
    "explain": "恭喜发财"
  },
  {
    "level": 684,
    "question": "73,438,554,505",
    "answer": "白首之心",
    "explain": "白首之心"
  },
  {
    "level": 685,
    "question": "501,501,226,226",
    "answer": "亲亲切切",
    "explain": "亲亲切切"
  },
  {
    "level": 686,
    "question": "336,554,766,3",
    "answer": "来之不易",
    "explain": "来之不易"
  },
  {
    "level": 687,
    "question": "423,425,105,226",
    "answer": "望闻问切",
    "explain": "望闻问切"
  },
  {
    "level": 688,
    "question": "766,431,554,415",
    "answer": "不由自主",
    "explain": "不由自主"
  },
  {
    "level": 689,
    "question": "388,39,274,442",
    "answer": "以防万一",
    "explain": "以防万一"
  },
  {
    "level": 690,
    "question": "435,753,766,305",
    "answer": "好梦不长",
    "explain": "好梦不长"
  },
  {
    "level": 691,
    "question": "388,423,399,647",
    "answer": "一目了然",
    "explain": "一目了然"
  },
  {
    "level": 692,
    "question": "624,662,624,512",
    "answer": "大红大绿",
    "explain": "大红大绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 693,
    "question": "388,369,388,373",
    "answer": "一龙一蛇",
    "explain": "一龙一蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 694,
    "question": "305,474,746,292",
    "answer": "埋头苦干",
    "explain": "埋头苦干"
  },
  {
    "level": 695,
    "question": "230,647,653,499",
    "answer": "趁火抢劫",
    "explain": "趁火抢劫"
  },
  {
    "level": 696,
    "question": "659,553,391,223",
    "answer": "金枝玉叶",
    "explain": "金枝玉叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 697,
    "question": "734,78,380,647",
    "answer": "凶多吉少",
    "explain": "凶多吉少"
  },
  {
    "level": 698,
    "question": "507,426,392,443",
    "answer": "心口如一",
    "explain": "心口如一"
  },
  {
    "level": 699,
    "question": "222,305,753,78",
    "answer": "夜长梦多",
    "explain": "夜长梦多"
  },
  {
    "level": 700,
    "question": "705,181,630,369",
    "answer": "小巧玲珑",
    "explain": "小巧玲珑"
  },
  {
    "level": 701,
    "question": "101,428,110,4",
    "answer": "雪上加霜",
    "explain": "雪上加霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 702,
    "question": "467,467,750,750",
    "answer": "战战兢兢",
    "explain": "战战兢兢"
  },
  {
    "level": 703,
    "question": "519,44,212,43",
    "answer": "光天化日",
    "explain": "光天化日"
  },
  {
    "level": 704,
    "question": "525,223,641,112",
    "answer": "水落石出",
    "explain": "水落石出"
  },
  {
    "level": 705,
    "question": "705,105,707,423",
    "answer": "喜闻乐见",
    "explain": "喜闻乐见"
  },
  {
    "level": 706,
    "question": "278,620,522,6",
    "answer": "醉生梦死",
    "explain": "醉生梦死"
  },
  {
    "level": 707,
    "question": "384,280,442,525",
    "answer": "相濡以沫",
    "explain": "相濡以沫"
  },
  {
    "level": 708,
    "question": "525,33,641,812",
    "answer": "水滴石穿",
    "explain": "水滴石穿"
  },
  {
    "level": 709,
    "question": "734,165,230,292",
    "answer": "胸有成竹",
    "explain": "胸有成竹"
  },
  {
    "level": 710,
    "question": "426,526,212,47",
    "answer": "春风化雨",
    "explain": "春风化雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 711,
    "question": "206,305,184,89",
    "answer": "草长莺飞",
    "explain": "草长莺飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 712,
    "question": "189,766,794,649",
    "answer": "按部就班",
    "explain": "按部就班"
  },
  {
    "level": 713,
    "question": "533,772,533,82",
    "answer": "百举百全",
    "explain": "百举百全"
  },
  {
    "level": 714,
    "question": "244,101,410,212",
    "answer": "冰雪融化",
    "explain": "冰雪融化"
  },
  {
    "level": 715,
    "question": "496,384,270,529",
    "answer": "万象更新",
    "explain": "万象更新"
  },
  {
    "level": 716,
    "question": "533,214,308,552",
    "answer": "百花盛开",
    "explain": "百花盛开"
  },
  {
    "level": 717,
    "question": "533,212,96,821",
    "answer": "百花争艳",
    "explain": "百花争艳"
  },
  {
    "level": 718,
    "question": "533,216,9,493",
    "answer": "百花齐发",
    "explain": "百花齐发"
  },
  {
    "level": 719,
    "question": "326,103,554,161",
    "answer": "情不自禁",
    "explain": "情不自禁"
  },
  {
    "level": 720,
    "question": "50,44,50,176",
    "answer": "欢天喜地",
    "explain": "欢天喜地"
  },
  {
    "level": 721,
    "question": "505,214,734,39",
    "answer": "心花怒放",
    "explain": "心花怒放"
  },
  {
    "level": 722,
    "question": "308,242,72,652",
    "answer": "神魂颠倒",
    "explain": "神魂颠倒"
  },
  {
    "level": 723,
    "question": "246,497,271,257",
    "answer": "方寸大乱",
    "explain": "方寸大乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 724,
    "question": "398,392,214,384",
    "answer": "鸟语花香",
    "explain": "鸟语花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 725,
    "question": "426,616,212,552",
    "answer": "春暖花开",
    "explain": "春暖花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 726,
    "question": "648,47,72,817",
    "answer": "电闪雷鸣",
    "explain": "电闪雷鸣"
  },
  {
    "level": 727,
    "question": "426,220,766,323",
    "answer": "寸草不生",
    "explain": "寸草不生"
  },
  {
    "level": 728,
    "question": "3,528,553,236",
    "answer": "一臂之力",
    "explain": "一臂之力"
  },
  {
    "level": 729,
    "question": "647,213,553,379",
    "answer": "燃眉之急",
    "explain": "燃眉之急"
  },
  {
    "level": 730,
    "question": "630,271,409,496",
    "answer": "灵丹妙药",
    "explain": "灵丹妙药"
  },
  {
    "level": 731,
    "question": "6,182,558,234",
    "answer": "四海升平",
    "explain": "四海升平"
  },
  {
    "level": 732,
    "question": "539,488,3,493",
    "answer": "千钧一发",
    "explain": "千钧一发"
  },
  {
    "level": 733,
    "question": "539,696,184,525",
    "answer": "千山万水",
    "explain": "千山万水"
  },
  {
    "level": 734,
    "question": "392,641,772,527",
    "answer": "玉石俱焚",
    "explain": "玉石俱焚"
  },
  {
    "level": 735,
    "question": "32,460,326,461",
    "answer": "重男轻女",
    "explain": "重男轻女"
  },
  {
    "level": 736,
    "question": "44,525,3,760",
    "answer": "天水一色",
    "explain": "天水一色"
  },
  {
    "level": 737,
    "question": "388,26,460,534",
    "answer": "一表人才",
    "explain": "一表人才"
  },
  {
    "level": 738,
    "question": "164,44,234,182",
    "answer": "瞒天过海",
    "explain": "瞒天过海"
  },
  {
    "level": 739,
    "question": "72,433,696,650",
    "answer": "电劈石击",
    "explain": "电劈石击"
  },
  {
    "level": 740,
    "question": "828,524,470,647",
    "answer": "出水芙蓉",
    "explain": "出水芙蓉"
  },
  {
    "level": 741,
    "question": "3,775,110,289",
    "answer": "一身正气",
    "explain": "一身正气"
  },
  {
    "level": 742,
    "question": "819,162,384,841",
    "answer": "碧空如洗",
    "explain": "碧空如洗"
  },
  {
    "level": 743,
    "question": "206,211,337,831",
    "answer": "春花烂漫",
    "explain": "春花烂漫"
  },
  {
    "level": 744,
    "question": "151,423,526,821",
    "answer": "过眼云烟",
    "explain": "过眼云烟"
  },
  {
    "level": 745,
    "question": "212,373,110,453",
    "answer": "画蛇添足",
    "explain": "画蛇添足"
  },
  {
    "level": 746,
    "question": "423,130,103,286",
    "answer": "目中无人",
    "explain": "目中无人"
  },
  {
    "level": 747,
    "question": "373,89,580,460",
    "answer": "舍己为人",
    "explain": "舍己为人"
  },
  {
    "level": 748,
    "question": "3,219,257,812",
    "answer": "一叶扁舟",
    "explain": "一叶扁舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 749,
    "question": "432,365,566,369",
    "answer": "卧虎藏龙",
    "explain": "卧虎藏龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 750,
    "question": "132,369,132,381",
    "answer": "阿猫阿狗",
    "explain": "阿猫阿狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 751,
    "question": "507,92,507,457",
    "answer": "碍手碍脚",
    "explain": "碍手碍脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 752,
    "question": "776,776,497,497",
    "answer": "安安稳稳",
    "explain": "安安稳稳"
  },
  {
    "level": 753,
    "question": "121,29,374,28",
    "answer": "鞍前马后",
    "explain": "鞍前马后"
  },
  {
    "level": 754,
    "question": "134,134,450,280",
    "answer": "嗷嗷待哺",
    "explain": "嗷嗷待哺"
  },
  {
    "level": 755,
    "question": "134,425,2,2",
    "answer": "傲骨嶙嶙",
    "explain": "傲骨嶙嶙"
  },
  {
    "level": 756,
    "question": "73,412,103,412",
    "answer": "白马非马",
    "explain": "白马非马"
  },
  {
    "level": 757,
    "question": "73,101,507,507",
    "answer": "白雪皑皑",
    "explain": "白雪皑皑"
  },
  {
    "level": 758,
    "question": "533,777,533,316",
    "answer": "百发百中",
    "explain": "百发百中"
  },
  {
    "level": 759,
    "question": "533,443,533,68",
    "answer": "百依百顺",
    "explain": "百依百顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 760,
    "question": "533,521,533,338",
    "answer": "百战百胜",
    "explain": "百战百胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 761,
    "question": "364,364,524,524",
    "answer": "斑斑点点",
    "explain": "斑斑点点"
  },
  {
    "level": 762,
    "question": "819,30,651,651",
    "answer": "板上钉钉",
    "explain": "板上钉钉"
  },
  {
    "level": 763,
    "question": "10,753,10,507",
    "answer": "半梦半醒",
    "explain": "半梦半醒"
  },
  {
    "level": 764,
    "question": "10,69,10,11",
    "answer": "半推半就",
    "explain": "半推半就"
  },
  {
    "level": 765,
    "question": "10,90,10,3",
    "answer": "半信半疑",
    "explain": "半信半疑"
  },
  {
    "level": 766,
    "question": "10,495,10,110",
    "answer": "半真半假",
    "explain": "半真半假"
  },
  {
    "level": 767,
    "question": "767,415,361,784",
    "answer": "抱头鼠窜",
    "explain": "抱头鼠窜"
  },
  {
    "level": 768,
    "question": "338,197,373,312",
    "answer": "杯弓蛇影",
    "explain": "杯弓蛇影"
  },
  {
    "level": 769,
    "question": "338,32,373,312",
    "answer": "杯中蛇影",
    "explain": "杯中蛇影"
  },
  {
    "level": 770,
    "question": "571,92,571,457",
    "answer": "笨手笨脚",
    "explain": "笨手笨脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 771,
    "question": "571,460,571,415",
    "answer": "笨头笨脑",
    "explain": "笨头笨脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 772,
    "question": "94,95,499,96",
    "answer": "比比皆是",
    "explain": "比比皆是"
  },
  {
    "level": 773,
    "question": "94,566,94,566",
    "answer": "彼此彼此",
    "explain": "彼此彼此"
  },
  {
    "level": 774,
    "question": "94,304,94,441",
    "answer": "必恭必敬",
    "explain": "必恭必敬"
  },
  {
    "level": 775,
    "question": "94,304,94,441",
    "answer": "毕恭毕敬",
    "explain": "毕恭毕敬"
  },
  {
    "level": 776,
    "question": "101,101,165,282",
    "answer": "彬彬有礼",
    "explain": "彬彬有礼"
  },
  {
    "level": 777,
    "question": "488,290,412,526",
    "answer": "兵荒马乱",
    "explain": "兵荒马乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 778,
    "question": "488,290,412,526",
    "answer": "兵慌马乱",
    "explain": "兵慌马乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 779,
    "question": "488,653,412,528",
    "answer": "兵强马壮",
    "explain": "兵强马壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 780,
    "question": "474,705,435,412",
    "answer": "伯乐相马",
    "explain": "伯乐相马"
  },
  {
    "level": 781,
    "question": "766,338,766,715",
    "answer": "不卑不亢",
    "explain": "不卑不亢"
  },
  {
    "level": 782,
    "question": "766,95,766,441",
    "answer": "不干不净",
    "explain": "不干不净"
  },
  {
    "level": 783,
    "question": "766,277,766,224",
    "answer": "不管不顾",
    "explain": "不管不顾"
  },
  {
    "level": 784,
    "question": "766,193,766,231",
    "answer": "不慌不忙",
    "explain": "不慌不忙"
  },
  {
    "level": 785,
    "question": "766,296,766,236",
    "answer": "不即不离",
    "explain": "不即不离"
  },
  {
    "level": 786,
    "question": "766,232,766,183",
    "answer": "不骄不躁",
    "explain": "不骄不躁"
  },
  {
    "level": 787,
    "question": "766,720,766,831",
    "answer": "不紧不慢",
    "explain": "不紧不慢"
  },
  {
    "level": 788,
    "question": "766,77,766,202",
    "answer": "不冷不热",
    "explain": "不冷不热"
  },
  {
    "level": 789,
    "question": "32,43,173,696",
    "answer": "聪明绝顶",
    "explain": "聪明绝顶"
  },
  {
    "level": 790,
    "question": "3,218,829,737",
    "answer": "一鼓作气",
    "explain": "一鼓作气"
  },
  {
    "level": 791,
    "question": "5,325,165,757",
    "answer": "三生有幸",
    "explain": "三生有幸"
  },
  {
    "level": 792,
    "question": "177,176,229,676",
    "answer": "日落西山",
    "explain": "日落西山"
  },
  {
    "level": 793,
    "question": "414,23,103,83",
    "answer": "望尘莫及",
    "explain": "望尘莫及"
  },
  {
    "level": 794,
    "question": "768,525,177,182",
    "answer": "福如东海",
    "explain": "福如东海"
  },
  {
    "level": 795,
    "question": "761,92,487,423",
    "answer": "袖手旁观",
    "explain": "袖手旁观"
  },
  {
    "level": 796,
    "question": "101,180,101,799",
    "answer": "冰天雪地",
    "explain": "冰天雪地"
  },
  {
    "level": 797,
    "question": "469,525,469,218",
    "answer": "同甘共苦",
    "explain": "同甘共苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 798,
    "question": "432,458,49,652",
    "answer": "大逆不道",
    "explain": "大逆不道"
  },
  {
    "level": 799,
    "question": "1,531,206,737",
    "answer": "一团和气",
    "explain": "一团和气"
  },
  {
    "level": 800,
    "question": "177,5,255,830",
    "answer": "东山再起",
    "explain": "东山再起"
  },
  {
    "level": 801,
    "question": "65,202,49,585",
    "answer": "心照不宣",
    "explain": "心照不宣"
  },
  {
    "level": 802,
    "question": "3,429,491,799",
    "answer": "一败涂地",
    "explain": "一败涂地"
  },
  {
    "level": 803,
    "question": "831,44,82,524",
    "answer": "行云流水",
    "explain": "行云流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 804,
    "question": "89,49,171,33",
    "answer": "机不可失",
    "explain": "机不可失"
  },
  {
    "level": 805,
    "question": "380,486,344,167",
    "answer": "起死回生",
    "explain": "起死回生"
  },
  {
    "level": 806,
    "question": "7,43,110,714",
    "answer": "五光十色",
    "explain": "五光十色"
  },
  {
    "level": 807,
    "question": "144,160,517,652",
    "answer": "求知心切",
    "explain": "求知心切"
  },
  {
    "level": 808,
    "question": "3,89,777,184",
    "answer": "一飞冲天",
    "explain": "一飞冲天"
  },
  {
    "level": 809,
    "question": "177,336,472,799",
    "answer": "出人头地",
    "explain": "出人头地"
  },
  {
    "level": 810,
    "question": "97,427,160,491",
    "answer": "成人之美",
    "explain": "成人之美"
  },
  {
    "level": 811,
    "question": "736,732,49,468",
    "answer": "忐忑不安",
    "explain": "忐忑不安"
  },
  {
    "level": 812,
    "question": "3,600,476,184",
    "answer": "一扫而空",
    "explain": "一扫而空"
  },
  {
    "level": 813,
    "question": "3,655,432,617",
    "answer": "一网打尽",
    "explain": "一网打尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 814,
    "question": "696,719,524,161",
    "answer": "山穷水尽",
    "explain": "山穷水尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 815,
    "question": "6,248,10,41",
    "answer": "四面八方",
    "explain": "四面八方"
  },
  {
    "level": 816,
    "question": "336,168,165,160",
    "answer": "人各有志",
    "explain": "人各有志"
  },
  {
    "level": 817,
    "question": "64,316,5,49",
    "answer": "梅花三弄",
    "explain": "梅花三弄"
  },
  {
    "level": 818,
    "question": "423,327,92,777",
    "answer": "眼明手快",
    "explain": "眼明手快"
  },
  {
    "level": 819,
    "question": "49,160,429,105",
    "answer": "不耻下问",
    "explain": "不耻下问"
  },
  {
    "level": 820,
    "question": "831,49,342,161",
    "answer": "行不由径",
    "explain": "行不由径"
  },
  {
    "level": 821,
    "question": "336,167,531,753",
    "answer": "人生如梦",
    "explain": "人生如梦"
  },
  {
    "level": 822,
    "question": "432,182,474,495",
    "answer": "大海捞针",
    "explain": "大海捞针"
  },
  {
    "level": 823,
    "question": "7,216,10,819",
    "answer": "五花八门",
    "explain": "五花八门"
  },
  {
    "level": 824,
    "question": "270,159,3,249",
    "answer": "万无一失",
    "explain": "万无一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 825,
    "question": "222,223,394,457",
    "answer": "落叶归根",
    "explain": "落叶归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 826,
    "question": "5,183,428,647",
    "answer": "煽风点火",
    "explain": "煽风点火"
  },
  {
    "level": 827,
    "question": "3,322,534,536",
    "answer": "一刻千金",
    "explain": "一刻千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 828,
    "question": "40,41,384,495",
    "answer": "黑白相间",
    "explain": "黑白相间"
  },
  {
    "level": 829,
    "question": "831,32,251,369",
    "answer": "人中之龙",
    "explain": "人中之龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 830,
    "question": "391,43,750,120",
    "answer": "与日俱下",
    "explain": "与日俱下"
  },
  {
    "level": 831,
    "question": "5,641,424,119",
    "answer": "三十而立",
    "explain": "三十而立"
  },
  {
    "level": 832,
    "question": "280,109,424,589",
    "answer": "平心而论",
    "explain": "平心而论"
  },
  {
    "level": 833,
    "question": "6,533,7,506",
    "answer": "四分五裂",
    "explain": "四分五裂"
  },
  {
    "level": 834,
    "question": "840,65,168,249",
    "answer": "洗心革面",
    "explain": "洗心革面"
  },
  {
    "level": 835,
    "question": "538,346,771,470",
    "answer": "金屋藏娇",
    "explain": "金屋藏娇"
  },
  {
    "level": 836,
    "question": "580,696,525,184",
    "answer": "江山如画",
    "explain": "江山如画"
  },
  {
    "level": 837,
    "question": "47,336,180,202",
    "answer": "雨过天晴",
    "explain": "雨过天晴"
  },
  {
    "level": 838,
    "question": "191,525,799,347",
    "answer": "半路出家",
    "explain": "半路出家"
  },
  {
    "level": 839,
    "question": "465,831,273,77",
    "answer": "人走茶凉",
    "explain": "人走茶凉"
  },
  {
    "level": 840,
    "question": "118,106,113,531",
    "answer": "左思右想",
    "explain": "左思右想"
  },
  {
    "level": 841,
    "question": "3,43,534,236",
    "answer": "一日千里",
    "explain": "一日千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 842,
    "question": "273,777,334,493",
    "answer": "万箭齐发",
    "explain": "万箭齐发"
  },
  {
    "level": 843,
    "question": "503,542,722,280",
    "answer": "爱富嫌贫",
    "explain": "爱富嫌贫"
  },
  {
    "level": 844,
    "question": "248,662,424,734",
    "answer": "面红耳赤",
    "explain": "面红耳赤"
  },
  {
    "level": 845,
    "question": "701,236,716,652",
    "answer": "笑里藏刀",
    "explain": "笑里藏刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 846,
    "question": "533,248,207,526",
    "answer": "满面春风",
    "explain": "满面春风"
  },
  {
    "level": 847,
    "question": "746,701,49,93",
    "answer": "哭笑不得",
    "explain": "哭笑不得"
  },
  {
    "level": 848,
    "question": "49,89,714,489",
    "answer": "眉飞色舞",
    "explain": "眉飞色舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 849,
    "question": "109,280,737,437",
    "answer": "心平气和",
    "explain": "心平气和"
  },
  {
    "level": 850,
    "question": "493,486,740,647",
    "answer": "毛骨悚然",
    "explain": "毛骨悚然"
  },
  {
    "level": 851,
    "question": "49,525,65,714",
    "answer": "不露形色",
    "explain": "不露形色"
  },
  {
    "level": 852,
    "question": "65,49,794,821",
    "answer": "心不在焉",
    "explain": "心不在焉"
  },
  {
    "level": 853,
    "question": "438,5,824,6",
    "answer": "推三阻四",
    "explain": "推三阻四"
  },
  {
    "level": 854,
    "question": "534,380,598,388",
    "answer": "金鸡报晓",
    "explain": "金鸡报晓"
  },
  {
    "level": 855,
    "question": "650,652,647,837",
    "answer": "大刀阔斧",
    "explain": "大刀阔斧"
  },
  {
    "level": 856,
    "question": "722,474,722,460",
    "answer": "傲头傲脑",
    "explain": "傲头傲脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 857,
    "question": "85,374,49,182",
    "answer": "野马无缰",
    "explain": "野马无缰"
  },
  {
    "level": 858,
    "question": "220,474,435,369",
    "answer": "叶公好龙",
    "explain": "叶公好龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 859,
    "question": "3,561,3,423",
    "answer": "一板一眼",
    "explain": "一板一眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 860,
    "question": "3,219,3,207",
    "answer": "一草一木",
    "explain": "一草一木"
  },
  {
    "level": 861,
    "question": "3,305,3,206",
    "answer": "一唱一和",
    "explain": "一唱一和"
  },
  {
    "level": 862,
    "question": "3,177,3,176",
    "answer": "一朝一夕",
    "explain": "一朝一夕"
  },
  {
    "level": 863,
    "question": "3,248,3,239",
    "answer": "一箪一瓢",
    "explain": "一箪一瓢"
  },
  {
    "level": 864,
    "question": "3,524,3,525",
    "answer": "一点一滴",
    "explain": "一点一滴"
  },
  {
    "level": 865,
    "question": "3,316,469,408",
    "answer": "一雕双兔",
    "explain": "一雕双兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 866,
    "question": "3,772,3,767",
    "answer": "一举一动",
    "explain": "一举一动"
  },
  {
    "level": 867,
    "question": "3,374,32,772",
    "answer": "一马当先",
    "explain": "一马当先"
  },
  {
    "level": 868,
    "question": "3,374,33,696",
    "answer": "一马平川",
    "explain": "一马平川"
  },
  {
    "level": 869,
    "question": "3,412,3,374",
    "answer": "一马一鞍",
    "explain": "一马一鞍"
  },
  {
    "level": 870,
    "question": "3,185,3,185",
    "answer": "一模一样",
    "explain": "一模一样"
  },
  {
    "level": 871,
    "question": "3,556,3,55",
    "answer": "一年一度",
    "explain": "一年一度"
  },
  {
    "level": 872,
    "question": "3,364,11,628",
    "answer": "一牛九锁",
    "explain": "一牛九锁"
  },
  {
    "level": 873,
    "question": "3,830,3,696",
    "answer": "一丘一壑",
    "explain": "一丘一壑"
  },
  {
    "level": 874,
    "question": "3,173,3,390",
    "answer": "一瘸一拐",
    "explain": "一瘸一拐"
  },
  {
    "level": 875,
    "question": "3,530,3,342",
    "answer": "一觞一咏",
    "explain": "一觞一咏"
  },
  {
    "level": 876,
    "question": "3,167,3,486",
    "answer": "一生一世",
    "explain": "一生一世"
  },
  {
    "level": 877,
    "question": "3,486,3,426",
    "answer": "一丝一毫",
    "explain": "一丝一毫"
  },
  {
    "level": 878,
    "question": "3,7,3,641",
    "answer": "一五一十",
    "explain": "一五一十"
  },
  {
    "level": 879,
    "question": "3,109,3,505",
    "answer": "一心一意",
    "explain": "一心一意"
  },
  {
    "level": 880,
    "question": "3,426,3,831",
    "answer": "一言一行",
    "explain": "一言一行"
  },
  {
    "level": 881,
    "question": "3,554,3,374",
    "answer": "一张一弛",
    "explain": "一张一弛"
  },
  {
    "level": 882,
    "question": "3,495,3,125",
    "answer": "一针一线",
    "explain": "一针一线"
  },
  {
    "level": 883,
    "question": "443,439,466,466",
    "answer": "衣冠楚楚",
    "explain": "衣冠楚楚"
  },
  {
    "level": 884,
    "question": "445,445,92,423",
    "answer": "依依不舍",
    "explain": "依依不舍"
  },
  {
    "level": 885,
    "question": "445,445,176,92",
    "answer": "依依惜别",
    "explain": "依依惜别"
  },
  {
    "level": 886,
    "question": "3,567,460,460",
    "answer": "仪表堂堂",
    "explain": "仪表堂堂"
  },
  {
    "level": 887,
    "question": "3,343,3,344",
    "answer": "宜室宜家",
    "explain": "宜室宜家"
  },
  {
    "level": 888,
    "question": "105,482,105,486",
    "answer": "疑神疑鬼",
    "explain": "疑神疑鬼"
  },
  {
    "level": 889,
    "question": "3,236,424,360",
    "answer": "以狸饵鼠",
    "explain": "以狸饵鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 890,
    "question": "3,376,428,412",
    "answer": "以鹿为马",
    "explain": "以鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 891,
    "question": "3,493,384,412",
    "answer": "以毛相马",
    "explain": "以毛相马"
  },
  {
    "level": 892,
    "question": "426,426,763,763",
    "answer": "议论纷纷",
    "explain": "议论纷纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 893,
    "question": "3,737,377,377",
    "answer": "意气洋洋",
    "explain": "意气洋洋"
  },
  {
    "level": 894,
    "question": "277,374,773,534",
    "answer": "饮马投钱",
    "explain": "饮马投钱"
  },
  {
    "level": 895,
    "question": "277,374,785,182",
    "answer": "饮马长江",
    "explain": "饮马长江"
  },
  {
    "level": 896,
    "question": "279,279,3,182",
    "answer": "盈盈一水",
    "explain": "盈盈一水"
  },
  {
    "level": 897,
    "question": "457,457,336,336",
    "answer": "营营逐逐",
    "explain": "营营逐逐"
  },
  {
    "level": 898,
    "question": "447,447,336,366",
    "answer": "庸庸碌碌",
    "explain": "庸庸碌碌"
  },
  {
    "level": 899,
    "question": "721,147,721,585",
    "answer": "忧国忧民",
    "explain": "忧国忧民"
  },
  {
    "level": 900,
    "question": "712,109,731,731",
    "answer": "忧心忡忡",
    "explain": "忧心忡忡"
  },
  {
    "level": 901,
    "question": "831,831,336,336",
    "answer": "悠悠忽忽",
    "explain": "悠悠忽忽"
  },
  {
    "level": 902,
    "question": "165,561,165,423",
    "answer": "有板有眼",
    "explain": "有板有眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 903,
    "question": "165,335,165,761",
    "answer": "有胆有识",
    "explain": "有胆有识"
  },
  {
    "level": 904,
    "question": "165,369,165,369",
    "answer": "有棱有角",
    "explain": "有棱有角"
  },
  {
    "level": 905,
    "question": "165,236,165,526",
    "answer": "有利有弊",
    "explain": "有利有弊"
  },
  {
    "level": 906,
    "question": "165,534,165,528",
    "answer": "有钱有势",
    "explain": "有钱有势"
  },
  {
    "level": 907,
    "question": "165,308,165,714",
    "answer": "有声有色",
    "explain": "有声有色"
  },
  {
    "level": 908,
    "question": "165,177,165,32",
    "answer": "有始有终",
    "explain": "有始有终"
  },
  {
    "level": 909,
    "question": "165,426,165,705",
    "answer": "有说有笑",
    "explain": "有说有笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 910,
    "question": "165,579,165,236",
    "answer": "有条有理",
    "explain": "有条有理"
  },
  {
    "level": 911,
    "question": "165,460,165,210",
    "answer": "有头有脸",
    "explain": "有头有脸"
  },
  {
    "level": 912,
    "question": "165,460,165,378",
    "answer": "有头有尾",
    "explain": "有头有尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 913,
    "question": "165,495,165,242",
    "answer": "有血有肉",
    "explain": "有血有肉"
  },
  {
    "level": 914,
    "question": "165,182,165,468",
    "answer": "有勇有谋",
    "explain": "有勇有谋"
  },
  {
    "level": 915,
    "question": "342,662,342,427",
    "answer": "又红又专",
    "explain": "又红又专"
  },
  {
    "level": 916,
    "question": "391,474,181,623",
    "answer": "鱼龙混杂",
    "explain": "鱼龙混杂"
  },
  {
    "level": 917,
    "question": "391,474,831,125",
    "answer": "鱼龙曼羡",
    "explain": "鱼龙曼羡"
  },
  {
    "level": 918,
    "question": "391,489,474,819",
    "answer": "鱼跃龙门",
    "explain": "鱼跃龙门"
  },
  {
    "level": 919,
    "question": "210,210,208,208",
    "answer": "郁郁葱葱",
    "explain": "郁郁葱葱"
  },
  {
    "level": 920,
    "question": "723,723,384,598",
    "answer": "冤冤相报",
    "explain": "冤冤相报"
  },
  {
    "level": 921,
    "question": "655,655,568,568",
    "answer": "原原本本",
    "explain": "原原本本"
  },
  {
    "level": 922,
    "question": "655,655,49,87",
    "answer": "源源不断",
    "explain": "源源不断"
  },
  {
    "level": 923,
    "question": "655,655,49,314",
    "answer": "源源不绝",
    "explain": "源源不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 924,
    "question": "489,489,47,486",
    "answer": "跃跃欲试",
    "explain": "跃跃欲试"
  },
  {
    "level": 925,
    "question": "44,474,534,416",
    "answer": "云龙井蛙",
    "explain": "云龙井蛙"
  },
  {
    "level": 926,
    "question": "44,44,130,322",
    "answer": "芸芸众生",
    "explain": "芸芸众生"
  },
  {
    "level": 927,
    "question": "789,322,789,489",
    "answer": "载歌载舞",
    "explain": "载歌载舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 928,
    "question": "226,799,226,528",
    "answer": "再接再历",
    "explain": "再接再历"
  },
  {
    "level": 929,
    "question": "226,799,226,528",
    "answer": "再接再厉",
    "explain": "再接再厉"
  },
  {
    "level": 930,
    "question": "480,49,417,423",
    "answer": "贼眉鼠眼",
    "explain": "贼眉鼠眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 931,
    "question": "480,49,417,423",
    "answer": "贼眉贼眼",
    "explain": "贼眉贼眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 932,
    "question": "480,460,417,474",
    "answer": "贼头贼脑",
    "explain": "贼头贼脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 933,
    "question": "696,696,460,705",
    "answer": "沾沾自喜",
    "explain": "沾沾自喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 934,
    "question": "125,175,831,831",
    "answer": "长夜漫漫",
    "explain": "长夜漫漫"
  },
  {
    "level": 935,
    "question": "177,468,542,412",
    "answer": "招兵买马",
    "explain": "招兵买马"
  },
  {
    "level": 936,
    "question": "177,409,309,407",
    "answer": "照猫画虎",
    "explain": "照猫画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 937,
    "question": "495,652,495,653",
    "answer": "真刀真枪",
    "explain": "真刀真枪"
  },
  {
    "level": 938,
    "question": "495,109,495,3",
    "answer": "真心真意",
    "explain": "真心真意"
  },
  {
    "level": 939,
    "question": "426,495,165,553",
    "answer": "振振有词",
    "explain": "振振有词"
  },
  {
    "level": 940,
    "question": "426,495,165,561",
    "answer": "振振有辞",
    "explain": "振振有辞"
  },
  {
    "level": 941,
    "question": "432,380,49,377",
    "answer": "争鸡失羊",
    "explain": "争鸡失羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 942,
    "question": "432,432,650,486",
    "answer": "铮铮铁骨",
    "explain": "铮铮铁骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 943,
    "question": "432,432,650,471",
    "answer": "铮铮铁汉",
    "explain": "铮铮铁汉"
  },
  {
    "level": 944,
    "question": "179,179,43,428",
    "answer": "蒸蒸日上",
    "explain": "蒸蒸日上"
  },
  {
    "level": 945,
    "question": "426,426,771,771",
    "answer": "支支吾吾",
    "explain": "支支吾吾"
  },
  {
    "level": 946,
    "question": "772,774,772,775",
    "answer": "知己知彼",
    "explain": "知己知彼"
  },
  {
    "level": 947,
    "question": "111,652,193,474",
    "answer": "直捣黄龙",
    "explain": "直捣黄龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 948,
    "question": "160,380,426,381",
    "answer": "指鸡骂狗",
    "explain": "指鸡骂狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 949,
    "question": "160,376,248,374",
    "answer": "指鹿为马",
    "explain": "指鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 950,
    "question": "160,415,426,381",
    "answer": "指猪骂狗",
    "explain": "指猪骂狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 951,
    "question": "130,407,469,109",
    "answer": "众虎同心",
    "explain": "众虎同心"
  },
  {
    "level": 952,
    "question": "130,423,215,215",
    "answer": "众目睽睽",
    "explain": "众目睽睽"
  },
  {
    "level": 953,
    "question": "415,486,374,737",
    "answer": "蛛丝马迹",
    "explain": "蛛丝马迹"
  },
  {
    "level": 954,
    "question": "446,441,446,337",
    "answer": "装模装样",
    "explain": "装模装样"
  },
  {
    "level": 955,
    "question": "653,480,480,543",
    "answer": "捉贼捉赃",
    "explain": "捉贼捉赃"
  },
  {
    "level": 956,
    "question": "431,431,92,553",
    "answer": "孜孜不倦",
    "explain": "孜孜不倦"
  },
  {
    "level": 957,
    "question": "431,431,49,553",
    "answer": "孜孜无倦",
    "explain": "孜孜无倦"
  },
  {
    "level": 958,
    "question": "431,431,476,476",
    "answer": "子子孙孙",
    "explain": "子子孙孙"
  },
  {
    "level": 959,
    "question": "460,183,460,289",
    "answer": "自暴自弃",
    "explain": "自暴自弃"
  },
  {
    "level": 960,
    "question": "460,327,460,72",
    "answer": "自吹自擂",
    "explain": "自吹自擂"
  },
  {
    "level": 961,
    "question": "460,143,460,457",
    "answer": "自给自足",
    "explain": "自给自足"
  },
  {
    "level": 962,
    "question": "460,67,460,423",
    "answer": "自轻自贱",
    "explain": "自轻自贱"
  },
  {
    "level": 963,
    "question": "460,167,460,486",
    "answer": "自生自灭",
    "explain": "自生自灭"
  },
  {
    "level": 964,
    "question": "460,177,460,176",
    "answer": "自始自终",
    "explain": "自始自终"
  },
  {
    "level": 965,
    "question": "460,249,460,528",
    "answer": "自私自利",
    "explain": "自私自利"
  },
  {
    "level": 966,
    "question": "460,426,460,524",
    "answer": "自言自语",
    "explain": "自言自语"
  },
  {
    "level": 967,
    "question": "460,165,460,799",
    "answer": "自由自在",
    "explain": "自由自在"
  },
  {
    "level": 968,
    "question": "460,742,460,501",
    "answer": "自怨自艾",
    "explain": "自怨自艾"
  },
  {
    "level": 969,
    "question": "460,69,460,831",
    "answer": "自作自受",
    "explain": "自作自受"
  },
  {
    "level": 970,
    "question": "831,412,655,502",
    "answer": "走马观花",
    "explain": "走马观花"
  },
  {
    "level": 971,
    "question": "273,369,772,742",
    "answer": "祖龙之虐",
    "explain": "祖龙之虐"
  },
  {
    "level": 972,
    "question": "499,364,566,566",
    "answer": "钻牛角尖",
    "explain": "钻牛角尖"
  },
  {
    "level": 973,
    "question": "69,580,69,555",
    "answer": "作威作福",
    "explain": "作威作福"
  },
  {
    "level": 974,
    "question": "739,223,739,379",
    "answer": "呆若木鸡",
    "explain": "呆若木鸡"
  },
  {
    "level": 975,
    "question": "739,286,739,471",
    "answer": "呆头呆脑",
    "explain": "呆头呆脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 976,
    "question": "442,442,384,500",
    "answer": "代代相传",
    "explain": "代代相传"
  },
  {
    "level": 977,
    "question": "283,653,526,374",
    "answer": "单枪匹马",
    "explain": "单枪匹马"
  },
  {
    "level": 978,
    "question": "283,701,391,361",
    "answer": "胆小如鼠",
    "explain": "胆小如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 979,
    "question": "715,443,375,375",
    "answer": "得意扬扬",
    "explain": "得意扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 980,
    "question": "715,565,376,376",
    "answer": "得意洋洋",
    "explain": "得意洋洋"
  },
  {
    "level": 981,
    "question": "281,281,49,649",
    "answer": "喋喋不休",
    "explain": "喋喋不休"
  },
  {
    "level": 982,
    "question": "562,97,369,530",
    "answer": "鼎成龙去",
    "explain": "鼎成龙去"
  },
  {
    "level": 983,
    "question": "27,275,431,380",
    "answer": "斗酒只鸡",
    "explain": "斗酒只鸡"
  },
  {
    "level": 984,
    "question": "27,25,373,831",
    "answer": "斗折蛇行",
    "explain": "斗折蛇行"
  },
  {
    "level": 985,
    "question": "491,565,491,831",
    "answer": "独断独行",
    "explain": "独断独行"
  },
  {
    "level": 986,
    "question": "469,363,325,326",
    "answer": "对牛弹琴",
    "explain": "对牛弹琴"
  },
  {
    "level": 987,
    "question": "214,270,214,443",
    "answer": "多才多艺",
    "explain": "多才多艺"
  },
  {
    "level": 988,
    "question": "214,837,363,310",
    "answer": "多如牛毛",
    "explain": "多如牛毛"
  },
  {
    "level": 989,
    "question": "214,270,214,471",
    "answer": "多灾多难",
    "explain": "多灾多难"
  },
  {
    "level": 990,
    "question": "214,426,214,427",
    "answer": "多嘴多舌",
    "explain": "多嘴多舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 991,
    "question": "431,431,133,471",
    "answer": "咄咄逼人",
    "explain": "咄咄逼人"
  },
  {
    "level": 992,
    "question": "485,86,485,598",
    "answer": "恶有恶报",
    "explain": "恶有恶报"
  },
  {
    "level": 993,
    "question": "485,365,837,6",
    "answer": "饿虎扑食",
    "explain": "饿虎扑食"
  },
  {
    "level": 994,
    "question": "501,501,65,65",
    "answer": "恩恩爱爱",
    "explain": "恩恩爱爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 995,
    "question": "93,369,313,382",
    "answer": "二龙戏珠",
    "explain": "二龙戏珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 996,
    "question": "246,246,431,620",
    "answer": "泛泛之交",
    "explain": "泛泛之交"
  },
  {
    "level": 997,
    "question": "66,374,335,376",
    "answer": "放马华阳",
    "explain": "放马华阳"
  },
  {
    "level": 998,
    "question": "89,369,270,184",
    "answer": "飞龙在天",
    "explain": "飞龙在天"
  },
  {
    "level": 999,
    "question": "89,398,831,381",
    "answer": "飞鹰走狗",
    "explain": "飞鹰走狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1000,
    "question": "89,501,89,746",
    "answer": "非亲非故",
    "explain": "非亲非故"
  },
  {
    "level": 1001,
    "question": "89,89,376,376",
    "answer": "沸沸扬扬",
    "explain": "沸沸扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 1002,
    "question": "506,506,611,611",
    "answer": "纷纷扰扰",
    "explain": "纷纷扰扰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1003,
    "question": "506,506,376,376",
    "answer": "纷纷扬扬",
    "explain": "纷纷扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 1004,
    "question": "734,734,92,280",
    "answer": "愤愤不平",
    "explain": "愤愤不平"
  },
  {
    "level": 1005,
    "question": "172,176,90,90",
    "answer": "风尘仆仆",
    "explain": "风尘仆仆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1006,
    "question": "172,367,527,527",
    "answer": "风度翩翩",
    "explain": "风度翩翩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1007,
    "question": "172,172,647,647",
    "answer": "风风火火",
    "explain": "风风火火"
  },
  {
    "level": 1008,
    "question": "172,172,47,47",
    "answer": "风风雨雨",
    "explain": "风风雨雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1009,
    "question": "172,423,172,391",
    "answer": "风言风语",
    "explain": "风言风语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1010,
    "question": "172,47,744,744",
    "answer": "风雨凄凄",
    "explain": "风雨凄凄"
  },
  {
    "level": 1011,
    "question": "462,435,459,459",
    "answer": "服服贴贴",
    "explain": "服服贴贴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1012,
    "question": "462,270,72,72",
    "answer": "负债累累",
    "explain": "负债累累"
  },
  {
    "level": 1013,
    "question": "462,379,431,236",
    "answer": "缚鸡之力",
    "explain": "缚鸡之力"
  },
  {
    "level": 1014,
    "question": "304,69,304,270",
    "answer": "敢作敢当",
    "explain": "敢作敢当"
  },
  {
    "level": 1015,
    "question": "454,454,270,428",
    "answer": "高高在上",
    "explain": "高高在上"
  },
  {
    "level": 1016,
    "question": "168,168,92,815",
    "answer": "格格不入",
    "explain": "格格不入"
  },
  {
    "level": 1017,
    "question": "168,714,168,377",
    "answer": "各色各样",
    "explain": "各色各样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1018,
    "question": "168,6,168,377",
    "answer": "各式各样",
    "explain": "各式各样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1019,
    "question": "745,745,391,26",
    "answer": "耿耿于怀",
    "explain": "耿耿于怀"
  },
  {
    "level": 1020,
    "question": "162,313,26,373",
    "answer": "弓影杯蛇",
    "explain": "弓影杯蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1021,
    "question": "162,6,162,546",
    "answer": "公事公办",
    "explain": "公事公办"
  },
  {
    "level": 1022,
    "question": "381,796,475,361",
    "answer": "狗逮老鼠",
    "explain": "狗逮老鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1023,
    "question": "381,831,418,65",
    "answer": "狗行狼心",
    "explain": "狗行狼心"
  },
  {
    "level": 1024,
    "question": "381,289,459,435",
    "answer": "狗急跳墙",
    "explain": "狗急跳墙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1025,
    "question": "381,526,92,820",
    "answer": "狗屁不通",
    "explain": "狗屁不通"
  },
  {
    "level": 1026,
    "question": "381,776,501,304",
    "answer": "狗续金貂",
    "explain": "狗续金貂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1027,
    "question": "381,101,630,472",
    "answer": "狗血淋头",
    "explain": "狗血淋头"
  },
  {
    "level": 1028,
    "question": "381,305,460,6",
    "answer": "狗仗人势",
    "explain": "狗仗人势"
  },
  {
    "level": 1029,
    "question": "742,714,742,384",
    "answer": "古色古香",
    "explain": "古色古香"
  },
  {
    "level": 1030,
    "question": "479,485,479,375",
    "answer": "怪模怪样",
    "explain": "怪模怪样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1031,
    "question": "37,37,384,409",
    "answer": "官官相护",
    "explain": "官官相护"
  },
  {
    "level": 1032,
    "question": "37,37,384,771",
    "answer": "官官相卫",
    "explain": "官官相卫"
  },
  {
    "level": 1033,
    "question": "481,481,753,753",
    "answer": "鬼鬼祟祟",
    "explain": "鬼鬼祟祟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1034,
    "question": "481,471,481,471",
    "answer": "鬼头鬼脑",
    "explain": "鬼头鬼脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1035,
    "question": "721,369,831,373",
    "answer": "骇龙走蛇",
    "explain": "骇龙走蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1036,
    "question": "721,445,431,374",
    "answer": "害群之马",
    "explain": "害群之马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1037,
    "question": "426,503,336,336",
    "answer": "含情脉脉",
    "explain": "含情脉脉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1038,
    "question": "720,374,162,251",
    "answer": "汗马功劳",
    "explain": "汗马功劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1039,
    "question": "720,374,431,162",
    "answer": "汗马之功",
    "explain": "汗马之功"
  },
  {
    "level": 1040,
    "question": "720,374,731,521",
    "answer": "汗马之劳",
    "explain": "汗马之劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1041,
    "question": "831,760,337,337",
    "answer": "行色匆匆",
    "explain": "行色匆匆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1042,
    "question": "143,437,502,167",
    "answer": "好好先生",
    "explain": "好好先生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1043,
    "question": "143,514,437,443",
    "answer": "好心好意",
    "explain": "好心好意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1044,
    "question": "143,821,437,391",
    "answer": "好言好语",
    "explain": "好言好语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1045,
    "question": "143,437,270,270",
    "answer": "浩浩荡荡",
    "explain": "浩浩荡荡"
  },
  {
    "level": 1046,
    "question": "279,503,776,236",
    "answer": "合情合理",
    "explain": "合情合理"
  },
  {
    "level": 1047,
    "question": "279,530,279,387",
    "answer": "何去何从",
    "explain": "何去何从"
  },
  {
    "level": 1048,
    "question": "279,278,86,193",
    "answer": "赫赫有名",
    "explain": "赫赫有名"
  },
  {
    "level": 1049,
    "question": "278,236,379,445",
    "answer": "鹤立鸡群",
    "explain": "鹤立鸡群"
  },
  {
    "level": 1050,
    "question": "737,737,380,380",
    "answer": "哼哼唧唧",
    "explain": "哼哼唧唧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1051,
    "question": "521,521,506,506",
    "answer": "轰轰烈烈",
    "explain": "轰轰烈烈"
  },
  {
    "level": 1052,
    "question": "378,555,374,555",
    "answer": "猴年马月",
    "explain": "猴年马月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1053,
    "question": "378,413,378,413",
    "answer": "猴头猴脑",
    "explain": "猴头猴脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1054,
    "question": "365,101,365,647",
    "answer": "忽冷忽热",
    "explain": "忽冷忽热"
  },
  {
    "level": 1055,
    "question": "409,344,365,711",
    "answer": "狐假虎威",
    "explain": "狐假虎威"
  },
  {
    "level": 1056,
    "question": "409,85,381,86",
    "answer": "狐朋狗友",
    "explain": "狐朋狗友"
  },
  {
    "level": 1057,
    "question": "409,486,367,289",
    "answer": "狐死兔泣",
    "explain": "狐死兔泣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1058,
    "question": "409,367,431,276",
    "answer": "狐兔之悲",
    "explain": "狐兔之悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1059,
    "question": "409,236,409,491",
    "answer": "糊里糊涂",
    "explain": "糊里糊涂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1060,
    "question": "407,276,419,496",
    "answer": "虎背熊腰",
    "explain": "虎背熊腰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1061,
    "question": "407,527,369,495",
    "answer": "虎变龙蒸",
    "explain": "虎变龙蒸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1062,
    "question": "407,530,369,550",
    "answer": "虎踞龙盘",
    "explain": "虎踞龙盘"
  },
  {
    "level": 1063,
    "question": "407,530,369,550",
    "answer": "虎踞龙蟠",
    "explain": "虎踞龙蟠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1064,
    "question": "407,426,318,702",
    "answer": "虎口拔牙",
    "explain": "虎口拔牙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1065,
    "question": "407,426,237,619",
    "answer": "虎口逃生",
    "explain": "虎口逃生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1066,
    "question": "407,381,160,6",
    "answer": "虎狼之势",
    "explain": "虎狼之势"
  },
  {
    "level": 1067,
    "question": "407,223,276,500",
    "answer": "虎落平川",
    "explain": "虎落平川"
  },
  {
    "level": 1068,
    "question": "407,223,276,215",
    "answer": "虎落平阳",
    "explain": "虎落平阳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1069,
    "question": "407,423,283,283",
    "answer": "虎视眈眈",
    "explain": "虎视眈眈"
  },
  {
    "level": 1070,
    "question": "407,423,283,283",
    "answer": "虎视耽耽",
    "explain": "虎视耽耽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1071,
    "question": "407,407,407,407",
    "answer": "虎头虎脑",
    "explain": "虎头虎脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1072,
    "question": "407,468,373,711",
    "answer": "虎头蛇尾",
    "explain": "虎头蛇尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1073,
    "question": "407,707,172,619",
    "answer": "虎啸风生",
    "explain": "虎啸风生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1074,
    "question": "212,212,776,476",
    "answer": "花花公子",
    "explain": "花花公子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1075,
    "question": "212,212,543,543",
    "answer": "花花绿绿",
    "explain": "花花绿绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1076,
    "question": "212,212,300,499",
    "answer": "花花世界",
    "explain": "花花世界"
  },
  {
    "level": 1077,
    "question": "45,365,436,97",
    "answer": "画虎不成",
    "explain": "画虎不成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1078,
    "question": "45,369,467,423",
    "answer": "画龙点睛",
    "explain": "画龙点睛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1079,
    "question": "45,373,110,494",
    "answer": "画蛇添足",
    "explain": "画蛇添足"
  },
  {
    "level": 1080,
    "question": "416,587,416,586",
    "answer": "患得患失",
    "explain": "患得患失"
  },
  {
    "level": 1081,
    "question": "750,750,543,543",
    "answer": "慌慌张张",
    "explain": "慌慌张张"
  },
  {
    "level": 1082,
    "question": "523,801,652,412",
    "answer": "毁车杀马",
    "explain": "毁车杀马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1083,
    "question": "564,620,564,714",
    "answer": "绘声绘色",
    "explain": "绘声绘色"
  },
  {
    "level": 1084,
    "question": "564,620,564,605",
    "answer": "绘声绘影",
    "explain": "绘声绘影"
  },
  {
    "level": 1085,
    "question": "503,503,97,97",
    "answer": "昏昏沉沉",
    "explain": "昏昏沉沉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1086,
    "question": "503,503,841,522",
    "answer": "昏昏欲睡",
    "explain": "昏昏欲睡"
  },
  {
    "level": 1087,
    "question": "481,481,730,730",
    "answer": "浑浑噩噩",
    "explain": "浑浑噩噩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1088,
    "question": "481,481,730,730",
    "answer": "混混噩噩",
    "explain": "混混噩噩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1089,
    "question": "647,369,647,820",
    "answer": "活龙活现",
    "explain": "活龙活现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1090,
    "question": "647,647,647,647",
    "answer": "火烧火燎",
    "explain": "火烧火燎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1091,
    "question": "379,89,521,91",
    "answer": "鸡飞蛋打",
    "explain": "鸡飞蛋打"
  },
  {
    "level": 1092,
    "question": "379,89,381,558",
    "answer": "鸡飞狗跳",
    "explain": "鸡飞狗跳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1093,
    "question": "379,387,545,546",
    "answer": "鸡毛蒜皮",
    "explain": "鸡毛蒜皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 1094,
    "question": "379,620,381,652",
    "answer": "鸡鸣狗盗",
    "explain": "鸡鸣狗盗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1095,
    "question": "379,620,381,768",
    "answer": "鸡鸣狗吠",
    "explain": "鸡鸣狗吠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1096,
    "question": "379,620,822,283",
    "answer": "鸡鸣戒旦",
    "explain": "鸡鸣戒旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1097,
    "question": "379,620,381,768",
    "answer": "鸡鸣犬吠",
    "explain": "鸡鸣犬吠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1098,
    "question": "379,381,820,182",
    "answer": "鸡犬不留",
    "explain": "鸡犬不留"
  },
  {
    "level": 1099,
    "question": "379,381,820,776",
    "answer": "鸡犬不宁",
    "explain": "鸡犬不宁"
  },
  {
    "level": 1100,
    "question": "379,381,352,427",
    "answer": "鸡犬升天",
    "explain": "鸡犬升天"
  },
  {
    "level": 1101,
    "question": "379,381,605,425",
    "answer": "鸡犬相闻",
    "explain": "鸡犬相闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1102,
    "question": "379,379,171,71",
    "answer": "岌岌可危",
    "explain": "岌岌可危"
  },
  {
    "level": 1103,
    "question": "343,343,344,344",
    "answer": "家家户户",
    "explain": "家家户户"
  },
  {
    "level": 1104,
    "question": "491,458,491,442",
    "answer": "假仁假义",
    "explain": "假仁假义"
  },
  {
    "level": 1105,
    "question": "503,381,431,381",
    "answer": "嫁狗随狗",
    "explain": "嫁狗随狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1106,
    "question": "495,426,378,146",
    "answer": "尖嘴猴腮",
    "explain": "尖嘴猴腮"
  },
  {
    "level": 1107,
    "question": "423,458,423,160",
    "answer": "见仁见智",
    "explain": "见仁见智"
  },
  {
    "level": 1108,
    "question": "181,819,365,476",
    "answer": "将门虎子",
    "explain": "将门虎子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1109,
    "question": "182,90,182,761",
    "answer": "将信将疑",
    "explain": "将信将疑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1110,
    "question": "773,369,323,365",
    "answer": "降龙伏虎",
    "explain": "降龙伏虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1111,
    "question": "566,367,5,703",
    "answer": "狡兔三窟",
    "explain": "狡兔三窟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1112,
    "question": "566,367,5,101",
    "answer": "狡兔三穴",
    "explain": "狡兔三穴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1113,
    "question": "820,713,820,734",
    "answer": "戒骄戒躁",
    "explain": "戒骄戒躁"
  },
  {
    "level": 1114,
    "question": "441,441,545,584",
    "answer": "斤斤计较",
    "explain": "斤斤计较"
  },
  {
    "level": 1115,
    "question": "441,438,441,481",
    "answer": "今生今世",
    "explain": "今生今世"
  },
  {
    "level": 1116,
    "question": "423,323,807,374",
    "answer": "金戈铁马",
    "explain": "金戈铁马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1117,
    "question": "441,379,486,236",
    "answer": "金鸡独立",
    "explain": "金鸡独立"
  },
  {
    "level": 1118,
    "question": "423,423,323,652",
    "answer": "津津乐道",
    "explain": "津津乐道"
  },
  {
    "level": 1119,
    "question": "441,441,165,427",
    "answer": "津津有味",
    "explain": "津津有味"
  },
  {
    "level": 1120,
    "question": "161,482,161,156",
    "answer": "尽善尽美",
    "explain": "尽善尽美"
  },
  {
    "level": 1121,
    "question": "161,109,161,528",
    "answer": "尽心尽力",
    "explain": "尽心尽力"
  },
  {
    "level": 1122,
    "question": "161,161,175,175",
    "answer": "兢兢业业",
    "explain": "兢兢业业"
  },
  {
    "level": 1123,
    "question": "161,161,786,786",
    "answer": "兢兢战战",
    "explain": "兢兢战战"
  },
  {
    "level": 1124,
    "question": "1,1,165,276",
    "answer": "井井有条",
    "explain": "井井有条"
  },
  {
    "level": 1125,
    "question": "1,1,165,644",
    "answer": "井井有序",
    "explain": "井井有序"
  },
  {
    "level": 1126,
    "question": "483,483,165,482",
    "answer": "炯炯有神",
    "explain": "炯炯有神"
  },
  {
    "level": 1127,
    "question": "11,11,394,3",
    "answer": "九九归一",
    "explain": "九九归一"
  },
  {
    "level": 1128,
    "question": "11,363,3,773",
    "answer": "九牛一毫",
    "explain": "九牛一毫"
  },
  {
    "level": 1129,
    "question": "11,363,3,387",
    "answer": "九牛一毛",
    "explain": "九牛一毛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1130,
    "question": "11,476,11,431",
    "answer": "久而久之",
    "explain": "久而久之"
  },
  {
    "level": 1131,
    "question": "652,365,550,369",
    "answer": "踞虎盘龙",
    "explain": "踞虎盘龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1132,
    "question": "652,652,476,530",
    "answer": "侃侃而谈",
    "explain": "侃侃而谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 1133,
    "question": "171,165,171,159",
    "answer": "可有可无",
    "explain": "可有可无"
  },
  {
    "level": 1134,
    "question": "652,328,652,654",
    "answer": "克勤克俭",
    "explain": "克勤克俭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1135,
    "question": "162,162,387,383",
    "answer": "空空如也",
    "explain": "空空如也"
  },
  {
    "level": 1136,
    "question": "426,426,620,620",
    "answer": "口口声声",
    "explain": "口口声声"
  },
  {
    "level": 1137,
    "question": "426,426,232,813",
    "answer": "口口相传",
    "explain": "口口相传"
  },
  {
    "level": 1138,
    "question": "281,374,476,510",
    "answer": "叩马而谏",
    "explain": "叩马而谏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1139,
    "question": "703,703,525,525",
    "answer": "哭哭啼啼",
    "explain": "哭哭啼啼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1140,
    "question": "435,435,339,530",
    "answer": "夸夸其谈",
    "explain": "夸夸其谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 1141,
    "question": "806,374,110,339",
    "answer": "快马加鞭",
    "explain": "快马加鞭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1142,
    "question": "806,374,3,339",
    "answer": "快马一鞭",
    "explain": "快马一鞭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1143,
    "question": "456,456,457,457",
    "answer": "拉拉扯扯",
    "explain": "拉拉扯扯"
  },
  {
    "level": 1144,
    "question": "120,369,119,305",
    "answer": "来龙去脉",
    "explain": "来龙去脉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1145,
    "question": "120,423,449,449",
    "answer": "来势汹汹",
    "explain": "来势汹汹"
  },
  {
    "level": 1146,
    "question": "381,771,365,821",
    "answer": "狼吞虎咽",
    "explain": "狼吞虎咽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1147,
    "question": "381,65,414,540",
    "answer": "狼心狗肺",
    "explain": "狼心狗肺"
  },
  {
    "level": 1148,
    "question": "381,381,534,390",
    "answer": "朗朗乾坤",
    "explain": "朗朗乾坤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1149,
    "question": "474,374,348,298",
    "answer": "老马识途",
    "explain": "老马识途"
  },
  {
    "level": 1150,
    "question": "474,363,348,486",
    "answer": "老牛舐犊",
    "explain": "老牛舐犊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1151,
    "question": "475,475,652,652",
    "answer": "唠唠叨叨",
    "explain": "唠唠叨叨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1152,
    "question": "521,521,525,525",
    "answer": "磊磊落落",
    "explain": "磊磊落落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1153,
    "question": "101,530,101,530",
    "answer": "冷言冷语",
    "explain": "冷言冷语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1154,
    "question": "101,316,101,32",
    "answer": "愣头愣脑",
    "explain": "愣头愣脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1155,
    "question": "236,65,236,148",
    "answer": "离心离德",
    "explain": "离心离德"
  },
  {
    "level": 1156,
    "question": "528,528,171,644",
    "answer": "历历可数",
    "explain": "历历可数"
  },
  {
    "level": 1157,
    "question": "528,528,799,423",
    "answer": "历历在目",
    "explain": "历历在目"
  },
  {
    "level": 1158,
    "question": "205,101,205,412",
    "answer": "厉兵粟马",
    "explain": "厉兵粟马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1159,
    "question": "501,501,166,373",
    "answer": "恋恋不舍",
    "explain": "恋恋不舍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1160,
    "question": "93,365,605,146",
    "answer": "两虎相斗",
    "explain": "两虎相斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1161,
    "question": "93,365,605,495",
    "answer": "两虎相争",
    "explain": "两虎相争"
  },
  {
    "level": 1162,
    "question": "93,92,162,162",
    "answer": "两手空空",
    "explain": "两手空空"
  },
  {
    "level": 1163,
    "question": "93,361,146,101",
    "answer": "两鼠斗穴",
    "explain": "两鼠斗穴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1164,
    "question": "530,530,171,361",
    "answer": "寥寥可数",
    "explain": "寥寥可数"
  },
  {
    "level": 1165,
    "question": "647,43,309,309",
    "answer": "烈日炎炎",
    "explain": "烈日炎炎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1166,
    "question": "2,197,701,412",
    "answer": "临崖勒马",
    "explain": "临崖勒马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1167,
    "question": "2,375,70,566",
    "answer": "羚羊挂角",
    "explain": "羚羊挂角"
  },
  {
    "level": 1168,
    "question": "2,2,98,98",
    "answer": "零零星星",
    "explain": "零零星星"
  },
  {
    "level": 1169,
    "question": "2,2,32,32",
    "answer": "零零总总",
    "explain": "零零总总"
  },
  {
    "level": 1170,
    "question": "369,82,365,273",
    "answer": "龙驰虎骤",
    "explain": "龙驰虎骤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1171,
    "question": "369,89,389,92",
    "answer": "龙飞凤舞",
    "explain": "龙飞凤舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1172,
    "question": "369,89,389,527",
    "answer": "龙飞凤翔",
    "explain": "龙飞凤翔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1173,
    "question": "369,389,97,527",
    "answer": "龙凤呈祥",
    "explain": "龙凤呈祥"
  },
  {
    "level": 1174,
    "question": "410,831,407,457",
    "answer": "龙行虎步",
    "explain": "龙行虎步"
  },
  {
    "level": 1175,
    "question": "410,407,223,44",
    "answer": "龙虎风云",
    "explain": "龙虎风云"
  },
  {
    "level": 1176,
    "question": "410,772,44,417",
    "answer": "龙举云属",
    "explain": "龙举云属"
  },
  {
    "level": 1177,
    "question": "410,345,389,171",
    "answer": "龙楼凤阁",
    "explain": "龙楼凤阁"
  },
  {
    "level": 1178,
    "question": "410,412,423,482",
    "answer": "龙马精神",
    "explain": "龙马精神"
  },
  {
    "level": 1179,
    "question": "410,585,366,426",
    "answer": "龙鸣狮吼",
    "explain": "龙鸣狮吼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1180,
    "question": "410,167,11,431",
    "answer": "龙生九子",
    "explain": "龙生九子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1181,
    "question": "410,743,407,495",
    "answer": "龙潭虎穴",
    "explain": "龙潭虎穴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1182,
    "question": "410,652,366,293",
    "answer": "龙韬豹略",
    "explain": "龙韬豹略"
  },
  {
    "level": 1183,
    "question": "410,744,407,469",
    "answer": "龙腾虎跃",
    "explain": "龙腾虎跃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1184,
    "question": "410,460,373,378",
    "answer": "龙头蛇尾",
    "explain": "龙头蛇尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1185,
    "question": "410,580,398,497",
    "answer": "龙威燕颔",
    "explain": "龙威燕颔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1186,
    "question": "410,389,407,469",
    "answer": "龙翔虎跃",
    "explain": "龙翔虎跃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1187,
    "question": "410,831,44,417",
    "answer": "龙兴云属",
    "explain": "龙兴云属"
  },
  {
    "level": 1188,
    "question": "410,426,389,47",
    "answer": "龙言凤语",
    "explain": "龙言凤语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1189,
    "question": "410,460,407,182",
    "answer": "龙吟虎啸",
    "explain": "龙吟虎啸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1190,
    "question": "410,466,391,182",
    "answer": "龙战鱼骇",
    "explain": "龙战鱼骇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1191,
    "question": "410,572,298,180",
    "answer": "龙章凤彩",
    "explain": "龙章凤彩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1192,
    "question": "410,572,298,154",
    "answer": "龙章凤函",
    "explain": "龙章凤函"
  },
  {
    "level": 1193,
    "question": "410,495,407,432",
    "answer": "龙争虎斗",
    "explain": "龙争虎斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1194,
    "question": "410,248,298,180",
    "answer": "龙姿凤采",
    "explain": "龙姿凤采"
  },
  {
    "level": 1195,
    "question": "376,376,159,711",
    "answer": "碌碌无为",
    "explain": "碌碌无为"
  },
  {
    "level": 1196,
    "question": "222,222,650,66",
    "answer": "落落大方",
    "explain": "落落大方"
  },
  {
    "level": 1197,
    "question": "402,426,374,426",
    "answer": "驴唇马嘴",
    "explain": "驴唇马嘴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1198,
    "question": "402,556,374,197",
    "answer": "驴年马月",
    "explain": "驴年马月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1199,
    "question": "374,92,461,374",
    "answer": "马不解鞍",
    "explain": "马不解鞍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1200,
    "question": "374,95,308,422",
    "answer": "马不停蹄",
    "explain": "马不停蹄"
  },
  {
    "level": 1201,
    "question": "374,218,93,162",
    "answer": "马到成功",
    "explain": "马到成功"
  },
  {
    "level": 1202,
    "question": "374,218,162,93",
    "answer": "马到功成",
    "explain": "马到功成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1203,
    "question": "374,345,462,696",
    "answer": "马放南山",
    "explain": "马放南山"
  },
  {
    "level": 1204,
    "question": "374,538,652,527",
    "answer": "马腹逃鞭",
    "explain": "马腹逃鞭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1205,
    "question": "374,374,407,407",
    "answer": "马马虎虎",
    "explain": "马马虎虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1206,
    "question": "374,119,162,93",
    "answer": "马上功成",
    "explain": "马上功成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1207,
    "question": "374,92,672,653",
    "answer": "马首是瞻",
    "explain": "马首是瞻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1208,
    "question": "374,422,389,497",
    "answer": "马踏飞燕",
    "explain": "马踏飞燕"
  },
  {
    "level": 1209,
    "question": "218,652,542,362",
    "answer": "卖剑买牛",
    "explain": "卖剑买牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1210,
    "question": "231,231,376,376",
    "answer": "忙忙碌碌",
    "explain": "忙忙碌碌"
  },
  {
    "level": 1211,
    "question": "409,360,476,376",
    "answer": "猫鼠同乳",
    "explain": "猫鼠同乳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1212,
    "question": "493,433,493,455",
    "answer": "毛手毛脚",
    "explain": "毛手毛脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1213,
    "question": "92,460,92,460",
    "answer": "没头没脑",
    "explain": "没头没脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1214,
    "question": "49,246,49,423",
    "answer": "没完没了",
    "explain": "没完没了"
  },
  {
    "level": 1215,
    "question": "478,376,478,157",
    "answer": "美轮美奂",
    "explain": "美轮美奂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1216,
    "question": "721,721,49,705",
    "answer": "闷闷不乐",
    "explain": "闷闷不乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1217,
    "question": "522,522,77,77",
    "answer": "懵懵懂懂",
    "explain": "懵懵懂懂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1218,
    "question": "389,389,431,322",
    "answer": "靡靡之音",
    "explain": "靡靡之音"
  },
  {
    "level": 1219,
    "question": "248,248,92,173",
    "answer": "绵绵不绝",
    "explain": "绵绵不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1220,
    "question": "249,249,470,652",
    "answer": "面面俱到",
    "explain": "面面俱到"
  },
  {
    "level": 1221,
    "question": "249,249,384,394",
    "answer": "面面相窥",
    "explain": "面面相窥"
  },
  {
    "level": 1222,
    "question": "94,369,716,298",
    "answer": "描龙绣凤",
    "explain": "描龙绣凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1223,
    "question": "94,92,162,162",
    "answer": "妙手空空",
    "explain": "妙手空空"
  },
  {
    "level": 1224,
    "question": "177,177,73,73",
    "answer": "明明白白",
    "explain": "明明白白"
  },
  {
    "level": 1225,
    "question": "131,652,647,647",
    "answer": "磨刀霍霍",
    "explain": "磨刀霍霍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1226,
    "question": "131,131,49,425",
    "answer": "默默无闻",
    "explain": "默默无闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1227,
    "question": "131,131,49,426",
    "answer": "默默无言",
    "explain": "默默无言"
  },
  {
    "level": 1228,
    "question": "423,380,377,652",
    "answer": "木鸡养到",
    "explain": "木鸡养到"
  },
  {
    "level": 1229,
    "question": "423,460,423,460",
    "answer": "木头木脑",
    "explain": "木头木脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1230,
    "question": "423,179,525,360",
    "answer": "目光如鼠",
    "explain": "目光如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1231,
    "question": "475,425,475,7",
    "answer": "乃文乃武",
    "explain": "乃文乃武"
  },
  {
    "level": 1232,
    "question": "460,527,460,461",
    "answer": "难分难解",
    "explain": "难分难解"
  },
  {
    "level": 1233,
    "question": "460,373,460,527",
    "answer": "难舍难分",
    "explain": "难舍难分"
  },
  {
    "level": 1234,
    "question": "460,734,460,476",
    "answer": "难兄难弟",
    "explain": "难兄难弟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1235,
    "question": "460,460,314,524",
    "answer": "喃喃细语",
    "explain": "喃喃细语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1236,
    "question": "460,460,460,524",
    "answer": "喃喃自语",
    "explain": "喃喃自语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1237,
    "question": "435,470,435,482",
    "answer": "能屈能伸",
    "explain": "能屈能伸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1238,
    "question": "435,425,435,7",
    "answer": "能文能武",
    "explain": "能文能武"
  },
  {
    "level": 1239,
    "question": "556,556,92,545",
    "answer": "念念不忘",
    "explain": "念念不忘"
  },
  {
    "level": 1240,
    "question": "487,487,489,489",
    "answer": "袅袅娜娜",
    "explain": "袅袅娜娜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1241,
    "question": "770,92,770,422",
    "answer": "蹑手蹑脚",
    "explain": "蹑手蹑脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1242,
    "question": "363,652,705,641",
    "answer": "牛刀小试",
    "explain": "牛刀小试"
  },
  {
    "level": 1243,
    "question": "363,650,412,432",
    "answer": "牛高马大",
    "explain": "牛高马大"
  },
  {
    "level": 1244,
    "question": "363,479,373,482",
    "answer": "牛鬼蛇神",
    "explain": "牛鬼蛇神"
  },
  {
    "level": 1245,
    "question": "363,422,641,323",
    "answer": "牛角之歌",
    "explain": "牛角之歌"
  },
  {
    "level": 1246,
    "question": "363,381,431,461",
    "answer": "牛郎织女",
    "explain": "牛郎织女"
  },
  {
    "level": 1247,
    "question": "363,310,314,47",
    "answer": "牛毛细雨",
    "explain": "牛毛细雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1248,
    "question": "363,363,412,249",
    "answer": "牛头马面",
    "explain": "牛头马面"
  },
  {
    "level": 1249,
    "question": "363,443,88,205",
    "answer": "牛衣对泣",
    "explain": "牛衣对泣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1250,
    "question": "734,737,130,130",
    "answer": "怒气冲冲",
    "explain": "怒气冲冲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1251,
    "question": "247,410,647,407",
    "answer": "盘龙卧虎",
    "explain": "盘龙卧虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1252,
    "question": "366,562,461,363",
    "answer": "庖丁解牛",
    "explain": "庖丁解牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1253,
    "question": "366,412,655,502",
    "answer": "跑马观花",
    "explain": "跑马观花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1254,
    "question": "647,410,366,298",
    "answer": "烹龙炮凤",
    "explain": "烹龙炮凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1255,
    "question": "94,412,630,256",
    "answer": "匹马当先",
    "explain": "匹马当先"
  },
  {
    "level": 1256,
    "question": "339,424,339,591",
    "answer": "偏听偏信",
    "explain": "偏听偏信"
  },
  {
    "level": 1257,
    "question": "339,339,474,476",
    "answer": "翩翩公子",
    "explain": "翩翩公子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1258,
    "question": "339,339,147,489",
    "answer": "翩翩起舞",
    "explain": "翩翩起舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1259,
    "question": "339,339,219,556",
    "answer": "翩翩少年",
    "explain": "翩翩少年"
  },
  {
    "level": 1260,
    "question": "223,223,524,482",
    "answer": "飘飘欲仙",
    "explain": "飘飘欲仙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1261,
    "question": "280,829,280,69",
    "answer": "平起平坐",
    "explain": "平起平坐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1262,
    "question": "135,654,135,837",
    "answer": "破罐破摔",
    "explain": "破罐破摔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1263,
    "question": "9,9,10,10",
    "answer": "七七八八",
    "explain": "七七八八"
  },
  {
    "level": 1264,
    "question": "380,380,501,501",
    "answer": "期期艾艾",
    "explain": "期期艾艾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1265,
    "question": "380,439,373,363",
    "answer": "齐王舍牛",
    "explain": "齐王舍牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1266,
    "question": "380,322,410,410",
    "answer": "其乐融融",
    "explain": "其乐融融"
  },
  {
    "level": 1267,
    "question": "829,407,460,120",
    "answer": "骑虎难下",
    "explain": "骑虎难下"
  },
  {
    "level": 1268,
    "question": "737,130,363,460",
    "answer": "气冲牛斗",
    "explain": "气冲牛斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1269,
    "question": "737,812,771,771",
    "answer": "气喘吁吁",
    "explain": "气喘吁吁"
  },
  {
    "level": 1270,
    "question": "737,486,734,734",
    "answer": "气势汹汹",
    "explain": "气势汹汹"
  },
  {
    "level": 1271,
    "question": "737,314,423,423",
    "answer": "气息奄奄",
    "explain": "气息奄奄"
  },
  {
    "level": 1272,
    "question": "538,468,246,412",
    "answer": "千兵万马",
    "explain": "千兵万马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1273,
    "question": "538,445,246,412",
    "answer": "千军万马",
    "explain": "千军万马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1274,
    "question": "538,205,469,489",
    "answer": "千里迢迢",
    "explain": "千里迢迢"
  },
  {
    "level": 1275,
    "question": "538,538,246,246",
    "answer": "千千万万",
    "explain": "千千万万"
  },
  {
    "level": 1276,
    "question": "566,566,445,553",
    "answer": "谦谦君子",
    "explain": "谦谦君子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1277,
    "question": "399,399,486,524",
    "answer": "切切私语",
    "explain": "切切私语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1278,
    "question": "762,762,833,833",
    "answer": "勤勤恳恳",
    "explain": "勤勤恳恳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1279,
    "question": "762,480,762,439",
    "answer": "擒贼擒王",
    "explain": "擒贼擒王"
  },
  {
    "level": 1280,
    "question": "210,239,457,412",
    "answer": "青梅竹马",
    "explain": "青梅竹马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1281,
    "question": "1,92,1,457",
    "answer": "轻手轻脚",
    "explain": "轻手轻脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1282,
    "question": "1,147,1,97",
    "answer": "倾国倾城",
    "explain": "倾国倾城"
  },
  {
    "level": 1283,
    "question": "1,1,134,134",
    "answer": "卿卿我我",
    "explain": "卿卿我我"
  },
  {
    "level": 1284,
    "question": "78,3,249,249",
    "answer": "情意绵绵",
    "explain": "情意绵绵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1285,
    "question": "333,298,714,714",
    "answer": "秋风瑟瑟",
    "explain": "秋风瑟瑟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1286,
    "question": "333,298,821,821",
    "answer": "秋风习习",
    "explain": "秋风习习"
  },
  {
    "level": 1287,
    "question": "333,298,705,705",
    "answer": "秋风萧萧",
    "explain": "秋风萧萧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1288,
    "question": "470,470,705,641",
    "answer": "区区小事",
    "explain": "区区小事"
  },
  {
    "level": 1289,
    "question": "82,109,82,3",
    "answer": "全心全意",
    "explain": "全心全意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1290,
    "question": "391,412,503,415",
    "answer": "犬马恋主",
    "explain": "犬马恋主"
  },
  {
    "level": 1291,
    "question": "391,412,431,205",
    "answer": "犬马之力",
    "explain": "犬马之力"
  },
  {
    "level": 1292,
    "question": "391,412,431,556",
    "answer": "犬马之年",
    "explain": "犬马之年"
  },
  {
    "level": 1293,
    "question": "445,410,7,92",
    "answer": "群龙无首",
    "explain": "群龙无首"
  },
  {
    "level": 1294,
    "question": "460,436,829,829",
    "answer": "人才济济",
    "explain": "人才济济"
  },
  {
    "level": 1295,
    "question": "460,154,412,160",
    "answer": "人喊马嘶",
    "explain": "人喊马嘶"
  },
  {
    "level": 1296,
    "question": "460,120,460,655",
    "answer": "人来人往",
    "explain": "人来人往"
  },
  {
    "level": 1297,
    "question": "460,497,381,376",
    "answer": "人模狗样",
    "explain": "人模狗样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1298,
    "question": "460,460,461,431",
    "answer": "人人皆知",
    "explain": "人人皆知"
  },
  {
    "level": 1299,
    "question": "460,460,827,711",
    "answer": "人人自危",
    "explain": "人人自危"
  },
  {
    "level": 1300,
    "question": "460,696,460,182",
    "answer": "人山人海",
    "explain": "人山人海"
  },
  {
    "level": 1301,
    "question": "460,109,439,439",
    "answer": "人心惶惶",
    "explain": "人心惶惶"
  },
  {
    "level": 1302,
    "question": "460,821,426,426",
    "answer": "人言啧啧",
    "explain": "人言啧啧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1303,
    "question": "460,377,412,246",
    "answer": "人仰马翻",
    "explain": "人仰马翻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1304,
    "question": "460,109,460,207",
    "answer": "仁心仁术",
    "explain": "仁心仁术"
  },
  {
    "level": 1305,
    "question": "460,474,460,73",
    "answer": "任劳任怨",
    "explain": "任劳任怨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1306,
    "question": "43,43,175,178",
    "answer": "日日夜夜",
    "explain": "日日夜夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1307,
    "question": "525,431,525,531",
    "answer": "如痴如梦",
    "explain": "如痴如梦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1308,
    "question": "525,431,525,426",
    "answer": "如痴如醉",
    "explain": "如痴如醉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1309,
    "question": "525,407,108,3",
    "answer": "如虎添翼",
    "explain": "如虎添翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1310,
    "question": "525,647,525,273",
    "answer": "如火如荼",
    "explain": "如火如荼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1311,
    "question": "525,381,641,407",
    "answer": "如狼似虎",
    "explain": "如狼似虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1312,
    "question": "525,205,525,208",
    "answer": "如泣如诉",
    "explain": "如泣如诉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1313,
    "question": "222,829,222,236",
    "answer": "若即若离",
    "explain": "若即若离"
  },
  {
    "level": 1314,
    "question": "222,329,222,256",
    "answer": "若隐若现",
    "explain": "若隐若现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1315,
    "question": "222,165,222,489",
    "answer": "若有若无",
    "explain": "若有若无"
  },
  {
    "level": 1316,
    "question": "183,389,641,412",
    "answer": "塞翁失马",
    "explain": "塞翁失马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1317,
    "question": "183,389,431,412",
    "answer": "塞翁之马",
    "explain": "塞翁之马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1318,
    "question": "5,460,230,407",
    "answer": "三人成虎",
    "explain": "三人成虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1319,
    "question": "5,5,4,4",
    "answer": "三三两两",
    "explain": "三三两两"
  },
  {
    "level": 1320,
    "question": "119,344,431,381",
    "answer": "丧家之狗",
    "explain": "丧家之狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1321,
    "question": "714,714,470,82",
    "answer": "色色俱全",
    "explain": "色色俱全"
  },
  {
    "level": 1322,
    "question": "103,380,326,378",
    "answer": "杀鸡儆猴",
    "explain": "杀鸡儆猴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1323,
    "question": "103,380,470,258",
    "answer": "杀鸡取卵",
    "explain": "杀鸡取卵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1324,
    "question": "696,696,120,160",
    "answer": "姗姗来迟",
    "explain": "姗姗来迟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1325,
    "question": "696,696,120,160",
    "answer": "珊珊来迟",
    "explain": "珊珊来迟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1326,
    "question": "696,641,696,130",
    "answer": "善始善终",
    "explain": "善始善终"
  },
  {
    "level": 1327,
    "question": "696,165,696,366",
    "answer": "善有善报",
    "explain": "善有善报"
  },
  {
    "level": 1328,
    "question": "373,641,1,768",
    "answer": "蛇食鲸吞",
    "explain": "蛇食鲸吞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1329,
    "question": "373,56,109,305",
    "answer": "蛇蝎心肠",
    "explain": "蛇蝎心肠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1330,
    "question": "167,436,3,3",
    "answer": "神采奕奕",
    "explain": "神采奕奕"
  },
  {
    "level": 1331,
    "question": "167,410,87,92",
    "answer": "神龙见首",
    "explain": "神龙见首"
  },
  {
    "level": 1332,
    "question": "167,410,412,491",
    "answer": "神龙马壮",
    "explain": "神龙马壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 1333,
    "question": "482,380,501,501",
    "answer": "生机勃勃",
    "explain": "生机勃勃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1334,
    "question": "482,410,647,407",
    "answer": "生龙活虎",
    "explain": "生龙活虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1335,
    "question": "482,737,501,501",
    "answer": "生气勃勃",
    "explain": "生气勃勃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1336,
    "question": "482,482,49,821",
    "answer": "生生不息",
    "explain": "生生不息"
  },
  {
    "level": 1337,
    "question": "482,482,641,641",
    "answer": "生生世世",
    "explain": "生生世世"
  },
  {
    "level": 1338,
    "question": "482,482,486,486",
    "answer": "生生死死",
    "explain": "生生死死"
  },
  {
    "level": 1339,
    "question": "482,714,381,412",
    "answer": "声色狗马",
    "explain": "声色狗马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1340,
    "question": "482,714,381,412",
    "answer": "声色犬马",
    "explain": "声色犬马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1341,
    "question": "641,772,410,87",
    "answer": "尸居龙见",
    "explain": "尸居龙见"
  },
  {
    "level": 1342,
    "question": "641,812,641,478",
    "answer": "十全十美",
    "explain": "十全十美"
  },
  {
    "level": 1343,
    "question": "641,491,474,412",
    "answer": "识涂老马",
    "explain": "识涂老马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1344,
    "question": "641,109,641,3",
    "answer": "实心实意",
    "explain": "实心实意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1345,
    "question": "641,412,8,279",
    "answer": "食马留肝",
    "explain": "食马留肝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1346,
    "question": "641,377,435,182",
    "answer": "使羊将狼",
    "explain": "使羊将狼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1347,
    "question": "641,641,451,451",
    "answer": "世世代代",
    "explain": "世世代代"
  },
  {
    "level": 1348,
    "question": "641,641,389,389",
    "answer": "是是非非",
    "explain": "是是非非"
  },
  {
    "level": 1349,
    "question": "92,415,451,408",
    "answer": "守株待兔",
    "explain": "守株待兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1350,
    "question": "92,360,4,821",
    "answer": "首鼠两端",
    "explain": "首鼠两端"
  },
  {
    "level": 1351,
    "question": "208,819,208,376",
    "answer": "熟门熟路",
    "explain": "熟门熟路"
  },
  {
    "level": 1352,
    "question": "360,423,380,305",
    "answer": "鼠肚鸡肠",
    "explain": "鼠肚鸡肠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1353,
    "question": "360,360,423,43",
    "answer": "鼠目寸光",
    "explain": "鼠目寸光"
  },
  {
    "level": 1354,
    "question": "360,226,381,652",
    "answer": "鼠窃狗盗",
    "explain": "鼠窃狗盗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1355,
    "question": "207,92,207,753",
    "answer": "束手束脚",
    "explain": "束手束脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1356,
    "question": "576,3,576,4",
    "answer": "数一数二",
    "explain": "数一数二"
  },
  {
    "level": 1357,
    "question": "101,745,101,208",
    "answer": "双栖双宿",
    "explain": "双栖双宿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1358,
    "question": "101,208,101,389",
    "answer": "双宿双飞",
    "explain": "双宿双飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1359,
    "question": "524,641,524,389",
    "answer": "谁是谁非",
    "explain": "谁是谁非"
  },
  {
    "level": 1360,
    "question": "316,433,539,377",
    "answer": "顺手牵羊",
    "explain": "顺手牵羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1361,
    "question": "426,147,227,227",
    "answer": "硕果累累",
    "explain": "硕果累累"
  },
  {
    "level": 1362,
    "question": "6,412,230,434",
    "answer": "司马称好",
    "explain": "司马称好"
  },
  {
    "level": 1363,
    "question": "6,6,525,426",
    "answer": "丝丝入扣",
    "explain": "丝丝入扣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1364,
    "question": "6,6,762,762",
    "answer": "斯斯文文",
    "explain": "斯斯文文"
  },
  {
    "level": 1365,
    "question": "6,412,651,701",
    "answer": "驷马高盖",
    "explain": "驷马高盖"
  },
  {
    "level": 1366,
    "question": "6,412,460,336",
    "answer": "驷马难追",
    "explain": "驷马难追"
  },
  {
    "level": 1367,
    "question": "576,653,576,753",
    "answer": "速战速决",
    "explain": "速战速决"
  },
  {
    "level": 1368,
    "question": "833,672,833,799",
    "answer": "随时随地",
    "explain": "随时随地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1369,
    "question": "628,652,628,567",
    "answer": "所见所闻",
    "explain": "所见所闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1370,
    "question": "628,430,628,428",
    "answer": "所作所为",
    "explain": "所作所为"
  },
  {
    "level": 1371,
    "question": "271,373,439,378",
    "answer": "贪蛇忘尾",
    "explain": "贪蛇忘尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1372,
    "question": "271,407,714,374",
    "answer": "谈虎色变",
    "explain": "谈虎色变"
  },
  {
    "level": 1373,
    "question": "741,741,721,721",
    "answer": "忐忐忑忑",
    "explain": "忐忐忑忑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1374,
    "question": "271,460,271,460",
    "answer": "探头探脑",
    "explain": "探头探脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1375,
    "question": "630,630,110,110",
    "answer": "堂堂正正",
    "explain": "堂堂正正"
  },
  {
    "level": 1376,
    "question": "652,652,49,56",
    "answer": "滔滔不竭",
    "explain": "滔滔不竭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1377,
    "question": "652,652,49,173",
    "answer": "滔滔不绝",
    "explain": "滔滔不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1378,
    "question": "652,431,336,336",
    "answer": "逃之夭夭",
    "explain": "逃之夭夭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1379,
    "question": "652,431,336,336",
    "answer": "桃之夭夭",
    "explain": "桃之夭夭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1380,
    "question": "45,77,45,435",
    "answer": "天兵天将",
    "explain": "天兵天将"
  },
  {
    "level": 1381,
    "question": "45,205,648,648",
    "answer": "天理昭昭",
    "explain": "天理昭昭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1382,
    "question": "45,412,831,162",
    "answer": "天马行空",
    "explain": "天马行空"
  },
  {
    "level": 1383,
    "question": "45,439,39,39",
    "answer": "天网恢恢",
    "explain": "天网恢恢"
  },
  {
    "level": 1384,
    "question": "489,489,661,661",
    "answer": "条条框框",
    "explain": "条条框框"
  },
  {
    "level": 1385,
    "question": "304,407,205,696",
    "answer": "调虎离山",
    "explain": "调虎离山"
  },
  {
    "level": 1386,
    "question": "247,247,562,562",
    "answer": "铁板钉钉",
    "explain": "铁板钉钉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1387,
    "question": "80,80,391,528",
    "answer": "亭亭玉立",
    "explain": "亭亭玉立"
  },
  {
    "level": 1388,
    "question": "77,323,77,737",
    "answer": "同声同气",
    "explain": "同声同气"
  },
  {
    "level": 1389,
    "question": "295,460,295,463",
    "answer": "童男童女",
    "explain": "童男童女"
  },
  {
    "level": 1390,
    "question": "460,460,479,479",
    "answer": "偷偷摸摸",
    "explain": "偷偷摸摸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1391,
    "question": "319,360,380,734",
    "answer": "投鼠忌器",
    "explain": "投鼠忌器"
  },
  {
    "level": 1392,
    "question": "408,167,408,565",
    "answer": "土生土长",
    "explain": "土生土长"
  },
  {
    "level": 1393,
    "question": "408,486,381,183",
    "answer": "兔死狗烹",
    "explain": "兔死狗烹"
  },
  {
    "level": 1394,
    "question": "408,486,368,276",
    "answer": "兔死狐悲",
    "explain": "兔死狐悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1395,
    "question": "837,435,431,339",
    "answer": "脱缰之马",
    "explain": "脱缰之马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1396,
    "question": "248,339,183,44",
    "answer": "万马奔腾",
    "explain": "万马奔腾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1397,
    "question": "486,377,49,474",
    "answer": "亡羊补牢",
    "explain": "亡羊补牢"
  },
  {
    "level": 1398,
    "question": "655,476,230,410",
    "answer": "望子成龙",
    "explain": "望子成龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1399,
    "question": "71,821,71,831",
    "answer": "危言危行",
    "explain": "危言危行"
  },
  {
    "level": 1400,
    "question": "71,298,696,696",
    "answer": "威风凛凛",
    "explain": "威风凛凛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1401,
    "question": "71,407,177,3",
    "answer": "为虎添翼",
    "explain": "为虎添翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1402,
    "question": "71,407,69,92",
    "answer": "为虎作伥",
    "explain": "为虎作伥"
  },
  {
    "level": 1403,
    "question": "71,373,502,457",
    "answer": "为蛇画足",
    "explain": "为蛇画足"
  },
  {
    "level": 1404,
    "question": "71,71,245,245",
    "answer": "唯唯诺诺",
    "explain": "唯唯诺诺"
  },
  {
    "level": 1405,
    "question": "71,27,71,705",
    "answer": "维妙维肖",
    "explain": "维妙维肖"
  },
  {
    "level": 1406,
    "question": "71,433,71,378",
    "answer": "畏首畏尾",
    "explain": "畏首畏尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1407,
    "question": "727,160,77,77",
    "answer": "文质彬彬",
    "explain": "文质彬彬"
  },
  {
    "level": 1408,
    "question": "727,380,737,489",
    "answer": "闻鸡起舞",
    "explain": "闻鸡起舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1409,
    "question": "501,495,501,495",
    "answer": "稳扎稳打",
    "explain": "稳扎稳打"
  },
  {
    "level": 1410,
    "question": "501,101,501,43",
    "answer": "问寒问暖",
    "explain": "问寒问暖"
  },
  {
    "level": 1411,
    "question": "106,543,106,821",
    "answer": "问长问短",
    "explain": "问长问短"
  },
  {
    "level": 1412,
    "question": "344,831,344,207",
    "answer": "我行我素",
    "explain": "我行我素"
  },
  {
    "level": 1413,
    "question": "7,36,412,522",
    "answer": "乌白马角",
    "explain": "乌白马角"
  },
  {
    "level": 1414,
    "question": "7,339,7,380",
    "answer": "无边无际",
    "explain": "无边无际"
  },
  {
    "level": 1415,
    "question": "7,493,7,180",
    "answer": "无法无天",
    "explain": "无法无天"
  },
  {
    "level": 1416,
    "question": "7,387,7,208",
    "answer": "无拘无束",
    "explain": "无拘无束"
  },
  {
    "level": 1417,
    "question": "7,87,7,229",
    "answer": "无牵无挂",
    "explain": "无牵无挂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1418,
    "question": "7,725,7,486",
    "answer": "无亲无故",
    "explain": "无亲无故"
  },
  {
    "level": 1419,
    "question": "7,468,7,3",
    "answer": "无情无义",
    "explain": "无情无义"
  },
  {
    "level": 1420,
    "question": "7,752,7,161",
    "answer": "无穷无尽",
    "explain": "无穷无尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1421,
    "question": "7,322,7,314",
    "answer": "无声无息",
    "explain": "无声无息"
  },
  {
    "level": 1422,
    "question": "7,674,7,171",
    "answer": "无时无刻",
    "explain": "无时无刻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1423,
    "question": "7,628,641,641",
    "answer": "无所事事",
    "explain": "无所事事"
  },
  {
    "level": 1424,
    "question": "7,460,7,378",
    "answer": "无头无尾",
    "explain": "无头无尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1425,
    "question": "7,3,7,651",
    "answer": "无依无靠",
    "explain": "无依无靠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1426,
    "question": "7,329,7,130",
    "answer": "无影无踪",
    "explain": "无影无踪"
  },
  {
    "level": 1427,
    "question": "7,73,7,746",
    "answer": "无缘无故",
    "explain": "无缘无故"
  },
  {
    "level": 1428,
    "question": "7,412,734,641",
    "answer": "五马分尸",
    "explain": "五马分尸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1429,
    "question": "7,650,7,478",
    "answer": "误打误撞",
    "explain": "误打误撞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1430,
    "question": "821,821,384,655",
    "answer": "息息相关",
    "explain": "息息相关"
  },
  {
    "level": 1431,
    "question": "821,821,384,77",
    "answer": "息息相通",
    "explain": "息息相通"
  },
  {
    "level": 1432,
    "question": "821,737,377,377",
    "answer": "喜气洋洋",
    "explain": "喜气洋洋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1433,
    "question": "120,43,43,43",
    "answer": "夏日炎炎",
    "explain": "夏日炎炎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1434,
    "question": "256,322,256,641",
    "answer": "先圣先师",
    "explain": "先圣先师"
  },
  {
    "level": 1435,
    "question": "256,431,256,753",
    "answer": "先知先觉",
    "explain": "先知先觉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1436,
    "question": "256,798,423,412",
    "answer": "鲜车健马",
    "explain": "鲜车健马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1437,
    "question": "384,246,384,230",
    "answer": "相反相成",
    "explain": "相反相成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1438,
    "question": "384,442,384,230",
    "answer": "相辅相成",
    "explain": "相辅相成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1439,
    "question": "384,300,265,265",
    "answer": "相貌堂堂",
    "explain": "相貌堂堂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1440,
    "question": "384,725,384,503",
    "answer": "相亲相爱",
    "explain": "相亲相爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 1441,
    "question": "384,322,384,171",
    "answer": "相生相克",
    "explain": "相生相克"
  },
  {
    "level": 1442,
    "question": "106,525,389,389",
    "answer": "想入非非",
    "explain": "想入非非"
  },
  {
    "level": 1443,
    "question": "384,479,384,377",
    "answer": "像模像样",
    "explain": "像模像样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1444,
    "question": "705,486,380,305",
    "answer": "小肚鸡肠",
    "explain": "小肚鸡肠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1445,
    "question": "705,710,705,558",
    "answer": "小恩小惠",
    "explain": "小恩小惠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1446,
    "question": "705,433,705,422",
    "answer": "小手小脚",
    "explain": "小手小脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1447,
    "question": "705,109,3,3",
    "answer": "小心翼翼",
    "explain": "小心翼翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1448,
    "question": "705,381,412,528",
    "answer": "效犬马力",
    "explain": "效犬马力"
  },
  {
    "level": 1449,
    "question": "579,180,579,476",
    "answer": "谢天谢地",
    "explain": "谢天谢地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1450,
    "question": "109,641,32,32",
    "answer": "心事重重",
    "explain": "心事重重"
  },
  {
    "level": 1451,
    "question": "109,109,384,329",
    "answer": "心心相印",
    "explain": "心心相印"
  },
  {
    "level": 1452,
    "question": "109,378,3,412",
    "answer": "心猿意马",
    "explain": "心猿意马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1453,
    "question": "109,109,384,410",
    "answer": "欣欣向荣",
    "explain": "欣欣向荣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1454,
    "question": "109,641,271,271",
    "answer": "信誓旦旦",
    "explain": "信誓旦旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1455,
    "question": "109,109,45,647",
    "answer": "星星点点",
    "explain": "星星点点"
  },
  {
    "level": 1456,
    "question": "109,109,431,647",
    "answer": "星星之火",
    "explain": "星星之火"
  },
  {
    "level": 1457,
    "question": "109,109,384,314",
    "answer": "惺惺相惜",
    "explain": "惺惺相惜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1458,
    "question": "109,109,69,752",
    "answer": "惺惺作态",
    "explain": "惺惺作态"
  },
  {
    "level": 1459,
    "question": "831,831,714,714",
    "answer": "形形色色",
    "explain": "形形色色"
  },
  {
    "level": 1460,
    "question": "109,431,608,608",
    "answer": "兴致勃勃",
    "explain": "兴致勃勃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1461,
    "question": "649,363,394,412",
    "answer": "休牛归马",
    "explain": "休牛归马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1462,
    "question": "649,407,489,410",
    "answer": "绣虎雕龙",
    "explain": "绣虎雕龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1463,
    "question": "771,771,641,641",
    "answer": "虚虚实实",
    "explain": "虚虚实实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1464,
    "question": "771,771,525,322",
    "answer": "栩栩如生",
    "explain": "栩栩如生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1465,
    "question": "771,771,652,652",
    "answer": "絮絮叨叨",
    "explain": "絮絮叨叨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1466,
    "question": "696,696,707,412",
    "answer": "悬崖勒马",
    "explain": "悬崖勒马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1467,
    "question": "101,213,567,567",
    "answer": "雪花飘飘",
    "explain": "雪花飘飘"
  },
  {
    "level": 1468,
    "question": "77,737,561,561",
    "answer": "血迹斑斑",
    "explain": "血迹斑斑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1469,
    "question": "77,799,746,746",
    "answer": "血债累累",
    "explain": "血债累累"
  },
  {
    "level": 1470,
    "question": "821,821,3,181",
    "answer": "奄奄一息",
    "explain": "奄奄一息"
  },
  {
    "level": 1471,
    "question": "377,377,827,93",
    "answer": "扬扬自得",
    "explain": "扬扬自得"
  },
  {
    "level": 1472,
    "question": "377,222,407,426",
    "answer": "羊落虎口",
    "explain": "羊落虎口"
  },
  {
    "level": 1473,
    "question": "377,8,3,3",
    "answer": "杨柳依依",
    "explain": "杨柳依依"
  },
  {
    "level": 1474,
    "question": "377,377,432,655",
    "answer": "洋洋大观",
    "explain": "洋洋大观"
  },
  {
    "level": 1475,
    "question": "496,496,73,73",
    "answer": "摇摇摆摆",
    "explain": "摇摇摆摆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1476,
    "question": "496,496,47,336",
    "answer": "摇摇欲坠",
    "explain": "摇摇欲坠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1477,
    "question": "496,496,696,256",
    "answer": "遥遥领先",
    "explain": "遥遥领先"
  },
  {
    "level": 1478,
    "question": "496,496,7,380",
    "answer": "遥遥无期",
    "explain": "遥遥无期"
  },
  {
    "level": 1479,
    "question": "496,496,384,88",
    "answer": "遥遥相对",
    "explain": "遥遥相对"
  },
  {
    "level": 1480,
    "question": "496,496,799,655",
    "answer": "遥遥在望",
    "explain": "遥遥在望"
  },
  {
    "level": 1481,
    "question": "766,831,766,570",
    "answer": "不蔓不枝",
    "explain": "不蔓不枝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1482,
    "question": "766,197,766,73",
    "answer": "不明不白",
    "explain": "不明不白"
  },
  {
    "level": 1483,
    "question": "766,316,766,388",
    "answer": "不偏不倚",
    "explain": "不偏不倚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1484,
    "question": "766,289,766,818",
    "answer": "不破不立",
    "explain": "不破不立"
  },
  {
    "level": 1485,
    "question": "766,125,766,584",
    "answer": "不屈不挠",
    "explain": "不屈不挠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1486,
    "question": "766,5,766,6",
    "answer": "不三不四",
    "explain": "不三不四"
  },
  {
    "level": 1487,
    "question": "766,30,766,31",
    "answer": "不上不下",
    "explain": "不上不下"
  },
  {
    "level": 1488,
    "question": "766,305,766,647",
    "answer": "不生不灭",
    "explain": "不生不灭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1489,
    "question": "766,323,766,521",
    "answer": "不声不响",
    "explain": "不声不响"
  },
  {
    "level": 1490,
    "question": "766,423,412,279",
    "answer": "不识马肝",
    "explain": "不识马肝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1491,
    "question": "766,495,766,703",
    "answer": "不痛不痒",
    "explain": "不痛不痒"
  },
  {
    "level": 1492,
    "question": "766,421,766,106",
    "answer": "不闻不问",
    "explain": "不闻不问"
  },
  {
    "level": 1493,
    "question": "766,426,766,47",
    "answer": "不言不语",
    "explain": "不言不语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1494,
    "question": "766,389,766,443",
    "answer": "不折不扣",
    "explain": "不折不扣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1495,
    "question": "766,572,766,204",
    "answer": "不知不觉",
    "explain": "不知不觉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1496,
    "question": "453,453,519,173",
    "answer": "步步登高",
    "explain": "步步登高"
  },
  {
    "level": 1497,
    "question": "453,453,173,777",
    "answer": "步步高升",
    "explain": "步步高升"
  },
  {
    "level": 1498,
    "question": "453,453,580,311",
    "answer": "步步为营",
    "explain": "步步为营"
  },
  {
    "level": 1499,
    "question": "218,218,397,365",
    "answer": "草草了事",
    "explain": "草草了事"
  },
  {
    "level": 1500,
    "question": "97,97,466,391",
    "answer": "绰绰有余",
    "explain": "绰绰有余"
  },
  {
    "level": 1501,
    "question": "177,177,175,175",
    "answer": "朝朝暮暮",
    "explain": "朝朝暮暮"
  },
  {
    "level": 1502,
    "question": "802,301,363,819",
    "answer": "车马填门",
    "explain": "车马填门"
  },
  {
    "level": 1503,
    "question": "801,840,339,369",
    "answer": "车水马龙",
    "explain": "车水马龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 1504,
    "question": "804,413,804,580",
    "answer": "彻头彻尾",
    "explain": "彻头彻尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 1505,
    "question": "230,338,230,295",
    "answer": "成名成家",
    "explain": "成名成家"
  },
  {
    "level": 1506,
    "question": "230,14,230,14",
    "answer": "成双成对",
    "explain": "成双成对"
  },
  {
    "level": 1507,
    "question": "230,193,230,765",
    "answer": "诚惶诚恐",
    "explain": "诚惶诚恐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1508,
    "question": "230,513,230,445",
    "answer": "诚心诚意",
    "explain": "诚心诚意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1509,
    "question": "230,410,469,295",
    "answer": "乘龙快婿",
    "explain": "乘龙快婿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1510,
    "question": "176,176,77,470",
    "answer": "楚楚动人",
    "explain": "楚楚动人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1511,
    "question": "176,176,278,735",
    "answer": "楚楚可怜",
    "explain": "楚楚可怜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1512,
    "question": "176,176,278,470",
    "answer": "楚楚可人",
    "explain": "楚楚可人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1513,
    "question": "292,292,650,650",
    "answer": "吹吹打打",
    "explain": "吹吹打打"
  },
  {
    "level": 1514,
    "question": "650,218,193,373",
    "answer": "打草惊蛇",
    "explain": "打草惊蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1515,
    "question": "650,403,525,381",
    "answer": "打落水狗",
    "explain": "打落水狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1516,
    "question": "650,801,650,489",
    "answer": "大彻大悟",
    "explain": "大彻大悟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1517,
    "question": "650,327,650,72",
    "answer": "大吹大擂",
    "explain": "大吹大擂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1518,
    "question": "650,339,650,338",
    "answer": "大慈大悲",
    "explain": "大慈大悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1519,
    "question": "650,650,780,780",
    "answer": "大大咧咧",
    "explain": "大大咧咧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1520,
    "question": "650,650,403,403",
    "answer": "大大落落",
    "explain": "大大落落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1521,
    "question": "650,501,650,170",
    "answer": "大恩大德",
    "explain": "大恩大德"
  },
  {
    "level": 1522,
    "question": "650,389,650,182",
    "answer": "大风大浪",
    "explain": "大风大浪"
  },
  {
    "level": 1523,
    "question": "650,234,650,235",
    "answer": "大红大绿",
    "explain": "大红大绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1524,
    "question": "650,234,650,227",
    "answer": "大红大紫",
    "explain": "大红大紫"
  },
  {
    "level": 1525,
    "question": "650,380,650,236",
    "answer": "大吉大利",
    "explain": "大吉大利"
  },
  {
    "level": 1526,
    "question": "650,552,650,163",
    "answer": "大开大合",
    "explain": "大开大合"
  },
  {
    "level": 1527,
    "question": "650,189,173,173",
    "answer": "大名鼎鼎",
    "explain": "大名鼎鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1528,
    "question": "650,130,650,375",
    "answer": "大模大样",
    "explain": "大模大样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1529,
    "question": "650,818,650,403",
    "answer": "大起大落",
    "explain": "大起大落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1530,
    "question": "650,460,650,3",
    "answer": "大仁大义",
    "explain": "大仁大义"
  },
  {
    "level": 1531,
    "question": "650,96,650,89",
    "answer": "大是大非",
    "explain": "大是大非"
  },
  {
    "level": 1532,
    "question": "650,433,650,457",
    "answer": "大手大脚",
    "explain": "大手大脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1533,
    "question": "650,496,650,10",
    "answer": "大摇大摆",
    "explain": "大摇大摆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1534,
    "question": "650,111,650,342",
    "answer": "大智大勇",
    "explain": "大智大勇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1535,
    "question": "426,47,159,580",
    "answer": "语言无味",
    "explain": "语言无味"
  },
  {
    "level": 1536,
    "question": "696,202,387,278",
    "answer": "旷日长久",
    "explain": "旷日长久"
  },
  {
    "level": 1537,
    "question": "338,246,310,757",
    "answer": "夸多斗靡",
    "explain": "夸多斗靡"
  },
  {
    "level": 1538,
    "question": "130,409,89,486",
    "answer": "众毛飞骨",
    "explain": "众毛飞骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1539,
    "question": "130,362,394,182",
    "answer": "众流归海",
    "explain": "众流归海"
  },
  {
    "level": 1540,
    "question": "206,202,214,48",
    "answer": "春暖花开",
    "explain": "春暖花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 1541,
    "question": "223,220,394,210",
    "answer": "落叶归根",
    "explain": "落叶归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 1542,
    "question": "524,209,787,337",
    "answer": "水木清华",
    "explain": "水木清华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1543,
    "question": "212,348,197,124",
    "answer": "花好月圆",
    "explain": "花好月圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1544,
    "question": "225,148,237,124",
    "answer": "世外桃源",
    "explain": "世外桃源"
  },
  {
    "level": 1545,
    "question": "526,211,101,197",
    "answer": "风花雪月",
    "explain": "风花雪月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1546,
    "question": "704,47,236,44",
    "answer": "杏雨梨云",
    "explain": "杏雨梨云"
  },
  {
    "level": 1547,
    "question": "124,209,333,391",
    "answer": "缘木求鱼",
    "explain": "缘木求鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1548,
    "question": "506,77,5,466",
    "answer": "岁寒三友",
    "explain": "岁寒三友"
  },
  {
    "level": 1549,
    "question": "631,211,524,197",
    "answer": "镜花水月",
    "explain": "镜花水月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1550,
    "question": "3,220,574,222",
    "answer": "一叶知秋",
    "explain": "一叶知秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1551,
    "question": "218,811,461,316",
    "answer": "草船借箭",
    "explain": "草船借箭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1552,
    "question": "471,708,423,500",
    "answer": "头晕目眩",
    "explain": "头晕目眩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1553,
    "question": "78,242,489,665",
    "answer": "空谷幽兰",
    "explain": "空谷幽兰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1554,
    "question": "218,209,461,101",
    "answer": "草木皆兵",
    "explain": "草木皆兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1555,
    "question": "7,211,384,40",
    "answer": "五花大绑",
    "explain": "五花大绑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1556,
    "question": "277,423,3,366",
    "answer": "可见一斑",
    "explain": "可见一斑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1557,
    "question": "207,384,210,255",
    "answer": "树大根深",
    "explain": "树大根深"
  },
  {
    "level": 1558,
    "question": "655,239,820,278",
    "answer": "望梅止渴",
    "explain": "望梅止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1559,
    "question": "653,208,271,47",
    "answer": "枪林弹雨",
    "explain": "枪林弹雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1560,
    "question": "265,211,3,423",
    "answer": "昙花一现",
    "explain": "昙花一现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1561,
    "question": "453,453,445,211",
    "answer": "步步莲花",
    "explain": "步步莲花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1562,
    "question": "696,211,202,218",
    "answer": "沾花惹草",
    "explain": "沾花惹草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1563,
    "question": "550,210,103,281",
    "answer": "盘根错节",
    "explain": "盘根错节"
  },
  {
    "level": 1564,
    "question": "211,47,181,426",
    "answer": "花言巧语",
    "explain": "花言巧语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1565,
    "question": "281,211,214,776",
    "answer": "借花献佛",
    "explain": "借花献佛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1566,
    "question": "492,384,208,313",
    "answer": "暗香疏影",
    "explain": "暗香疏影"
  },
  {
    "level": 1567,
    "question": "392,207,168,650",
    "answer": "榆木圪垯",
    "explain": "榆木圪垯"
  },
  {
    "level": 1568,
    "question": "211,90,556,337",
    "answer": "花信年华",
    "explain": "花信年华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1569,
    "question": "460,389,218,209",
    "answer": "人非草木",
    "explain": "人非草木"
  },
  {
    "level": 1570,
    "question": "237,211,364,840",
    "answer": "桃花流水",
    "explain": "桃花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1571,
    "question": "211,177,197,176",
    "answer": "花晨月夕",
    "explain": "花晨月夕"
  },
  {
    "level": 1572,
    "question": "423,3,97,812",
    "answer": "木已成舟",
    "explain": "木已成舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1573,
    "question": "753,95,167,211",
    "answer": "梦笔生花",
    "explain": "梦笔生花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1574,
    "question": "443,193,175,831",
    "answer": "衣锦夜行",
    "explain": "衣锦夜行"
  },
  {
    "level": 1575,
    "question": "206,337,222,366",
    "answer": "春华秋实",
    "explain": "春华秋实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1576,
    "question": "223,214,362,840",
    "answer": "落花流水",
    "explain": "落花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1577,
    "question": "206,211,222,366",
    "answer": "春花秋实",
    "explain": "春花秋实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1578,
    "question": "3,221,769,423",
    "answer": "一叶障目",
    "explain": "一叶障目"
  },
  {
    "level": 1579,
    "question": "233,211,159,47",
    "answer": "落花无言",
    "explain": "落花无言"
  },
  {
    "level": 1580,
    "question": "840,362,212,233",
    "answer": "水流花落",
    "explain": "水流花落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1581,
    "question": "3,423,265,337",
    "answer": "一现昙华",
    "explain": "一现昙华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1582,
    "question": "840,362,212,108",
    "answer": "水流花谢",
    "explain": "水流花谢"
  },
  {
    "level": 1583,
    "question": "435,265,3,423",
    "answer": "优昙一现",
    "explain": "优昙一现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1584,
    "question": "820,278,366,239",
    "answer": "止渴思梅",
    "explain": "止渴思梅"
  },
  {
    "level": 1585,
    "question": "426,239,820,278",
    "answer": "说梅止渴",
    "explain": "说梅止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1586,
    "question": "159,210,159,466",
    "answer": "无根无蒂",
    "explain": "无根无蒂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1587,
    "question": "655,443,222,840",
    "answer": "望穿秋水",
    "explain": "望穿秋水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1588,
    "question": "707,840,387,362",
    "answer": "细水长流",
    "explain": "细水长流"
  },
  {
    "level": 1589,
    "question": "221,233,576,222",
    "answer": "叶落知秋",
    "explain": "叶落知秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1590,
    "question": "221,233,394,210",
    "answer": "叶落归根",
    "explain": "叶落归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 1591,
    "question": "206,211,222,197",
    "answer": "春花秋月",
    "explain": "春花秋月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1592,
    "question": "783,207,211,701",
    "answer": "铁树花开",
    "explain": "铁树花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 1593,
    "question": "783,207,701,337",
    "answer": "铁树开华",
    "explain": "铁树开华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1594,
    "question": "783,207,701,214",
    "answer": "铁树开花",
    "explain": "铁树开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1595,
    "question": "646,202,231,214",
    "answer": "明日黄花",
    "explain": "明日黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1596,
    "question": "236,609,237,486",
    "answer": "李代桃僵",
    "explain": "李代桃僵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1597,
    "question": "486,236,609,237",
    "answer": "僵李代桃",
    "explain": "僵李代桃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1598,
    "question": "207,30,701,211",
    "answer": "树上开花",
    "explain": "树上开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1599,
    "question": "237,211,265,840",
    "answer": "桃花潭水",
    "explain": "桃花潭水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1600,
    "question": "202,255,265,840",
    "answer": "情深潭水",
    "explain": "情深潭水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1601,
    "question": "3,237,609,236",
    "answer": "以桃代李",
    "explain": "以桃代李"
  },
  {
    "level": 1602,
    "question": "701,212,281,366",
    "answer": "开花结实",
    "explain": "开花结实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1603,
    "question": "701,211,281,205",
    "answer": "开花结果",
    "explain": "开花结果"
  },
  {
    "level": 1604,
    "question": "468,236,609,237",
    "answer": "将李代桃",
    "explain": "将李代桃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1605,
    "question": "696,202,521,278",
    "answer": "旷日经久",
    "explain": "旷日经久"
  },
  {
    "level": 1606,
    "question": "237,236,206,526",
    "answer": "桃李春风",
    "explain": "桃李春风"
  },
  {
    "level": 1607,
    "question": "197,176,211,177",
    "answer": "月夕花朝",
    "explain": "月夕花朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1608,
    "question": "206,202,211,298",
    "answer": "春暖花香",
    "explain": "春暖花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 1609,
    "question": "576,209,580,554",
    "answer": "本末倒置",
    "explain": "本末倒置"
  },
  {
    "level": 1610,
    "question": "211,257,193,112",
    "answer": "花团锦簇",
    "explain": "花团锦簇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1611,
    "question": "236,214,451,47",
    "answer": "梨花带雨",
    "explain": "梨花带雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1612,
    "question": "3,214,281,209",
    "answer": "移花接木",
    "explain": "移花接木"
  },
  {
    "level": 1613,
    "question": "362,121,211,189",
    "answer": "柳暗花明",
    "explain": "柳暗花明"
  },
  {
    "level": 1614,
    "question": "193,30,295,211",
    "answer": "锦上添花",
    "explain": "锦上添花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1615,
    "question": "298,218,239,471",
    "answer": "香草美人",
    "explain": "香草美人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1616,
    "question": "218,387,388,89",
    "answer": "草长莺飞",
    "explain": "草长莺飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1617,
    "question": "103,227,821,234",
    "answer": "姹紫嫣红",
    "explain": "姹紫嫣红"
  },
  {
    "level": 1618,
    "question": "647,207,288,211",
    "answer": "火树银花",
    "explain": "火树银花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1619,
    "question": "403,288,101,389",
    "answer": "落英缤纷",
    "explain": "落英缤纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 1620,
    "question": "184,415,97,94",
    "answer": "看朱成碧",
    "explain": "看朱成碧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1621,
    "question": "415,237,366,236",
    "answer": "投桃报李",
    "explain": "投桃报李"
  },
  {
    "level": 1622,
    "question": "538,514,94,66",
    "answer": "万紫千红",
    "explain": "万紫千红"
  },
  {
    "level": 1623,
    "question": "211,160,648,212",
    "answer": "花枝招展",
    "explain": "花枝招展"
  },
  {
    "level": 1624,
    "question": "281,218,502,124",
    "answer": "结草衔环",
    "explain": "结草衔环"
  },
  {
    "level": 1625,
    "question": "47,207,2,526",
    "answer": "玉树临风",
    "explain": "玉树临风"
  },
  {
    "level": 1626,
    "question": "458,207,3,818",
    "answer": "独树一帜",
    "explain": "独树一帜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1627,
    "question": "650,214,160,229",
    "answer": "乔迁之喜",
    "explain": "乔迁之喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1628,
    "question": "412,211,3,701",
    "answer": "拈花一笑",
    "explain": "拈花一笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1629,
    "question": "175,461,47,211",
    "answer": "天女散花",
    "explain": "天女散花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1630,
    "question": "218,84,514,47",
    "answer": "孤芳自赏",
    "explain": "孤芳自赏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1631,
    "question": "94,197,489,211",
    "answer": "闭月羞花",
    "explain": "闭月羞花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1632,
    "question": "84,211,486,193",
    "answer": "繁花似锦",
    "explain": "繁花似锦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1633,
    "question": "533,49,207,471",
    "answer": "百年树人",
    "explain": "百年树人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1634,
    "question": "345,347,211,127",
    "answer": "洞房花烛",
    "explain": "洞房花烛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1635,
    "question": "426,47,159,580",
    "answer": "语言无味",
    "explain": "语言无味"
  },
  {
    "level": 1636,
    "question": "696,202,387,278",
    "answer": "旷日长久",
    "explain": "旷日长久"
  },
  {
    "level": 1637,
    "question": "338,246,310,757",
    "answer": "夸多斗靡",
    "explain": "夸多斗靡"
  },
  {
    "level": 1638,
    "question": "130,409,89,486",
    "answer": "众毛飞骨",
    "explain": "众毛飞骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1639,
    "question": "130,362,394,182",
    "answer": "众流归海",
    "explain": "众流归海"
  },
  {
    "level": 1640,
    "question": "206,202,214,48",
    "answer": "春暖花开",
    "explain": "春暖花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 1641,
    "question": "223,220,394,210",
    "answer": "落叶归根",
    "explain": "落叶归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 1642,
    "question": "524,209,787,337",
    "answer": "水木清华",
    "explain": "水木清华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1643,
    "question": "212,348,197,124",
    "answer": "花好月圆",
    "explain": "花好月圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1644,
    "question": "225,148,237,124",
    "answer": "世外桃源",
    "explain": "世外桃源"
  },
  {
    "level": 1645,
    "question": "526,211,101,197",
    "answer": "风花雪月",
    "explain": "风花雪月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1646,
    "question": "704,47,236,44",
    "answer": "杏雨梨云",
    "explain": "杏雨梨云"
  },
  {
    "level": 1647,
    "question": "124,209,333,391",
    "answer": "缘木求鱼",
    "explain": "缘木求鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 1648,
    "question": "506,77,5,466",
    "answer": "岁寒三友",
    "explain": "岁寒三友"
  },
  {
    "level": 1649,
    "question": "631,211,524,197",
    "answer": "镜花水月",
    "explain": "镜花水月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1650,
    "question": "3,220,574,222",
    "answer": "一叶知秋",
    "explain": "一叶知秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1651,
    "question": "218,811,461,316",
    "answer": "草船借箭",
    "explain": "草船借箭"
  },
  {
    "level": 1652,
    "question": "471,708,423,500",
    "answer": "头晕目眩",
    "explain": "头晕目眩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1653,
    "question": "78,242,489,665",
    "answer": "空谷幽兰",
    "explain": "空谷幽兰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1654,
    "question": "218,209,461,101",
    "answer": "草木皆兵",
    "explain": "草木皆兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1655,
    "question": "7,211,384,40",
    "answer": "五花大绑",
    "explain": "五花大绑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1656,
    "question": "277,423,3,366",
    "answer": "可见一斑",
    "explain": "可见一斑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1657,
    "question": "207,384,210,255",
    "answer": "树大根深",
    "explain": "树大根深"
  },
  {
    "level": 1658,
    "question": "655,239,820,278",
    "answer": "望梅止渴",
    "explain": "望梅止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1659,
    "question": "653,208,271,47",
    "answer": "枪林弹雨",
    "explain": "枪林弹雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1660,
    "question": "265,211,3,423",
    "answer": "昙花一现",
    "explain": "昙花一现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1661,
    "question": "453,453,445,211",
    "answer": "步步莲花",
    "explain": "步步莲花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1662,
    "question": "696,211,202,218",
    "answer": "沾花惹草",
    "explain": "沾花惹草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1663,
    "question": "550,210,103,281",
    "answer": "盘根错节",
    "explain": "盘根错节"
  },
  {
    "level": 1664,
    "question": "211,47,181,426",
    "answer": "花言巧语",
    "explain": "花言巧语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1665,
    "question": "281,211,214,776",
    "answer": "借花献佛",
    "explain": "借花献佛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1666,
    "question": "492,384,208,313",
    "answer": "暗香疏影",
    "explain": "暗香疏影"
  },
  {
    "level": 1667,
    "question": "392,207,168,650",
    "answer": "榆木圪垯",
    "explain": "榆木圪垯"
  },
  {
    "level": 1668,
    "question": "211,90,556,337",
    "answer": "花信年华",
    "explain": "花信年华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1669,
    "question": "460,389,218,209",
    "answer": "人非草木",
    "explain": "人非草木"
  },
  {
    "level": 1670,
    "question": "237,211,364,840",
    "answer": "桃花流水",
    "explain": "桃花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1671,
    "question": "211,177,197,176",
    "answer": "花晨月夕",
    "explain": "花晨月夕"
  },
  {
    "level": 1672,
    "question": "423,3,97,812",
    "answer": "木已成舟",
    "explain": "木已成舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 1673,
    "question": "753,95,167,211",
    "answer": "梦笔生花",
    "explain": "梦笔生花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1674,
    "question": "443,193,175,831",
    "answer": "衣锦夜行",
    "explain": "衣锦夜行"
  },
  {
    "level": 1675,
    "question": "206,337,222,366",
    "answer": "春华秋实",
    "explain": "春华秋实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1676,
    "question": "223,214,362,840",
    "answer": "落花流水",
    "explain": "落花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1677,
    "question": "206,211,222,366",
    "answer": "春花秋实",
    "explain": "春花秋实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1678,
    "question": "3,221,769,423",
    "answer": "一叶障目",
    "explain": "一叶障目"
  },
  {
    "level": 1679,
    "question": "233,211,159,47",
    "answer": "落花无言",
    "explain": "落花无言"
  },
  {
    "level": 1680,
    "question": "840,362,212,233",
    "answer": "水流花落",
    "explain": "水流花落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1681,
    "question": "3,423,265,337",
    "answer": "一现昙华",
    "explain": "一现昙华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1682,
    "question": "840,362,212,108",
    "answer": "水流花谢",
    "explain": "水流花谢"
  },
  {
    "level": 1683,
    "question": "435,265,3,423",
    "answer": "优昙一现",
    "explain": "优昙一现"
  },
  {
    "level": 1684,
    "question": "820,278,366,239",
    "answer": "止渴思梅",
    "explain": "止渴思梅"
  },
  {
    "level": 1685,
    "question": "426,239,820,278",
    "answer": "说梅止渴",
    "explain": "说梅止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1686,
    "question": "159,210,159,466",
    "answer": "无根无蒂",
    "explain": "无根无蒂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1687,
    "question": "655,443,222,840",
    "answer": "望穿秋水",
    "explain": "望穿秋水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1688,
    "question": "707,840,387,362",
    "answer": "细水长流",
    "explain": "细水长流"
  },
  {
    "level": 1689,
    "question": "221,233,576,222",
    "answer": "叶落知秋",
    "explain": "叶落知秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1690,
    "question": "221,233,394,210",
    "answer": "叶落归根",
    "explain": "叶落归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 1691,
    "question": "206,211,222,197",
    "answer": "春花秋月",
    "explain": "春花秋月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1692,
    "question": "783,207,211,701",
    "answer": "铁树花开",
    "explain": "铁树花开"
  },
  {
    "level": 1693,
    "question": "783,207,701,337",
    "answer": "铁树开华",
    "explain": "铁树开华"
  },
  {
    "level": 1694,
    "question": "783,207,701,214",
    "answer": "铁树开花",
    "explain": "铁树开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1695,
    "question": "646,202,231,214",
    "answer": "明日黄花",
    "explain": "明日黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1696,
    "question": "236,609,237,486",
    "answer": "李代桃僵",
    "explain": "李代桃僵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1697,
    "question": "486,236,609,237",
    "answer": "僵李代桃",
    "explain": "僵李代桃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1698,
    "question": "207,30,701,211",
    "answer": "树上开花",
    "explain": "树上开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1699,
    "question": "237,211,265,840",
    "answer": "桃花潭水",
    "explain": "桃花潭水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1700,
    "question": "202,255,265,840",
    "answer": "情深潭水",
    "explain": "情深潭水"
  },
  {
    "level": 1701,
    "question": "3,237,609,236",
    "answer": "以桃代李",
    "explain": "以桃代李"
  },
  {
    "level": 1702,
    "question": "701,212,281,366",
    "answer": "开花结实",
    "explain": "开花结实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1703,
    "question": "701,211,281,205",
    "answer": "开花结果",
    "explain": "开花结果"
  },
  {
    "level": 1704,
    "question": "468,236,609,237",
    "answer": "将李代桃",
    "explain": "将李代桃"
  },
  {
    "level": 1705,
    "question": "696,202,521,278",
    "answer": "旷日经久",
    "explain": "旷日经久"
  },
  {
    "level": 1706,
    "question": "237,236,206,526",
    "answer": "桃李春风",
    "explain": "桃李春风"
  },
  {
    "level": 1707,
    "question": "197,176,211,177",
    "answer": "月夕花朝",
    "explain": "月夕花朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1708,
    "question": "206,202,211,298",
    "answer": "春暖花香",
    "explain": "春暖花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 1709,
    "question": "576,209,580,554",
    "answer": "本末倒置",
    "explain": "本末倒置"
  },
  {
    "level": 1710,
    "question": "211,257,193,112",
    "answer": "花团锦簇",
    "explain": "花团锦簇"
  },
  {
    "level": 1711,
    "question": "236,214,451,47",
    "answer": "梨花带雨",
    "explain": "梨花带雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1712,
    "question": "3,214,281,209",
    "answer": "移花接木",
    "explain": "移花接木"
  },
  {
    "level": 1713,
    "question": "362,121,211,189",
    "answer": "柳暗花明",
    "explain": "柳暗花明"
  },
  {
    "level": 1714,
    "question": "193,30,295,211",
    "answer": "锦上添花",
    "explain": "锦上添花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1715,
    "question": "298,218,239,471",
    "answer": "香草美人",
    "explain": "香草美人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1716,
    "question": "218,387,388,89",
    "answer": "草长莺飞",
    "explain": "草长莺飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 1717,
    "question": "103,227,821,234",
    "answer": "姹紫嫣红",
    "explain": "姹紫嫣红"
  },
  {
    "level": 1718,
    "question": "647,207,288,211",
    "answer": "火树银花",
    "explain": "火树银花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1719,
    "question": "403,288,101,389",
    "answer": "落英缤纷",
    "explain": "落英缤纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 1720,
    "question": "184,415,97,94",
    "answer": "看朱成碧",
    "explain": "看朱成碧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1721,
    "question": "415,237,366,236",
    "answer": "投桃报李",
    "explain": "投桃报李"
  },
  {
    "level": 1722,
    "question": "538,514,94,66",
    "answer": "万紫千红",
    "explain": "万紫千红"
  },
  {
    "level": 1723,
    "question": "211,160,648,212",
    "answer": "花枝招展",
    "explain": "花枝招展"
  },
  {
    "level": 1724,
    "question": "281,218,502,124",
    "answer": "结草衔环",
    "explain": "结草衔环"
  },
  {
    "level": 1725,
    "question": "47,207,2,526",
    "answer": "玉树临风",
    "explain": "玉树临风"
  },
  {
    "level": 1726,
    "question": "458,207,3,818",
    "answer": "独树一帜",
    "explain": "独树一帜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1727,
    "question": "650,214,160,229",
    "answer": "乔迁之喜",
    "explain": "乔迁之喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1728,
    "question": "412,211,3,701",
    "answer": "拈花一笑",
    "explain": "拈花一笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1729,
    "question": "175,461,47,211",
    "answer": "天女散花",
    "explain": "天女散花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1730,
    "question": "218,84,514,47",
    "answer": "孤芳自赏",
    "explain": "孤芳自赏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1731,
    "question": "94,197,489,211",
    "answer": "闭月羞花",
    "explain": "闭月羞花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1732,
    "question": "84,211,486,193",
    "answer": "繁花似锦",
    "explain": "繁花似锦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1733,
    "question": "533,49,207,471",
    "answer": "百年树人",
    "explain": "百年树人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1734,
    "question": "345,347,211,127",
    "answer": "洞房花烛",
    "explain": "洞房花烛"
  },
  {
    "level": 1735,
    "question": "398,426,211,298",
    "answer": "鸟语花香",
    "explain": "鸟语花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 1736,
    "question": "521,211,202,218",
    "answer": "拈花惹草",
    "explain": "拈花惹草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1737,
    "question": "7,211,10,819",
    "answer": "五花八门",
    "explain": "五花八门"
  },
  {
    "level": 1738,
    "question": "650,47,2,373",
    "answer": "巧言令色",
    "explain": "巧言令色"
  },
  {
    "level": 1739,
    "question": "533,211,818,246",
    "answer": "百花齐放",
    "explain": "百花齐放"
  },
  {
    "level": 1740,
    "question": "263,427,364,513",
    "answer": "巧舌如簧",
    "explain": "巧舌如簧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1741,
    "question": "818,381,47,207",
    "answer": "芝兰玉树",
    "explain": "芝兰玉树"
  },
  {
    "level": 1742,
    "question": "211,175,275,476",
    "answer": "花天酒地",
    "explain": "花天酒地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1743,
    "question": "464,211,206,392",
    "answer": "杏花春雨",
    "explain": "杏花春雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1744,
    "question": "211,110,818,445",
    "answer": "花甲之年",
    "explain": "花甲之年"
  },
  {
    "level": 1745,
    "question": "94,193,6,218",
    "answer": "千金市骨",
    "explain": "千金市骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1746,
    "question": "281,294,4,818",
    "answer": "揭竿而起",
    "explain": "揭竿而起"
  },
  {
    "level": 1747,
    "question": "218,193,471,248",
    "answer": "草菅人命",
    "explain": "草菅人命"
  },
  {
    "level": 1748,
    "question": "210,89,66,394",
    "answer": "绿肥红瘦",
    "explain": "绿肥红瘦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1749,
    "question": "228,233,476,403",
    "answer": "瓜熟蒂落",
    "explain": "瓜熟蒂落"
  },
  {
    "level": 1750,
    "question": "7,72,641,180",
    "answer": "五光十色",
    "explain": "五光十色"
  },
  {
    "level": 1751,
    "question": "409,2,841,292",
    "answer": "茂林修竹",
    "explain": "茂林修竹"
  },
  {
    "level": 1752,
    "question": "337,4,103,366",
    "answer": "华而不实",
    "explain": "华而不实"
  },
  {
    "level": 1753,
    "question": "4,221,654,423",
    "answer": "两叶掩目",
    "explain": "两叶掩目"
  },
  {
    "level": 1754,
    "question": "491,5,412,309",
    "answer": "指桑骂槐",
    "explain": "指桑骂槐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1755,
    "question": "175,211,182,426",
    "answer": "天花乱坠",
    "explain": "天花乱坠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1756,
    "question": "415,178,423,211",
    "answer": "头晕眼花",
    "explain": "头晕眼花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1757,
    "question": "497,218,206,122",
    "answer": "寸草春晖",
    "explain": "寸草春晖"
  },
  {
    "level": 1758,
    "question": "495,818,251,821",
    "answer": "争奇斗艳",
    "explain": "争奇斗艳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1759,
    "question": "7,821,8,714",
    "answer": "五颜六色",
    "explain": "五颜六色"
  },
  {
    "level": 1760,
    "question": "305,218,173,109",
    "answer": "革故鼎新",
    "explain": "革故鼎新"
  },
  {
    "level": 1761,
    "question": "338,337,111,394",
    "answer": "荣华富贵",
    "explain": "荣华富贵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1762,
    "question": "480,211,6,47",
    "answer": "如花似玉",
    "explain": "如花似玉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1763,
    "question": "211,538,197,31",
    "answer": "花前月下",
    "explain": "花前月下"
  },
  {
    "level": 1764,
    "question": "495,6,7,94",
    "answer": "徇私舞弊",
    "explain": "徇私舞弊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1765,
    "question": "109,211,423,246",
    "answer": "心花怒放",
    "explain": "心花怒放"
  },
  {
    "level": 1766,
    "question": "746,209,389,206",
    "answer": "枯木逢春",
    "explain": "枯木逢春"
  },
  {
    "level": 1767,
    "question": "818,211,3,218",
    "answer": "奇花异草",
    "explain": "奇花异草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1768,
    "question": "412,211,580,50",
    "answer": "拈花微笑",
    "explain": "拈花微笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1769,
    "question": "533,211,495,423",
    "answer": "百花争妍",
    "explain": "百花争妍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1770,
    "question": "211,449,450,246",
    "answer": "含苞待放",
    "explain": "含苞待放"
  },
  {
    "level": 1771,
    "question": "456,506,651,452",
    "answer": "踏破铁鞋",
    "explain": "踏破铁鞋"
  },
  {
    "level": 1772,
    "question": "218,369,292,717",
    "answer": "故弄玄虚",
    "explain": "故弄玄虚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1773,
    "question": "197,175,211,177",
    "answer": "月夜花朝",
    "explain": "月夜花朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1774,
    "question": "746,554,533,221",
    "answer": "枯枝败叶",
    "explain": "枯枝败叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 1775,
    "question": "207,384,648,526",
    "answer": "树大招风",
    "explain": "树大招风"
  },
  {
    "level": 1776,
    "question": "218,412,323,420",
    "answer": "草莽英雄",
    "explain": "草莽英雄"
  },
  {
    "level": 1777,
    "question": "389,111,170,180",
    "answer": "丰富多彩",
    "explain": "丰富多彩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1778,
    "question": "237,9,8,323",
    "answer": "桃蹊柳曲",
    "explain": "桃蹊柳曲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1779,
    "question": "180,211,533,8",
    "answer": "残花败柳",
    "explain": "残花败柳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1780,
    "question": "8,211,524,8",
    "answer": "傍花随柳",
    "explain": "傍花随柳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1781,
    "question": "3,554,94,193",
    "answer": "一掷千金",
    "explain": "一掷千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 1782,
    "question": "112,514,384,221",
    "answer": "粗枝大叶",
    "explain": "粗枝大叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 1783,
    "question": "206,207,423,44",
    "answer": "春树暮云",
    "explain": "春树暮云"
  },
  {
    "level": 1784,
    "question": "533,211,495,821",
    "answer": "百花争艳",
    "explain": "百花争艳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1785,
    "question": "218,209,208,175",
    "answer": "古木参天",
    "explain": "古木参天"
  },
  {
    "level": 1786,
    "question": "424,409,384,101",
    "answer": "鹅毛大雪",
    "explain": "鹅毛大雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 1787,
    "question": "524,451,47,246",
    "answer": "含苞欲放",
    "explain": "含苞欲放"
  },
  {
    "level": 1788,
    "question": "526,211,101,175",
    "answer": "风花雪夜",
    "explain": "风花雪夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1789,
    "question": "526,327,218,73",
    "answer": "风吹草动",
    "explain": "风吹草动"
  },
  {
    "level": 1790,
    "question": "394,554,223,384",
    "answer": "桂子飘香",
    "explain": "桂子飘香"
  },
  {
    "level": 1791,
    "question": "391,209,168,650",
    "answer": "榆木疙瘩",
    "explain": "榆木疙瘩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1792,
    "question": "831,412,655,502",
    "answer": "走马看花",
    "explain": "走马看花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1793,
    "question": "480,211,641,193",
    "answer": "如花似锦",
    "explain": "如花似锦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1794,
    "question": "237,234,8,235",
    "answer": "桃红柳绿",
    "explain": "桃红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1795,
    "question": "460,470,423,292",
    "answer": "头昏目眩",
    "explain": "头昏目眩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1796,
    "question": "384,207,468,445",
    "answer": "大树将军",
    "explain": "大树将军"
  },
  {
    "level": 1797,
    "question": "193,373,815,218",
    "answer": "惊蛇入草",
    "explain": "惊蛇入草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1798,
    "question": "3,218,446,207",
    "answer": "依草附木",
    "explain": "依草附木"
  },
  {
    "level": 1799,
    "question": "369,771,69,344",
    "answer": "弄虚作假",
    "explain": "弄虚作假"
  },
  {
    "level": 1800,
    "question": "486,397,387,821",
    "answer": "故伎重演",
    "explain": "故伎重演"
  },
  {
    "level": 1801,
    "question": "649,211,495,460",
    "answer": "绣花枕头",
    "explain": "绣花枕头"
  },
  {
    "level": 1802,
    "question": "211,234,8,235",
    "answer": "花红柳绿",
    "explain": "花红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1803,
    "question": "734,211,462,8",
    "answer": "分花拂柳",
    "explain": "分花拂柳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1804,
    "question": "460,470,423,211",
    "answer": "头昏眼花",
    "explain": "头昏眼花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1805,
    "question": "441,170,649,222",
    "answer": "进德修业",
    "explain": "进德修业"
  },
  {
    "level": 1806,
    "question": "652,218,112,454",
    "answer": "斩草除根",
    "explain": "斩草除根"
  },
  {
    "level": 1807,
    "question": "108,344,366,207",
    "answer": "谢家宝树",
    "explain": "谢家宝树"
  },
  {
    "level": 1808,
    "question": "111,211,182,212",
    "answer": "浮花浪蕊",
    "explain": "浮花浪蕊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1809,
    "question": "237,236,495,821",
    "answer": "桃李争妍",
    "explain": "桃李争妍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1810,
    "question": "818,211,496,218",
    "answer": "琪花瑶草",
    "explain": "琪花瑶草"
  },
  {
    "level": 1811,
    "question": "207,571,840,655",
    "answer": "木本水源",
    "explain": "木本水源"
  },
  {
    "level": 1812,
    "question": "167,211,409,94",
    "answer": "生花妙笔",
    "explain": "生花妙笔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1813,
    "question": "206,381,222,772",
    "answer": "春兰秋菊",
    "explain": "春兰秋菊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1814,
    "question": "175,431,110,221",
    "answer": "添枝加叶",
    "explain": "添枝加叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 1815,
    "question": "538,193,3,705",
    "answer": "千金一笑",
    "explain": "千金一笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1816,
    "question": "3,397,239,211",
    "answer": "驿寄梅花",
    "explain": "驿寄梅花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1817,
    "question": "391,207,776,431",
    "answer": "玉树琼枝",
    "explain": "玉树琼枝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1818,
    "question": "423,218,766,167",
    "answer": "寸草不生",
    "explain": "寸草不生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1819,
    "question": "5,391,175,441",
    "answer": "桑榆暮景",
    "explain": "桑榆暮景"
  },
  {
    "level": 1820,
    "question": "339,799,701,211",
    "answer": "遍地开花",
    "explain": "遍地开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1821,
    "question": "211,112,193,435",
    "answer": "花簇锦攒",
    "explain": "花簇锦攒"
  },
  {
    "level": 1822,
    "question": "211,236,365,650",
    "answer": "花里胡哨",
    "explain": "花里胡哨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1823,
    "question": "276,342,276,112",
    "answer": "悖入悖出",
    "explain": "悖入悖出"
  },
  {
    "level": 1824,
    "question": "496,237,369,236",
    "answer": "夭桃秾李",
    "explain": "夭桃秾李"
  },
  {
    "level": 1825,
    "question": "111,411,411,278",
    "answer": "负荆请罪",
    "explain": "负荆请罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 1826,
    "question": "423,45,101,476",
    "answer": "惊天动地",
    "explain": "惊天动地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1827,
    "question": "3,737,279,230",
    "answer": "一气呵成",
    "explain": "一气呵成"
  },
  {
    "level": 1828,
    "question": "11,476,11,554",
    "answer": "久而久之",
    "explain": "久而久之"
  },
  {
    "level": 1829,
    "question": "763,554,525,486",
    "answer": "恨之入骨",
    "explain": "恨之入骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1830,
    "question": "213,230,222,555",
    "answer": "华星秋月",
    "explain": "华星秋月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1831,
    "question": "579,821,476,594",
    "answer": "不言而信",
    "explain": "不言而信"
  },
  {
    "level": 1832,
    "question": "336,163,236,523",
    "answer": "外合里差",
    "explain": "外合里差"
  },
  {
    "level": 1833,
    "question": "87,442,399,278",
    "answer": "惭凫企鹤",
    "explain": "惭凫企鹤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1834,
    "question": "82,831,82,394",
    "answer": "全受全归",
    "explain": "全受全归"
  },
  {
    "level": 1835,
    "question": "391,842,476,525",
    "answer": "鱼贯而入",
    "explain": "鱼贯而入"
  },
  {
    "level": 1836,
    "question": "322,162,591,186",
    "answer": "歌功颂德",
    "explain": "歌功颂德"
  },
  {
    "level": 1837,
    "question": "486,411,7,501",
    "answer": "古井无波",
    "explain": "古井无波"
  },
  {
    "level": 1838,
    "question": "650,176,562,562",
    "answer": "大名鼎鼎",
    "explain": "大名鼎鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1839,
    "question": "478,460,431,423",
    "answer": "美人迟暮",
    "explain": "美人迟暮"
  },
  {
    "level": 1840,
    "question": "431,109,366,147",
    "answer": "赤心报国",
    "explain": "赤心报国"
  },
  {
    "level": 1841,
    "question": "460,7,171,460",
    "answer": "忍无可忍",
    "explain": "忍无可忍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1842,
    "question": "650,346,650,120",
    "answer": "高楼大厦",
    "explain": "高楼大厦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1843,
    "question": "5,387,6,186",
    "answer": "三从四德",
    "explain": "三从四德"
  },
  {
    "level": 1844,
    "question": "7,245,480,647",
    "answer": "五内如焚",
    "explain": "五内如焚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1845,
    "question": "533,786,533,482",
    "answer": "百战百胜",
    "explain": "百战百胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1846,
    "question": "176,496,647,130",
    "answer": "造谣惑众",
    "explain": "造谣惑众"
  },
  {
    "level": 1847,
    "question": "7,752,7,161",
    "answer": "无穷无尽",
    "explain": "无穷无尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1848,
    "question": "377,210,380,294",
    "answer": "扬清激浊",
    "explain": "扬清激浊"
  },
  {
    "level": 1849,
    "question": "213,410,555,407",
    "answer": "花容月貌",
    "explain": "花容月貌"
  },
  {
    "level": 1850,
    "question": "460,116,111,130",
    "answer": "忍辱负重",
    "explain": "忍辱负重"
  },
  {
    "level": 1851,
    "question": "641,247,162,97",
    "answer": "事半功倍",
    "explain": "事半功倍"
  },
  {
    "level": 1852,
    "question": "408,819,776,426",
    "answer": "免开尊口",
    "explain": "免开尊口"
  },
  {
    "level": 1853,
    "question": "94,445,273,412",
    "answer": "千军万马",
    "explain": "千军万马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1854,
    "question": "49,45,438,476",
    "answer": "铺天盖地",
    "explain": "铺天盖地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1855,
    "question": "182,280,480,441",
    "answer": "水平如镜",
    "explain": "水平如镜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1856,
    "question": "176,801,336,167",
    "answer": "明哲保身",
    "explain": "明哲保身"
  },
  {
    "level": 1857,
    "question": "237,205,579,821",
    "answer": "桃李不言",
    "explain": "桃李不言"
  },
  {
    "level": 1858,
    "question": "460,249,237,213",
    "answer": "人面桃花",
    "explain": "人面桃花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1859,
    "question": "555,377,165,460",
    "answer": "俯仰由人",
    "explain": "俯仰由人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1860,
    "question": "696,7,161,165",
    "answer": "绝无仅有",
    "explain": "绝无仅有"
  },
  {
    "level": 1861,
    "question": "323,369,389,395",
    "answer": "伏龙凤雏",
    "explain": "伏龙凤雏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1862,
    "question": "278,493,298,423",
    "answer": "鹤发童颜",
    "explain": "鹤发童颜"
  },
  {
    "level": 1863,
    "question": "650,167,7,165",
    "answer": "高枕无忧",
    "explain": "高枕无忧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1864,
    "question": "441,441,545,650",
    "answer": "斤斤计较",
    "explain": "斤斤计较"
  },
  {
    "level": 1865,
    "question": "525,207,5,734",
    "answer": "入木三分",
    "explain": "入木三分"
  },
  {
    "level": 1866,
    "question": "125,45,650,458",
    "answer": "泼天大祸",
    "explain": "泼天大祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 1867,
    "question": "280,3,161,460",
    "answer": "平易近人",
    "explain": "平易近人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1868,
    "question": "176,368,641,3",
    "answer": "名贸实易",
    "explain": "名贸实易"
  },
  {
    "level": 1869,
    "question": "213,80,8,99",
    "answer": "花红柳绿",
    "explain": "花红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 1870,
    "question": "69,7,771,277",
    "answer": "座无虚席",
    "explain": "座无虚席"
  },
  {
    "level": 1871,
    "question": "734,423,476,423",
    "answer": "怒目而视",
    "explain": "怒目而视"
  },
  {
    "level": 1872,
    "question": "479,579,799,130",
    "answer": "摩肩接踵",
    "explain": "摩肩接踵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1873,
    "question": "389,176,389,35",
    "answer": "若明若暗",
    "explain": "若明若暗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1874,
    "question": "367,486,368,276",
    "answer": "兔死狐悲",
    "explain": "兔死狐悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1875,
    "question": "109,130,165,207",
    "answer": "心中有数",
    "explain": "心中有数"
  },
  {
    "level": 1876,
    "question": "147,423,579,655",
    "answer": "过目不忘",
    "explain": "过目不忘"
  },
  {
    "level": 1877,
    "question": "384,162,480,821",
    "answer": "囊空如洗",
    "explain": "囊空如洗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1878,
    "question": "478,767,69,375",
    "answer": "装模作样",
    "explain": "装模作样"
  },
  {
    "level": 1879,
    "question": "165,165,579,696",
    "answer": "犹豫不决",
    "explain": "犹豫不决"
  },
  {
    "level": 1880,
    "question": "3,245,94,423",
    "answer": "一诺千金",
    "explain": "一诺千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 1881,
    "question": "460,704,431,442",
    "answer": "头梢自领",
    "explain": "头梢自领"
  },
  {
    "level": 1882,
    "question": "426,205,170,499",
    "answer": "探骊得珠",
    "explain": "探骊得珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1883,
    "question": "555,7,438,431",
    "answer": "福无双至",
    "explain": "福无双至"
  },
  {
    "level": 1884,
    "question": "45,7,4,43",
    "answer": "天无二日",
    "explain": "天无二日"
  },
  {
    "level": 1885,
    "question": "423,399,314,171",
    "answer": "精雕细刻",
    "explain": "精雕细刻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1886,
    "question": "167,275,8,110",
    "answer": "身怀六甲",
    "explain": "身怀六甲"
  },
  {
    "level": 1887,
    "question": "555,480,101,182",
    "answer": "福如东海",
    "explain": "福如东海"
  },
  {
    "level": 1888,
    "question": "47,310,580,223",
    "answer": "羽毛未丰",
    "explain": "羽毛未丰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1889,
    "question": "94,831,273,746",
    "answer": "千辛万苦",
    "explain": "千辛万苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 1890,
    "question": "109,378,3,412",
    "answer": "心猿意马",
    "explain": "心猿意马"
  },
  {
    "level": 1891,
    "question": "580,67,482,7",
    "answer": "慰情胜无",
    "explain": "慰情胜无"
  },
  {
    "level": 1892,
    "question": "777,367,746,381",
    "answer": "见兔顾犬",
    "explain": "见兔顾犬"
  },
  {
    "level": 1893,
    "question": "641,77,456,555",
    "answer": "十冬腊月",
    "explain": "十冬腊月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1894,
    "question": "45,584,476,104",
    "answer": "天寒地冻",
    "explain": "天寒地冻"
  },
  {
    "level": 1895,
    "question": "696,116,298,167",
    "answer": "绝处逢生",
    "explain": "绝处逢生"
  },
  {
    "level": 1896,
    "question": "640,554,3,111",
    "answer": "持之以恒",
    "explain": "持之以恒"
  },
  {
    "level": 1897,
    "question": "734,501,163,380",
    "answer": "分进合击",
    "explain": "分进合击"
  },
  {
    "level": 1898,
    "question": "304,387,304,478",
    "answer": "共从共荣",
    "explain": "共从共荣"
  },
  {
    "level": 1899,
    "question": "283,650,109,705",
    "answer": "胆大心小",
    "explain": "胆大心小"
  },
  {
    "level": 1900,
    "question": "786,45,146,476",
    "answer": "战天斗地",
    "explain": "战天斗地"
  },
  {
    "level": 1901,
    "question": "103,3,326,533",
    "answer": "杀一儆百",
    "explain": "杀一儆百"
  },
  {
    "level": 1902,
    "question": "431,476,94,236",
    "answer": "赤地千里",
    "explain": "赤地千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 1903,
    "question": "35,4,207,366",
    "answer": "安良除暴",
    "explain": "安良除暴"
  },
  {
    "level": 1904,
    "question": "577,313,380,771",
    "answer": "酌盈剂虚",
    "explain": "酌盈剂虚"
  },
  {
    "level": 1905,
    "question": "525,182,230,77",
    "answer": "滴水成冰",
    "explain": "滴水成冰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1906,
    "question": "408,474,7,162",
    "answer": "徒劳无功",
    "explain": "徒劳无功"
  },
  {
    "level": 1907,
    "question": "486,47,35,322",
    "answer": "死于安乐",
    "explain": "死于安乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1908,
    "question": "461,743,651,3",
    "answer": "街谈巷议",
    "explain": "街谈巷议"
  },
  {
    "level": 1909,
    "question": "408,752,652,777",
    "answer": "图穷匕见",
    "explain": "图穷匕见"
  },
  {
    "level": 1910,
    "question": "11,486,446,428",
    "answer": "救死扶伤",
    "explain": "救死扶伤"
  },
  {
    "level": 1911,
    "question": "3,47,246,90",
    "answer": "易于反手",
    "explain": "易于反手"
  },
  {
    "level": 1912,
    "question": "407,147,113,599",
    "answer": "护国佑民",
    "explain": "护国佑民"
  },
  {
    "level": 1913,
    "question": "533,236,489,3",
    "answer": "百里挑一",
    "explain": "百里挑一"
  },
  {
    "level": 1914,
    "question": "460,821,426,426",
    "answer": "人言啧啧",
    "explain": "人言啧啧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1915,
    "question": "652,376,647,103",
    "answer": "奸掳烧杀",
    "explain": "奸掳烧杀"
  },
  {
    "level": 1916,
    "question": "431,356,232,451",
    "answer": "赤诚相待",
    "explain": "赤诚相待"
  },
  {
    "level": 1917,
    "question": "374,218,3,232",
    "answer": "变俗易教",
    "explain": "变俗易教"
  },
  {
    "level": 1918,
    "question": "749,732,579,35",
    "answer": "忐忑不安",
    "explain": "忐忑不安"
  },
  {
    "level": 1919,
    "question": "799,5,503,6",
    "answer": "接三连四",
    "explain": "接三连四"
  },
  {
    "level": 1920,
    "question": "94,165,161,165",
    "answer": "必有近忧",
    "explain": "必有近忧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1921,
    "question": "821,424,162,424",
    "answer": "洗耳恭听",
    "explain": "洗耳恭听"
  },
  {
    "level": 1922,
    "question": "423,580,45,182",
    "answer": "精卫填海",
    "explain": "精卫填海"
  },
  {
    "level": 1923,
    "question": "734,33,94,432",
    "answer": "分秒必争",
    "explain": "分秒必争"
  },
  {
    "level": 1924,
    "question": "245,746,554,165",
    "answer": "内顾之忧",
    "explain": "内顾之忧"
  },
  {
    "level": 1925,
    "question": "280,147,280,69",
    "answer": "平起平坐",
    "explain": "平起平坐"
  },
  {
    "level": 1926,
    "question": "378,556,412,555",
    "answer": "猴年马月",
    "explain": "猴年马月"
  },
  {
    "level": 1927,
    "question": "408,389,497,427",
    "answer": "徒费唇舌",
    "explain": "徒费唇舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 1928,
    "question": "378,298,841,841",
    "answer": "微风习习",
    "explain": "微风习习"
  },
  {
    "level": 1929,
    "question": "230,222,380,49",
    "answer": "星罗棋布",
    "explain": "星罗棋布"
  },
  {
    "level": 1930,
    "question": "445,2,480,696",
    "answer": "军令如山",
    "explain": "军令如山"
  },
  {
    "level": 1931,
    "question": "273,423,215,215",
    "answer": "万目睽睽",
    "explain": "万目睽睽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1932,
    "question": "460,130,380,412",
    "answer": "人中骐骥",
    "explain": "人中骐骥"
  },
  {
    "level": 1933,
    "question": "5,641,8,545",
    "answer": "三十六计",
    "explain": "三十六计"
  },
  {
    "level": 1934,
    "question": "273,486,785,210",
    "answer": "万古长青",
    "explain": "万古长青"
  },
  {
    "level": 1935,
    "question": "647,647,647,647",
    "answer": "火烧火燎",
    "explain": "火烧火燎"
  },
  {
    "level": 1936,
    "question": "555,130,25,486",
    "answer": "月中折桂",
    "explain": "月中折桂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1937,
    "question": "650,653,73,207",
    "answer": "高瞻远瞩",
    "explain": "高瞻远瞩"
  },
  {
    "level": 1938,
    "question": "491,431,630,44",
    "answer": "壮志凌云",
    "explain": "壮志凌云"
  },
  {
    "level": 1939,
    "question": "342,373,831,565",
    "answer": "用舍行藏",
    "explain": "用舍行藏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1940,
    "question": "236,109,236,186",
    "answer": "离心离德",
    "explain": "离心离德"
  },
  {
    "level": 1941,
    "question": "3,650,319,562",
    "answer": "遗大投艰",
    "explain": "遗大投艰"
  },
  {
    "level": 1942,
    "question": "6,280,10,501",
    "answer": "四平八稳",
    "explain": "四平八稳"
  },
  {
    "level": 1943,
    "question": "73,73,571,571",
    "answer": "原原本本",
    "explain": "原原本本"
  },
  {
    "level": 1944,
    "question": "481,92,273,457",
    "answer": "昂首阔步",
    "explain": "昂首阔步"
  },
  {
    "level": 1945,
    "question": "92,167,480,47",
    "answer": "守身如玉",
    "explain": "守身如玉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1946,
    "question": "43,403,177,696",
    "answer": "日落西山",
    "explain": "日落西山"
  },
  {
    "level": 1947,
    "question": "426,424,298,426",
    "answer": "道听途说",
    "explain": "道听途说"
  },
  {
    "level": 1948,
    "question": "92,119,176,499",
    "answer": "掌上明珠",
    "explain": "掌上明珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 1949,
    "question": "460,821,171,45",
    "answer": "人言可畏",
    "explain": "人言可畏"
  },
  {
    "level": 1950,
    "question": "641,112,165,322",
    "answer": "事出有因",
    "explain": "事出有因"
  },
  {
    "level": 1951,
    "question": "389,97,273,236",
    "answer": "鹏程万里",
    "explain": "鹏程万里"
  },
  {
    "level": 1952,
    "question": "777,460,777,160",
    "answer": "见仁见智",
    "explain": "见仁见智"
  },
  {
    "level": 1953,
    "question": "495,842,130,177",
    "answer": "学贯中西",
    "explain": "学贯中西"
  },
  {
    "level": 1954,
    "question": "45,168,3,66",
    "answer": "天各一方",
    "explain": "天各一方"
  },
  {
    "level": 1955,
    "question": "650,743,650,812",
    "answer": "高谈大论",
    "explain": "高谈大论"
  },
  {
    "level": 1956,
    "question": "431,109,654,531",
    "answer": "痴心妄想",
    "explain": "痴心妄想"
  },
  {
    "level": 1957,
    "question": "305,389,460,270",
    "answer": "肠肥脑满",
    "explain": "肠肥脑满"
  },
  {
    "level": 1958,
    "question": "3,333,554,182",
    "answer": "一丘之貉",
    "explain": "一丘之貉"
  },
  {
    "level": 1959,
    "question": "423,431,737,641",
    "answer": "目指气使",
    "explain": "目指气使"
  },
  {
    "level": 1960,
    "question": "222,298,591,469",
    "answer": "秋风送爽",
    "explain": "秋风送爽"
  },
  {
    "level": 1961,
    "question": "650,743,273,812",
    "answer": "高谈阔论",
    "explain": "高谈阔论"
  },
  {
    "level": 1962,
    "question": "160,827,7,246",
    "answer": "只轮无反",
    "explain": "只轮无反"
  },
  {
    "level": 1963,
    "question": "771,67,344,3",
    "answer": "虚情假意",
    "explain": "虚情假意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1964,
    "question": "94,363,271,641",
    "answer": "弊衣箪食",
    "explain": "弊衣箪食"
  },
  {
    "level": 1965,
    "question": "647,207,323,213",
    "answer": "火树银花",
    "explain": "火树银花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1966,
    "question": "3,647,431,170",
    "answer": "怡然自得",
    "explain": "怡然自得"
  },
  {
    "level": 1967,
    "question": "499,633,94,163",
    "answer": "珠联璧合",
    "explain": "珠联璧合"
  },
  {
    "level": 1968,
    "question": "135,799,478,423",
    "answer": "迫在眉睫",
    "explain": "迫在眉睫"
  },
  {
    "level": 1969,
    "question": "785,556,5,369",
    "answer": "长年三老",
    "explain": "长年三老"
  },
  {
    "level": 1970,
    "question": "3,207,533,647",
    "answer": "一树百获",
    "explain": "一树百获"
  },
  {
    "level": 1971,
    "question": "4,365,232,146",
    "answer": "两虎相斗",
    "explain": "两虎相斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 1972,
    "question": "171,256,165,32",
    "answer": "克鲜有终",
    "explain": "克鲜有终"
  },
  {
    "level": 1973,
    "question": "10,555,230,391",
    "answer": "八字成语",
    "explain": "八字成语"
  },
  {
    "level": 1974,
    "question": "737,11,408,109",
    "answer": "弃旧图新",
    "explain": "弃旧图新"
  },
  {
    "level": 1975,
    "question": "5,246,7,652",
    "answer": "三番五次",
    "explain": "三番五次"
  },
  {
    "level": 1976,
    "question": "533,6,579,461",
    "answer": "百思不解",
    "explain": "百思不解"
  },
  {
    "level": 1977,
    "question": "478,213,538,486",
    "answer": "荣华富贵",
    "explain": "荣华富贵"
  },
  {
    "level": 1978,
    "question": "325,7,771,493",
    "answer": "弹无虚发",
    "explain": "弹无虚发"
  },
  {
    "level": 1979,
    "question": "3,6,579,486",
    "answer": "一丝不挂",
    "explain": "一丝不挂"
  },
  {
    "level": 1980,
    "question": "219,460,45,476",
    "answer": "草头天子",
    "explain": "草头天子"
  },
  {
    "level": 1981,
    "question": "690,226,554,641",
    "answer": "狷介之士",
    "explain": "狷介之士"
  },
  {
    "level": 1982,
    "question": "460,476,7,594",
    "answer": "人而无信",
    "explain": "人而无信"
  },
  {
    "level": 1983,
    "question": "3,7,3,641",
    "answer": "一五一十",
    "explain": "一五一十"
  },
  {
    "level": 1984,
    "question": "210,112,47,663",
    "answer": "青出于蓝",
    "explain": "青出于蓝"
  },
  {
    "level": 1985,
    "question": "171,812,333,700",
    "answer": "刻舟求剑",
    "explain": "刻舟求剑"
  },
  {
    "level": 1986,
    "question": "298,491,460,67",
    "answer": "风土人情",
    "explain": "风土人情"
  },
  {
    "level": 1987,
    "question": "753,238,3,333",
    "answer": "梦寐以求",
    "explain": "梦寐以求"
  },
  {
    "level": 1988,
    "question": "379,381,579,776",
    "answer": "鸡犬不宁",
    "explain": "鸡犬不宁"
  },
  {
    "level": 1989,
    "question": "435,641,214,157",
    "answer": "好事多磨",
    "explain": "好事多磨"
  },
  {
    "level": 1990,
    "question": "696,130,389,232",
    "answer": "山中宰相",
    "explain": "山中宰相"
  },
  {
    "level": 1991,
    "question": "232,7,495,427",
    "answer": "鹦鹉学舌",
    "explain": "鹦鹉学舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 1992,
    "question": "5,734,384,460",
    "answer": "三分象人",
    "explain": "三分象人"
  },
  {
    "level": 1993,
    "question": "95,279,528,283",
    "answer": "披肝沥胆",
    "explain": "披肝沥胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 1994,
    "question": "32,834,226,423",
    "answer": "终南捷径",
    "explain": "终南捷径"
  },
  {
    "level": 1995,
    "question": "495,109,641,3",
    "answer": "真心实意",
    "explain": "真心实意"
  },
  {
    "level": 1996,
    "question": "478,461,330,213",
    "answer": "美女簪花",
    "explain": "美女簪花"
  },
  {
    "level": 1997,
    "question": "236,45,336,147",
    "answer": "里通外国",
    "explain": "里通外国"
  },
  {
    "level": 1998,
    "question": "101,480,837,367",
    "answer": "动如脱兔",
    "explain": "动如脱兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 1999,
    "question": "773,528,236,432",
    "answer": "据理力争",
    "explain": "据理力争"
  },
  {
    "level": 2000,
    "question": "7,380,94,246",
    "answer": "物极必反",
    "explain": "物极必反"
  },
  {
    "level": 2001,
    "question": "522,376,641,647",
    "answer": "骄阳似火",
    "explain": "骄阳似火"
  },
  {
    "level": 2002,
    "question": "210,249,423,426",
    "answer": "青面獠牙",
    "explain": "青面獠牙"
  },
  {
    "level": 2003,
    "question": "163,130,503,111",
    "answer": "合纵连横",
    "explain": "合纵连横"
  },
  {
    "level": 2004,
    "question": "7,179,641,174",
    "answer": "五光十色",
    "explain": "五光十色"
  },
  {
    "level": 2005,
    "question": "821,662,431,392",
    "answer": "短垣自逾",
    "explain": "短垣自逾"
  },
  {
    "level": 2006,
    "question": "5,167,165,831",
    "answer": "三生有幸",
    "explain": "三生有幸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2007,
    "question": "176,579,771,600",
    "answer": "名不虚传",
    "explain": "名不虚传"
  },
  {
    "level": 2008,
    "question": "424,423,130,214",
    "answer": "耳目众多",
    "explain": "耳目众多"
  },
  {
    "level": 2009,
    "question": "7,101,47,130",
    "answer": "无动于衷",
    "explain": "无动于衷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2010,
    "question": "3,176,94,556",
    "answer": "一夕千念",
    "explain": "一夕千念"
  },
  {
    "level": 2011,
    "question": "3,7,628,165",
    "answer": "一无所有",
    "explain": "一无所有"
  },
  {
    "level": 2012,
    "question": "8,35,213,176",
    "answer": "柳暗花明",
    "explain": "柳暗花明"
  },
  {
    "level": 2013,
    "question": "557,773,173,648",
    "answer": "证据确凿",
    "explain": "证据确凿"
  },
  {
    "level": 2014,
    "question": "175,471,431,650",
    "answer": "夜郎自大",
    "explain": "夜郎自大"
  },
  {
    "level": 2015,
    "question": "246,369,188,298",
    "answer": "返老还童",
    "explain": "返老还童"
  },
  {
    "level": 2016,
    "question": "460,369,499,71",
    "answer": "人老珠黄",
    "explain": "人老珠黄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2017,
    "question": "460,737,154,431",
    "answer": "人迹罕至",
    "explain": "人迹罕至"
  },
  {
    "level": 2018,
    "question": "398,161,162,565",
    "answer": "鸟尽弓藏",
    "explain": "鸟尽弓藏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2019,
    "question": "3,14,476,47",
    "answer": "一哄而散",
    "explain": "一哄而散"
  },
  {
    "level": 2020,
    "question": "157,563,230,495",
    "answer": "磨杵成针",
    "explain": "磨杵成针"
  },
  {
    "level": 2021,
    "question": "27,389,176,230",
    "answer": "寥若晨星",
    "explain": "寥若晨星"
  },
  {
    "level": 2022,
    "question": "92,426,480,468",
    "answer": "守口如瓶",
    "explain": "守口如瓶"
  },
  {
    "level": 2023,
    "question": "94,445,3,493",
    "answer": "千钧一发",
    "explain": "千钧一发"
  },
  {
    "level": 2024,
    "question": "47,6,298,221",
    "answer": "雨丝风片",
    "explain": "雨丝风片"
  },
  {
    "level": 2025,
    "question": "533,162,94,565",
    "answer": "百孔千疮",
    "explain": "百孔千疮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2026,
    "question": "45,412,831,162",
    "answer": "天马行空",
    "explain": "天马行空"
  },
  {
    "level": 2027,
    "question": "182,2,453,90",
    "answer": "河梁携手",
    "explain": "河梁携手"
  },
  {
    "level": 2028,
    "question": "772,3,246,5",
    "answer": "举一反三",
    "explain": "举一反三"
  },
  {
    "level": 2029,
    "question": "94,821,273,391",
    "answer": "千言万语",
    "explain": "千言万语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2030,
    "question": "93,93,630,630",
    "answer": "业业矜矜",
    "explain": "业业矜矜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2031,
    "question": "94,402,3,49",
    "answer": "千虑一失",
    "explain": "千虑一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 2032,
    "question": "567,236,232,380",
    "answer": "表里相济",
    "explain": "表里相济"
  },
  {
    "level": 2033,
    "question": "7,389,7,314",
    "answer": "无声无息",
    "explain": "无声无息"
  },
  {
    "level": 2034,
    "question": "81,655,579,222",
    "answer": "既往不咎",
    "explain": "既往不咎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2035,
    "question": "3,45,167,785",
    "answer": "意味深长",
    "explain": "意味深长"
  },
  {
    "level": 2036,
    "question": "7,555,630,819",
    "answer": "五福临门",
    "explain": "五福临门"
  },
  {
    "level": 2037,
    "question": "218,579,171,348",
    "answer": "俗不可医",
    "explain": "俗不可医"
  },
  {
    "level": 2038,
    "question": "812,132,171,725",
    "answer": "和蔼可亲",
    "explain": "和蔼可亲"
  },
  {
    "level": 2039,
    "question": "273,130,3,109",
    "answer": "万众一心",
    "explain": "万众一心"
  },
  {
    "level": 2040,
    "question": "279,630,3,109",
    "answer": "甘棠遗爱",
    "explain": "甘棠遗爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2041,
    "question": "342,696,246,182",
    "answer": "游山玩水",
    "explain": "游山玩水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2042,
    "question": "143,162,522,225",
    "answer": "能工巧匠",
    "explain": "能工巧匠"
  },
  {
    "level": 2043,
    "question": "73,45,165,460",
    "answer": "怨天尤人",
    "explain": "怨天尤人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2044,
    "question": "474,564,579,696",
    "answer": "络绎不绝",
    "explain": "络绎不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2045,
    "question": "530,218,11,109",
    "answer": "去故就新",
    "explain": "去故就新"
  },
  {
    "level": 2046,
    "question": "177,2,423,176",
    "answer": "朝梁暮陈",
    "explain": "朝梁暮陈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2047,
    "question": "746,650,333,167",
    "answer": "苦大仇深",
    "explain": "苦大仇深"
  },
  {
    "level": 2048,
    "question": "523,389,434,300",
    "answer": "差若毫氂",
    "explain": "差若毫氂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2049,
    "question": "88,278,270,322",
    "answer": "对酒当歌",
    "explain": "对酒当歌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2050,
    "question": "397,579,230,389",
    "answer": "泣不成声",
    "explain": "泣不成声"
  },
  {
    "level": 2051,
    "question": "423,130,7,460",
    "answer": "目中无人",
    "explain": "目中无人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2052,
    "question": "182,655,431,37",
    "answer": "勇往直前",
    "explain": "勇往直前"
  },
  {
    "level": 2053,
    "question": "173,478,753,36",
    "answer": "须眉茭白",
    "explain": "须眉茭白"
  },
  {
    "level": 2054,
    "question": "555,641,495,207",
    "answer": "浮石沉木",
    "explain": "浮石沉木"
  },
  {
    "level": 2055,
    "question": "280,109,617,737",
    "answer": "平心静气",
    "explain": "平心静气"
  },
  {
    "level": 2056,
    "question": "567,236,480,3",
    "answer": "表里如一",
    "explain": "表里如一"
  },
  {
    "level": 2057,
    "question": "476,120,776,425",
    "answer": "地下修文",
    "explain": "地下修文"
  },
  {
    "level": 2058,
    "question": "3,7,628,722",
    "answer": "一无所知",
    "explain": "一无所知"
  },
  {
    "level": 2059,
    "question": "36,493,559,559",
    "answer": "白发苍苍",
    "explain": "白发苍苍"
  },
  {
    "level": 2060,
    "question": "6,412,471,336",
    "answer": "驷马难追",
    "explain": "驷马难追"
  },
  {
    "level": 2061,
    "question": "3,365,533,312",
    "answer": "一呼百应",
    "explain": "一呼百应"
  },
  {
    "level": 2062,
    "question": "147,457,562,471",
    "answer": "国步艰难",
    "explain": "国步艰难"
  },
  {
    "level": 2063,
    "question": "273,227,94,80",
    "answer": "万紫千红",
    "explain": "万紫千红"
  },
  {
    "level": 2064,
    "question": "650,111,248,248",
    "answer": "大腹便便",
    "explain": "大腹便便"
  },
  {
    "level": 2065,
    "question": "460,486,182,176",
    "answer": "人死留名",
    "explain": "人死留名"
  },
  {
    "level": 2066,
    "question": "9,785,10,821",
    "answer": "七长八短",
    "explain": "七长八短"
  },
  {
    "level": 2067,
    "question": "236,432,119,342",
    "answer": "力争上游",
    "explain": "力争上游"
  },
  {
    "level": 2068,
    "question": "424,32,423,176",
    "answer": "耳聪目明",
    "explain": "耳聪目明"
  },
  {
    "level": 2069,
    "question": "298,415,435,556",
    "answer": "风烛残年",
    "explain": "风烛残年"
  },
  {
    "level": 2070,
    "question": "489,489,435,435",
    "answer": "踉踉跄跄",
    "explain": "踉踉跄跄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2071,
    "question": "310,90,310,457",
    "answer": "毛手毛脚",
    "explain": "毛手毛脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2072,
    "question": "3,6,579,381",
    "answer": "一丝不苟",
    "explain": "一丝不苟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2073,
    "question": "276,298,365,707",
    "answer": "北风呼啸",
    "explain": "北风呼啸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2074,
    "question": "562,101,506,89",
    "answer": "瑞雪纷飞",
    "explain": "瑞雪纷飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2075,
    "question": "4,65,554,435",
    "answer": "二姓之好",
    "explain": "二姓之好"
  },
  {
    "level": 2076,
    "question": "807,563,230,495",
    "answer": "铁杵成针",
    "explain": "铁杵成针"
  },
  {
    "level": 2077,
    "question": "8,752,213,128",
    "answer": "柳宠花迷",
    "explain": "柳宠花迷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2078,
    "question": "777,528,6,3",
    "answer": "见利思义",
    "explain": "见利思义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2079,
    "question": "641,486,579,502",
    "answer": "食古不化",
    "explain": "食古不化"
  },
  {
    "level": 2080,
    "question": "412,162,49,180",
    "answer": "马工枚速",
    "explain": "马工枚速"
  },
  {
    "level": 2081,
    "question": "497,426,232,3",
    "answer": "唇齿相依",
    "explain": "唇齿相依"
  },
  {
    "level": 2082,
    "question": "561,819,478,446",
    "answer": "班门弄斧",
    "explain": "班门弄斧"
  },
  {
    "level": 2083,
    "question": "380,655,819,120",
    "answer": "继往开来",
    "explain": "继往开来"
  },
  {
    "level": 2084,
    "question": "4,82,339,478",
    "answer": "两全其美",
    "explain": "两全其美"
  },
  {
    "level": 2085,
    "question": "182,130,474,555",
    "answer": "海中捞月",
    "explain": "海中捞月"
  },
  {
    "level": 2086,
    "question": "389,161,655,641",
    "answer": "废寝忘食",
    "explain": "废寝忘食"
  },
  {
    "level": 2087,
    "question": "374,827,652,380",
    "answer": "香轮宝骑",
    "explain": "香轮宝骑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2088,
    "question": "579,722,167,87",
    "answer": "不知深浅",
    "explain": "不知深浅"
  },
  {
    "level": 2089,
    "question": "591,655,290,120",
    "answer": "送往迎来",
    "explain": "送往迎来"
  },
  {
    "level": 2090,
    "question": "415,6,412,737",
    "answer": "蛛丝马迹",
    "explain": "蛛丝马迹"
  },
  {
    "level": 2091,
    "question": "495,623,486,460",
    "answer": "达官贵人",
    "explain": "达官贵人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2092,
    "question": "502,373,108,457",
    "answer": "画蛇添足",
    "explain": "画蛇添足"
  },
  {
    "level": 2093,
    "question": "298,44,460,7",
    "answer": "风云人物",
    "explain": "风云人物"
  },
  {
    "level": 2094,
    "question": "45,82,495,374",
    "answer": "通权达变",
    "explain": "通权达变"
  },
  {
    "level": 2095,
    "question": "641,725,539,74",
    "answer": "食亲财黑",
    "explain": "食亲财黑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2096,
    "question": "6,579,4,389",
    "answer": "势不两立",
    "explain": "势不两立"
  },
  {
    "level": 2097,
    "question": "293,777,3,191",
    "answer": "略见一斑",
    "explain": "略见一斑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2098,
    "question": "93,219,256,213",
    "answer": "野草闲花",
    "explain": "野草闲花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2099,
    "question": "506,431,296,120",
    "answer": "纷至沓来",
    "explain": "纷至沓来"
  },
  {
    "level": 2100,
    "question": "101,652,177,47",
    "answer": "东逃西散",
    "explain": "东逃西散"
  },
  {
    "level": 2101,
    "question": "3,426,496,696",
    "answer": "一口咬定",
    "explain": "一口咬定"
  },
  {
    "level": 2102,
    "question": "193,45,273,294",
    "answer": "经纬万端",
    "explain": "经纬万端"
  },
  {
    "level": 2103,
    "question": "92,772,3,431",
    "answer": "首屈一指",
    "explain": "首屈一指"
  },
  {
    "level": 2104,
    "question": "655,82,222,182",
    "answer": "望穿秋水",
    "explain": "望穿秋水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2105,
    "question": "478,344,230,495",
    "answer": "弄假成真",
    "explain": "弄假成真"
  },
  {
    "level": 2106,
    "question": "641,371,298,44",
    "answer": "叱咤风云",
    "explain": "叱咤风云"
  },
  {
    "level": 2107,
    "question": "486,377,170,363",
    "answer": "亡羊得牛",
    "explain": "亡羊得牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2108,
    "question": "460,130,457,67",
    "answer": "头重脚轻",
    "explain": "头重脚轻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2109,
    "question": "460,628,304,722",
    "answer": "人所共知",
    "explain": "人所共知"
  },
  {
    "level": 2110,
    "question": "526,462,7,278",
    "answer": "匹夫无罪",
    "explain": "匹夫无罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2111,
    "question": "533,556,207,460",
    "answer": "百年树人",
    "explain": "百年树人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2112,
    "question": "373,426,389,495",
    "answer": "蛇口蜂针",
    "explain": "蛇口蜂针"
  },
  {
    "level": 2113,
    "question": "147,672,71,213",
    "answer": "过时黄花",
    "explain": "过时黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2114,
    "question": "312,44,476,167",
    "answer": "应运而生",
    "explain": "应运而生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2115,
    "question": "26,162,373,313",
    "answer": "杯弓蛇影",
    "explain": "杯弓蛇影"
  },
  {
    "level": 2116,
    "question": "314,182,785,8",
    "answer": "细水长流",
    "explain": "细水长流"
  },
  {
    "level": 2117,
    "question": "10,700,232,382",
    "answer": "拔剑相助",
    "explain": "拔剑相助"
  },
  {
    "level": 2118,
    "question": "45,222,476,439",
    "answer": "天罗地网",
    "explain": "天罗地网"
  },
  {
    "level": 2119,
    "question": "94,66,533,545",
    "answer": "千方百计",
    "explain": "千方百计"
  },
  {
    "level": 2120,
    "question": "478,460,374,219",
    "answer": "美人香草",
    "explain": "美人香草"
  },
  {
    "level": 2121,
    "question": "391,460,554,528",
    "answer": "渔人之利",
    "explain": "渔人之利"
  },
  {
    "level": 2122,
    "question": "87,640,579,579",
    "answer": "坚持不懈",
    "explain": "坚持不懈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2123,
    "question": "652,276,480,8",
    "answer": "倒背如流",
    "explain": "倒背如流"
  },
  {
    "level": 2124,
    "question": "579,584,476,205",
    "answer": "不寒而栗",
    "explain": "不寒而栗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2125,
    "question": "423,579,120,799",
    "answer": "目不暇接",
    "explain": "目不暇接"
  },
  {
    "level": 2126,
    "question": "655,434,111,3",
    "answer": "忘恩负义",
    "explain": "忘恩负义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2127,
    "question": "445,711,445,283",
    "answer": "群威群胆",
    "explain": "群威群胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2128,
    "question": "381,768,365,821",
    "answer": "狼吞虎咽",
    "explain": "狼吞虎咽"
  },
  {
    "level": 2129,
    "question": "177,368,502,365",
    "answer": "照猫画虎",
    "explain": "照猫画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2130,
    "question": "478,1,554,256",
    "answer": "美芹之献",
    "explain": "美芹之献"
  },
  {
    "level": 2131,
    "question": "298,389,278,821",
    "answer": "风声鹤唳",
    "explain": "风声鹤唳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2132,
    "question": "182,393,620,401",
    "answer": "水乳交融",
    "explain": "水乳交融"
  },
  {
    "level": 2133,
    "question": "425,298,476,147",
    "answer": "闻风而起",
    "explain": "闻风而起"
  },
  {
    "level": 2134,
    "question": "270,73,210,174",
    "answer": "满园春色",
    "explain": "满园春色"
  },
  {
    "level": 2135,
    "question": "641,273,647,380",
    "answer": "十万火急",
    "explain": "十万火急"
  },
  {
    "level": 2136,
    "question": "49,380,752,819",
    "answer": "否极泰回",
    "explain": "否极泰回"
  },
  {
    "level": 2137,
    "question": "737,6,400,45",
    "answer": "气势雄伟",
    "explain": "气势雄伟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2138,
    "question": "7,641,460,389",
    "answer": "物是人非",
    "explain": "物是人非"
  },
  {
    "level": 2139,
    "question": "3,412,270,502",
    "answer": "一马当先",
    "explain": "一马当先"
  },
  {
    "level": 2140,
    "question": "813,175,159,566",
    "answer": "转弯抹角",
    "explain": "转弯抹角"
  },
  {
    "level": 2141,
    "question": "229,555,336,43",
    "answer": "夸父追日",
    "explain": "夸父追日"
  },
  {
    "level": 2142,
    "question": "427,700,497,653",
    "answer": "舌剑唇枪",
    "explain": "舌剑唇枪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2143,
    "question": "501,647,650,734",
    "answer": "勃然大怒",
    "explain": "勃然大怒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2144,
    "question": "276,356,461,3",
    "answer": "背城借一",
    "explain": "背城借一"
  },
  {
    "level": 2145,
    "question": "400,379,366,647",
    "answer": "雄鸡报晓",
    "explain": "雄鸡报晓"
  },
  {
    "level": 2146,
    "question": "3,207,471,431",
    "answer": "一木难支",
    "explain": "一木难支"
  },
  {
    "level": 2147,
    "question": "87,460,579,10",
    "answer": "坚韧不拔",
    "explain": "坚韧不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 2148,
    "question": "3,799,821,336",
    "answer": "意在言外",
    "explain": "意在言外"
  },
  {
    "level": 2149,
    "question": "186,650,655,130",
    "answer": "德高望重",
    "explain": "德高望重"
  },
  {
    "level": 2150,
    "question": "781,298,135,182",
    "answer": "乘风破浪",
    "explain": "乘风破浪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2151,
    "question": "218,525,460,278",
    "answer": "故入人罪",
    "explain": "故入人罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2152,
    "question": "496,390,273,842",
    "answer": "腰缠万贯",
    "explain": "腰缠万贯"
  },
  {
    "level": 2153,
    "question": "71,628,47,71",
    "answer": "为所欲为",
    "explain": "为所欲为"
  },
  {
    "level": 2154,
    "question": "165,469,47,167",
    "answer": "忧患余生",
    "explain": "忧患余生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2155,
    "question": "746,561,431,400",
    "answer": "顾盼自雄",
    "explain": "顾盼自雄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2156,
    "question": "162,746,600,389",
    "answer": "空谷传声",
    "explain": "空谷传声"
  },
  {
    "level": 2157,
    "question": "412,579,308,422",
    "answer": "马不停蹄",
    "explain": "马不停蹄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2158,
    "question": "9,90,10,457",
    "answer": "七手八脚",
    "explain": "七手八脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2159,
    "question": "3,273,531,556",
    "answer": "亿万斯年",
    "explain": "亿万斯年"
  },
  {
    "level": 2160,
    "question": "3,310,579,10",
    "answer": "一毛不拔",
    "explain": "一毛不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 2161,
    "question": "480,831,280,476",
    "answer": "如履平地",
    "explain": "如履平地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2162,
    "question": "9,2,10,403",
    "answer": "七零八落",
    "explain": "七零八落"
  },
  {
    "level": 2163,
    "question": "366,460,111,110",
    "answer": "暴敛横征",
    "explain": "暴敛横征"
  },
  {
    "level": 2164,
    "question": "65,65,384,478",
    "answer": "欣欣向荣",
    "explain": "欣欣向荣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2165,
    "question": "746,412,528,101",
    "answer": "谷马砺兵",
    "explain": "谷马砺兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2166,
    "question": "451,71,426,605",
    "answer": "代为说项",
    "explain": "代为说项"
  },
  {
    "level": 2167,
    "question": "119,120,620,753",
    "answer": "上下交困",
    "explain": "上下交困"
  },
  {
    "level": 2168,
    "question": "3,249,554,620",
    "answer": "一面之交",
    "explain": "一面之交"
  },
  {
    "level": 2169,
    "question": "110,799,503,45",
    "answer": "甲第连天",
    "explain": "甲第连天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2170,
    "question": "711,470,333,82",
    "answer": "委曲求全",
    "explain": "委曲求全"
  },
  {
    "level": 2171,
    "question": "109,641,130,130",
    "answer": "心事重重",
    "explain": "心事重重"
  },
  {
    "level": 2172,
    "question": "480,777,339,460",
    "answer": "如见其人",
    "explain": "如见其人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2173,
    "question": "3,391,135,773",
    "answer": "一语破的",
    "explain": "一语破的"
  },
  {
    "level": 2174,
    "question": "7,628,45,407",
    "answer": "无所畏惧",
    "explain": "无所畏惧"
  },
  {
    "level": 2175,
    "question": "579,333,167,461",
    "answer": "不求甚解",
    "explain": "不求甚解"
  },
  {
    "level": 2176,
    "question": "249,249,579,762",
    "answer": "喋喋不休",
    "explain": "喋喋不休"
  },
  {
    "level": 2177,
    "question": "45,650,44,326",
    "answer": "天高云淡",
    "explain": "天高云淡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2178,
    "question": "38,147,554,762",
    "answer": "后起之秀",
    "explain": "后起之秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 2179,
    "question": "365,460,365,711",
    "answer": "虎头虎尾",
    "explain": "虎头虎尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 2180,
    "question": "412,753,431,705",
    "answer": "麻雀虽小",
    "explain": "麻雀虽小"
  },
  {
    "level": 2181,
    "question": "273,182,94,696",
    "answer": "万水千山",
    "explain": "万水千山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2182,
    "question": "436,407,438,82",
    "answer": "才貌双全",
    "explain": "才貌双全"
  },
  {
    "level": 2183,
    "question": "533,501,230,649",
    "answer": "百炼成钢",
    "explain": "百炼成钢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2184,
    "question": "147,175,271,74",
    "answer": "起早贪黑",
    "explain": "起早贪黑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2185,
    "question": "167,525,87,112",
    "answer": "深入简出",
    "explain": "深入简出"
  },
  {
    "level": 2186,
    "question": "73,73,579,696",
    "answer": "源源不绝",
    "explain": "源源不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2187,
    "question": "382,460,71,322",
    "answer": "助人为乐",
    "explain": "助人为乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2188,
    "question": "324,365,753,469",
    "answer": "欢呼雀跃",
    "explain": "欢呼雀跃"
  },
  {
    "level": 2189,
    "question": "109,776,431,356",
    "answer": "心虔志诚",
    "explain": "心虔志诚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2190,
    "question": "482,436,3,3",
    "answer": "神采奕奕",
    "explain": "神采奕奕"
  },
  {
    "level": 2191,
    "question": "734,7,45,479",
    "answer": "胸无点墨",
    "explain": "胸无点墨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2192,
    "question": "457,422,641,476",
    "answer": "脚踏实地",
    "explain": "脚踏实地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2193,
    "question": "147,423,44,821",
    "answer": "过眼云烟",
    "explain": "过眼云烟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2194,
    "question": "565,519,463,180",
    "answer": "张灯结彩",
    "explain": "张灯结彩"
  },
  {
    "level": 2195,
    "question": "182,157,162,462",
    "answer": "水磨工夫",
    "explain": "水磨工夫"
  },
  {
    "level": 2196,
    "question": "647,415,323,213",
    "answer": "火烛银花",
    "explain": "火烛银花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2197,
    "question": "8,482,7,415",
    "answer": "六神无主",
    "explain": "六神无主"
  },
  {
    "level": 2198,
    "question": "35,538,776,478",
    "answer": "安富尊荣",
    "explain": "安富尊荣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2199,
    "question": "533,3,533,316",
    "answer": "百依百顺",
    "explain": "百依百顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2200,
    "question": "380,207,3,343",
    "answer": "机杼一家",
    "explain": "机杼一家"
  },
  {
    "level": 2201,
    "question": "3,230,579,374",
    "answer": "一成不变",
    "explain": "一成不变"
  },
  {
    "level": 2202,
    "question": "641,579,147,111",
    "answer": "食不果腹",
    "explain": "食不果腹"
  },
  {
    "level": 2203,
    "question": "94,486,696,305",
    "answer": "千古绝唱",
    "explain": "千古绝唱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2204,
    "question": "4,270,5,280",
    "answer": "二满三平",
    "explain": "二满三平"
  },
  {
    "level": 2205,
    "question": "696,176,182,762",
    "answer": "山明水秀",
    "explain": "山明水秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 2206,
    "question": "411,455,554,416",
    "answer": "井底之蛙",
    "explain": "井底之蛙"
  },
  {
    "level": 2207,
    "question": "426,389,696,182",
    "answer": "口若悬河",
    "explain": "口若悬河"
  },
  {
    "level": 2208,
    "question": "696,387,400,45",
    "answer": "峰峦雄伟",
    "explain": "峰峦雄伟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2209,
    "question": "176,470,495,94",
    "answer": "明婚正配",
    "explain": "明婚正配"
  },
  {
    "level": 2210,
    "question": "435,380,11,380",
    "answer": "将机就机",
    "explain": "将机就机"
  },
  {
    "level": 2211,
    "question": "318,318,165,47",
    "answer": "绰绰有余",
    "explain": "绰绰有余"
  },
  {
    "level": 2212,
    "question": "339,389,5,278",
    "answer": "驭凤骖鹤",
    "explain": "驭凤骖鹤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2213,
    "question": "304,101,539,435",
    "answer": "调兵遣将",
    "explain": "调兵遣将"
  },
  {
    "level": 2214,
    "question": "5,389,6,86",
    "answer": "三朋四友",
    "explain": "三朋四友"
  },
  {
    "level": 2215,
    "question": "460,249,92,109",
    "answer": "人面兽心",
    "explain": "人面兽心"
  },
  {
    "level": 2216,
    "question": "75,109,489,283",
    "answer": "提心吊胆",
    "explain": "提心吊胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2217,
    "question": "312,165,161,165",
    "answer": "应有尽有",
    "explain": "应有尽有"
  },
  {
    "level": 2218,
    "question": "819,275,650,704",
    "answer": "开怀大笑",
    "explain": "开怀大笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2219,
    "question": "2,531,232,411",
    "answer": "梁孟相敬",
    "explain": "梁孟相敬"
  },
  {
    "level": 2220,
    "question": "431,47,431,696",
    "answer": "止于至善",
    "explain": "止于至善"
  },
  {
    "level": 2221,
    "question": "8,163,554,245",
    "answer": "六合之内",
    "explain": "六合之内"
  },
  {
    "level": 2222,
    "question": "534,389,177,94",
    "answer": "今非昔比",
    "explain": "今非昔比"
  },
  {
    "level": 2223,
    "question": "77,101,32,176",
    "answer": "冰雪聪明",
    "explain": "冰雪聪明"
  },
  {
    "level": 2224,
    "question": "167,486,236,92",
    "answer": "生死离别",
    "explain": "生死离别"
  },
  {
    "level": 2225,
    "question": "389,389,120,3",
    "answer": "凤凰来仪",
    "explain": "凤凰来仪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2226,
    "question": "160,73,831,66",
    "answer": "智圆行方",
    "explain": "智圆行方"
  },
  {
    "level": 2227,
    "question": "45,722,476,722",
    "answer": "天知地知",
    "explain": "天知地知"
  },
  {
    "level": 2228,
    "question": "246,571,177,539",
    "answer": "返本朝元",
    "explain": "返本朝元"
  },
  {
    "level": 2229,
    "question": "89,183,111,458",
    "answer": "飞灾横祸",
    "explain": "飞灾横祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2230,
    "question": "389,278,431,652",
    "answer": "声罪致讨",
    "explain": "声罪致讨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2231,
    "question": "696,702,746,322",
    "answer": "山栖谷隐",
    "explain": "山栖谷隐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2232,
    "question": "426,426,495,391",
    "answer": "牙牙学语",
    "explain": "牙牙学语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2233,
    "question": "103,415,389,377",
    "answer": "杀猪宰羊",
    "explain": "杀猪宰羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 2234,
    "question": "502,69,210,298",
    "answer": "化做春风",
    "explain": "化做春风"
  },
  {
    "level": 2235,
    "question": "226,522,226,220",
    "answer": "戒骄戒操",
    "explain": "戒骄戒操"
  },
  {
    "level": 2236,
    "question": "313,171,38,501",
    "answer": "盈科后进",
    "explain": "盈科后进"
  },
  {
    "level": 2237,
    "question": "641,579,130,45",
    "answer": "食不重味",
    "explain": "食不重味"
  },
  {
    "level": 2238,
    "question": "278,821,213,832",
    "answer": "鹤唳华亭",
    "explain": "鹤唳华亭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2239,
    "question": "479,271,486,380",
    "answer": "怪诞诡奇",
    "explain": "怪诞诡奇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2240,
    "question": "821,831,3,431",
    "answer": "言行一致",
    "explain": "言行一致"
  },
  {
    "level": 2241,
    "question": "49,470,403,181",
    "answer": "失魂落魄",
    "explain": "失魂落魄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2242,
    "question": "10,5,188,6",
    "answer": "巴三览四",
    "explain": "巴三览四"
  },
  {
    "level": 2243,
    "question": "11,45,11,476",
    "answer": "九天九地",
    "explain": "九天九地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2244,
    "question": "47,479,298,5",
    "answer": "雨沐风餐",
    "explain": "雨沐风餐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2245,
    "question": "457,457,357,650",
    "answer": "步步登高",
    "explain": "步步登高"
  },
  {
    "level": 2246,
    "question": "205,147,482,812",
    "answer": "李郭仙舟",
    "explain": "李郭仙舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2247,
    "question": "45,66,175,271",
    "answer": "天方夜谭",
    "explain": "天方夜谭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2248,
    "question": "579,777,752,696",
    "answer": "不见泰山",
    "explain": "不见泰山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2249,
    "question": "3,743,486,182",
    "answer": "一潭死水",
    "explain": "一潭死水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2250,
    "question": "163,387,503,111",
    "answer": "合从连衡",
    "explain": "合从连衡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2251,
    "question": "171,641,554,304",
    "answer": "隔世之感",
    "explain": "隔世之感"
  },
  {
    "level": 2252,
    "question": "641,112,7,280",
    "answer": "事出无奈",
    "explain": "事出无奈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2253,
    "question": "555,236,831,650",
    "answer": "字里行间",
    "explain": "字里行间"
  },
  {
    "level": 2254,
    "question": "389,725,389,218",
    "answer": "非亲非故",
    "explain": "非亲非故"
  },
  {
    "level": 2255,
    "question": "752,696,276,146",
    "answer": "泰山北斗",
    "explain": "泰山北斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2256,
    "question": "562,230,369,352",
    "answer": "鼎成龙升",
    "explain": "鼎成龙升"
  },
  {
    "level": 2257,
    "question": "120,130,530,737",
    "answer": "来踪去迹",
    "explain": "来踪去迹"
  },
  {
    "level": 2258,
    "question": "599,579,426,167",
    "answer": "民不聊生",
    "explain": "民不聊生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2259,
    "question": "43,486,273,821",
    "answer": "日试万言",
    "explain": "日试万言"
  },
  {
    "level": 2260,
    "question": "182,147,696,276",
    "answer": "水过鸭背",
    "explain": "水过鸭背"
  },
  {
    "level": 2261,
    "question": "777,486,579,11",
    "answer": "见死不救",
    "explain": "见死不救"
  },
  {
    "level": 2262,
    "question": "398,391,73,389",
    "answer": "燕语莺声",
    "explain": "燕语莺声"
  },
  {
    "level": 2263,
    "question": "8,230,555,555",
    "answer": "流星岁月",
    "explain": "流星岁月"
  },
  {
    "level": 2264,
    "question": "182,101,555,369",
    "answer": "江东父老",
    "explain": "江东父老"
  },
  {
    "level": 2265,
    "question": "298,486,704,358",
    "answer": "风骨峭峻",
    "explain": "风骨峭峻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2266,
    "question": "831,389,7,641",
    "answer": "行若无事",
    "explain": "行若无事"
  },
  {
    "level": 2267,
    "question": "374,795,47,476",
    "answer": "香消玉殒",
    "explain": "香消玉殒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2268,
    "question": "460,480,69,555",
    "answer": "认贼作父",
    "explain": "认贼作父"
  },
  {
    "level": 2269,
    "question": "246,90,71,44",
    "answer": "翻手为云",
    "explain": "翻手为云"
  },
  {
    "level": 2270,
    "question": "342,324,579,209",
    "answer": "永垂不朽",
    "explain": "永垂不朽"
  },
  {
    "level": 2271,
    "question": "411,380,208,167",
    "answer": "荆棘丛生",
    "explain": "荆棘丛生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2272,
    "question": "82,482,842,382",
    "answer": "全神贯注",
    "explain": "全神贯注"
  },
  {
    "level": 2273,
    "question": "460,554,305,67",
    "answer": "人之常情",
    "explain": "人之常情"
  },
  {
    "level": 2274,
    "question": "93,77,280,233",
    "answer": "饮冰茹檗",
    "explain": "饮冰茹檗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2275,
    "question": "431,641,273,126",
    "answer": "碎尸万段",
    "explain": "碎尸万段"
  },
  {
    "level": 2276,
    "question": "431,641,339,236",
    "answer": "自食其力",
    "explain": "自食其力"
  },
  {
    "level": 2277,
    "question": "476,525,486,503",
    "answer": "痛入骨髓",
    "explain": "痛入骨髓"
  },
  {
    "level": 2278,
    "question": "381,226,389,167",
    "answer": "苟且偷生",
    "explain": "苟且偷生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2279,
    "question": "377,776,116,165",
    "answer": "养尊处优",
    "explain": "养尊处优"
  },
  {
    "level": 2280,
    "question": "3,6,579,125",
    "answer": "一丝不线",
    "explain": "一丝不线"
  },
  {
    "level": 2281,
    "question": "175,47,88,344",
    "answer": "夜雨对床",
    "explain": "夜雨对床"
  },
  {
    "level": 2282,
    "question": "87,176,370,563",
    "answer": "简明扼要",
    "explain": "简明扼要"
  },
  {
    "level": 2283,
    "question": "377,785,94,821",
    "answer": "扬长避短",
    "explain": "扬长避短"
  },
  {
    "level": 2284,
    "question": "176,232,579,374",
    "answer": "明教不变",
    "explain": "明教不变"
  },
  {
    "level": 2285,
    "question": "182,486,641,663",
    "answer": "水枯石烂",
    "explain": "水枯石烂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2286,
    "question": "109,479,143,382",
    "answer": "爱莫能助",
    "explain": "爱莫能助"
  },
  {
    "level": 2287,
    "question": "210,345,294,182",
    "answer": "清尘浊水",
    "explain": "清尘浊水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2288,
    "question": "69,821,147,831",
    "answer": "坐言起行",
    "explain": "坐言起行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2289,
    "question": "314,431,479,463",
    "answer": "细枝末节",
    "explain": "细枝末节"
  },
  {
    "level": 2290,
    "question": "368,389,381,86",
    "answer": "狐朋狗友",
    "explain": "狐朋狗友"
  },
  {
    "level": 2291,
    "question": "111,478,389,423",
    "answer": "横眉立目",
    "explain": "横眉立目"
  },
  {
    "level": 2292,
    "question": "245,336,620,753",
    "answer": "内外交困",
    "explain": "内外交困"
  },
  {
    "level": 2293,
    "question": "270,550,399,576",
    "answer": "满盘皆输",
    "explain": "满盘皆输"
  },
  {
    "level": 2294,
    "question": "438,423,87,182",
    "answer": "双瞳剪水",
    "explain": "双瞳剪水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2295,
    "question": "393,398,127,89",
    "answer": "乳燕初飞",
    "explain": "乳燕初飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2296,
    "question": "120,801,397,278",
    "answer": "下车泣罪",
    "explain": "下车泣罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2297,
    "question": "819,356,232,777",
    "answer": "开诚相见",
    "explain": "开诚相见"
  },
  {
    "level": 2298,
    "question": "305,45,7,820",
    "answer": "畅通无阻",
    "explain": "畅通无阻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2299,
    "question": "283,316,297,442",
    "answer": "单鹄寡凫",
    "explain": "单鹄寡凫"
  },
  {
    "level": 2300,
    "question": "3,167,71,2",
    "answer": "一枕黄梁",
    "explain": "一枕黄梁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2301,
    "question": "7,423,8,174",
    "answer": "五颜六色",
    "explain": "五颜六色"
  },
  {
    "level": 2302,
    "question": "182,8,125,380",
    "answer": "水流湍急",
    "explain": "水流湍急"
  },
  {
    "level": 2303,
    "question": "88,6,389,147",
    "answer": "退思补过",
    "explain": "退思补过"
  },
  {
    "level": 2304,
    "question": "423,579,761,562",
    "answer": "目不识丁",
    "explain": "目不识丁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2305,
    "question": "650,90,480,630",
    "answer": "高手如林",
    "explain": "高手如林"
  },
  {
    "level": 2306,
    "question": "380,6,43,3",
    "answer": "集思广议",
    "explain": "集思广议"
  },
  {
    "level": 2307,
    "question": "658,542,579,426",
    "answer": "萎靡不振",
    "explain": "萎靡不振"
  },
  {
    "level": 2308,
    "question": "45,179,641,647",
    "answer": "电光石火",
    "explain": "电光石火"
  },
  {
    "level": 2309,
    "question": "304,188,376,801",
    "answer": "共挽鹿车",
    "explain": "共挽鹿车"
  },
  {
    "level": 2310,
    "question": "431,165,431,799",
    "answer": "自由自在",
    "explain": "自由自在"
  },
  {
    "level": 2311,
    "question": "167,468,73,402",
    "answer": "深谋远虑",
    "explain": "深谋远虑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2312,
    "question": "3,326,3,278",
    "answer": "一琴一鹤",
    "explain": "一琴一鹤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2313,
    "question": "641,336,7,316",
    "answer": "十围五攻",
    "explain": "十围五攻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2314,
    "question": "435,821,435,391",
    "answer": "好言好语",
    "explain": "好言好语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2315,
    "question": "3,579,470,410",
    "answer": "义不取容",
    "explain": "义不取容"
  },
  {
    "level": 2316,
    "question": "339,785,479,380",
    "answer": "鞭长莫及",
    "explain": "鞭长莫及"
  },
  {
    "level": 2317,
    "question": "271,71,655,431",
    "answer": "叹为观止",
    "explain": "叹为观止"
  },
  {
    "level": 2318,
    "question": "460,696,460,182",
    "answer": "人山人海",
    "explain": "人山人海"
  },
  {
    "level": 2319,
    "question": "89,377,10,10",
    "answer": "飞扬跋扈",
    "explain": "飞扬跋扈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2320,
    "question": "298,47,476,812",
    "answer": "风雨同舟",
    "explain": "风雨同舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2321,
    "question": "785,554,650,812",
    "answer": "长篇大论",
    "explain": "长篇大论"
  },
  {
    "level": 2322,
    "question": "594,426,819,182",
    "answer": "信口开河",
    "explain": "信口开河"
  },
  {
    "level": 2323,
    "question": "502,460,38,380",
    "answer": "先人后己",
    "explain": "先人后己"
  },
  {
    "level": 2324,
    "question": "576,737,110,460",
    "answer": "暑气蒸人",
    "explain": "暑气蒸人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2325,
    "question": "696,641,344,460",
    "answer": "绝世佳人",
    "explain": "绝世佳人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2326,
    "question": "26,550,381,380",
    "answer": "杯盘狼藉",
    "explain": "杯盘狼藉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2327,
    "question": "460,270,305,389",
    "answer": "脑满肠肥",
    "explain": "脑满肠肥"
  },
  {
    "level": 2328,
    "question": "77,43,171,109",
    "answer": "冬日可爱",
    "explain": "冬日可爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2329,
    "question": "112,167,525,486",
    "answer": "出生入死",
    "explain": "出生入死"
  },
  {
    "level": 2330,
    "question": "734,279,304,746",
    "answer": "分甘共苦",
    "explain": "分甘共苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 2331,
    "question": "379,620,381,652",
    "answer": "鸡鸣狗盗",
    "explain": "鸡鸣狗盗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2332,
    "question": "3,313,829,163",
    "answer": "一拍即合",
    "explain": "一拍即合"
  },
  {
    "level": 2333,
    "question": "182,182,813,650",
    "answer": "水涨船高",
    "explain": "水涨船高"
  },
  {
    "level": 2334,
    "question": "110,799,503,44",
    "answer": "甲第连云",
    "explain": "甲第连云"
  },
  {
    "level": 2335,
    "question": "112,463,476,47",
    "answer": "础润而雨",
    "explain": "础润而雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2336,
    "question": "478,819,423,704",
    "answer": "眉开眼笑",
    "explain": "眉开眼笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2337,
    "question": "3,721,273,556",
    "answer": "遗臭万年",
    "explain": "遗臭万年"
  },
  {
    "level": 2338,
    "question": "6,579,171,270",
    "answer": "势不可当",
    "explain": "势不可当"
  },
  {
    "level": 2339,
    "question": "556,556,579,655",
    "answer": "念念不忘",
    "explain": "念念不忘"
  },
  {
    "level": 2340,
    "question": "179,37,269,38",
    "answer": "光前裕后",
    "explain": "光前裕后"
  },
  {
    "level": 2341,
    "question": "650,47,631,236",
    "answer": "大雨淋漓",
    "explain": "大雨淋漓"
  },
  {
    "level": 2342,
    "question": "379,620,476,147",
    "answer": "鸡鸣而起",
    "explain": "鸡鸣而起"
  },
  {
    "level": 2343,
    "question": "277,322,579,71",
    "answer": "何乐不为",
    "explain": "何乐不为"
  },
  {
    "level": 2344,
    "question": "2,91,431,651",
    "answer": "零打碎敲",
    "explain": "零打碎敲"
  },
  {
    "level": 2345,
    "question": "87,426,476,763",
    "answer": "切齿痛恨",
    "explain": "切齿痛恨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2346,
    "question": "94,165,486,391",
    "answer": "必有死鱼",
    "explain": "必有死鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2347,
    "question": "478,423,480,502",
    "answer": "眉目如画",
    "explain": "眉目如画"
  },
  {
    "level": 2348,
    "question": "110,460,7,349",
    "answer": "征敛无度",
    "explain": "征敛无度"
  },
  {
    "level": 2349,
    "question": "4,249,5,652",
    "answer": "两面三刀",
    "explain": "两面三刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 2350,
    "question": "641,457,66,219",
    "answer": "十步芳草",
    "explain": "十步芳草"
  },
  {
    "level": 2351,
    "question": "3,403,94,521",
    "answer": "一落千丈",
    "explain": "一落千丈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2352,
    "question": "147,174,45,374",
    "answer": "国色天香",
    "explain": "国色天香"
  },
  {
    "level": 2353,
    "question": "305,482,435,445",
    "answer": "常胜将军",
    "explain": "常胜将军"
  },
  {
    "level": 2354,
    "question": "71,380,6,323",
    "answer": "危机四伏",
    "explain": "危机四伏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2355,
    "question": "11,745,44,336",
    "answer": "九霄云外",
    "explain": "九霄云外"
  },
  {
    "level": 2356,
    "question": "242,167,641,283",
    "answer": "浑身是胆",
    "explain": "浑身是胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2357,
    "question": "799,7,246,461",
    "answer": "体无完肤",
    "explain": "体无完肤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2358,
    "question": "3,812,506,506",
    "answer": "议论纷纷",
    "explain": "议论纷纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2359,
    "question": "130,562,579,391",
    "answer": "忠贞不渝",
    "explain": "忠贞不渝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2360,
    "question": "71,380,423,486",
    "answer": "危急存亡",
    "explain": "危急存亡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2361,
    "question": "391,704,584,365",
    "answer": "语笑喧呼",
    "explain": "语笑喧呼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2362,
    "question": "641,147,624,579",
    "answer": "事过境迁",
    "explain": "事过境迁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2363,
    "question": "232,411,480,468",
    "answer": "相敬如宾",
    "explain": "相敬如宾"
  },
  {
    "level": 2364,
    "question": "161,3,402,380",
    "answer": "严以律己",
    "explain": "严以律己"
  },
  {
    "level": 2365,
    "question": "280,316,579,3",
    "answer": "贫贱不移",
    "explain": "贫贱不移"
  },
  {
    "level": 2366,
    "question": "135,579,380,451",
    "answer": "迫不及待",
    "explain": "迫不及待"
  },
  {
    "level": 2367,
    "question": "77,210,47,841",
    "answer": "冰清玉洁",
    "explain": "冰清玉洁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2368,
    "question": "457,363,247,641",
    "answer": "粗衣粝食",
    "explain": "粗衣粝食"
  },
  {
    "level": 2369,
    "question": "99,219,480,322",
    "answer": "绿草如茵",
    "explain": "绿草如茵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2370,
    "question": "6,45,10,495",
    "answer": "四通八达",
    "explain": "四通八达"
  },
  {
    "level": 2371,
    "question": "73,777,318,761",
    "answer": "远见卓识",
    "explain": "远见卓识"
  },
  {
    "level": 2372,
    "question": "476,11,45,785",
    "answer": "地久天长",
    "explain": "地久天长"
  },
  {
    "level": 2373,
    "question": "9,45,10,652",
    "answer": "七颠八倒",
    "explain": "七颠八倒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2374,
    "question": "389,310,380,478",
    "answer": "凤毛济美",
    "explain": "凤毛济美"
  },
  {
    "level": 2375,
    "question": "746,176,304,47",
    "answer": "沽名钓誉",
    "explain": "沽名钓誉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2376,
    "question": "302,460,554,478",
    "answer": "掠人之美",
    "explain": "掠人之美"
  },
  {
    "level": 2377,
    "question": "112,438,230,88",
    "answer": "出双成对",
    "explain": "出双成对"
  },
  {
    "level": 2378,
    "question": "423,162,554,398",
    "answer": "惊弓之鸟",
    "explain": "惊弓之鸟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2379,
    "question": "118,746,113,561",
    "answer": "左顾右盼",
    "explain": "左顾右盼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2380,
    "question": "3,138,130,330",
    "answer": "一傅众咻",
    "explain": "一傅众咻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2381,
    "question": "554,305,94,812",
    "answer": "此唱彼和",
    "explain": "此唱彼和"
  },
  {
    "level": 2382,
    "question": "101,801,554,560",
    "answer": "兵车之会",
    "explain": "兵车之会"
  },
  {
    "level": 2383,
    "question": "641,242,161,546",
    "answer": "食肉寝皮",
    "explain": "食肉寝皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2384,
    "question": "777,214,761,43",
    "answer": "见多识广",
    "explain": "见多识广"
  },
  {
    "level": 2385,
    "question": "651,787,11,3",
    "answer": "慷慨就义",
    "explain": "慷慨就义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2386,
    "question": "6,210,8,647",
    "answer": "四清六活",
    "explain": "四清六活"
  },
  {
    "level": 2387,
    "question": "109,109,232,129",
    "answer": "心心相印",
    "explain": "心心相印"
  },
  {
    "level": 2388,
    "question": "7,298,641,47",
    "answer": "五风十雨",
    "explain": "五风十雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2389,
    "question": "389,539,474,599",
    "answer": "费财劳民",
    "explain": "费财劳民"
  },
  {
    "level": 2390,
    "question": "752,298,479,376",
    "answer": "穷途末路",
    "explain": "穷途末路"
  },
  {
    "level": 2391,
    "question": "77,210,47,463",
    "answer": "冰清玉润",
    "explain": "冰清玉润"
  },
  {
    "level": 2392,
    "question": "493,336,641,460",
    "answer": "法外施仁",
    "explain": "法外施仁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2393,
    "question": "380,579,373,641",
    "answer": "饥不择食",
    "explain": "饥不择食"
  },
  {
    "level": 2394,
    "question": "283,650,109,314",
    "answer": "胆大心细",
    "explain": "胆大心细"
  },
  {
    "level": 2395,
    "question": "571,479,652,431",
    "answer": "本末倒置",
    "explain": "本末倒置"
  },
  {
    "level": 2396,
    "question": "3,821,11,562",
    "answer": "一言九鼎",
    "explain": "一言九鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2397,
    "question": "322,305,554,441",
    "answer": "乐昌之镜",
    "explain": "乐昌之镜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2398,
    "question": "734,423,94,314",
    "answer": "奴颜婢膝",
    "explain": "奴颜婢膝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2399,
    "question": "655,298,95,542",
    "answer": "望风披靡",
    "explain": "望风披靡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2400,
    "question": "812,550,403,112",
    "answer": "和盘托出",
    "explain": "和盘托出"
  },
  {
    "level": 2401,
    "question": "696,641,696,32",
    "answer": "善始善终",
    "explain": "善始善终"
  },
  {
    "level": 2402,
    "question": "486,207,5,45",
    "answer": "古树参天",
    "explain": "古树参天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2403,
    "question": "278,389,379,445",
    "answer": "鹤立鸡群",
    "explain": "鹤立鸡群"
  },
  {
    "level": 2404,
    "question": "490,389,490,174",
    "answer": "绘声绘色",
    "explain": "绘声绘色"
  },
  {
    "level": 2405,
    "question": "696,218,304,119",
    "answer": "雅俗共赏",
    "explain": "雅俗共赏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2406,
    "question": "502,110,71,2",
    "answer": "化整为零",
    "explain": "化整为零"
  },
  {
    "level": 2407,
    "question": "5,109,4,3",
    "answer": "三心二意",
    "explain": "三心二意"
  },
  {
    "level": 2408,
    "question": "49,746,72,819",
    "answer": "布鼓雷门",
    "explain": "布鼓雷门"
  },
  {
    "level": 2409,
    "question": "460,67,101,647",
    "answer": "人情冷暖",
    "explain": "人情冷暖"
  },
  {
    "level": 2410,
    "question": "503,4,700,5",
    "answer": "连二赶三",
    "explain": "连二赶三"
  },
  {
    "level": 2411,
    "question": "8,821,89,391",
    "answer": "流言飞语",
    "explain": "流言飞语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2412,
    "question": "230,460,470,3",
    "answer": "成仁取义",
    "explain": "成仁取义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2413,
    "question": "812,476,579,305",
    "answer": "和而不唱",
    "explain": "和而不唱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2414,
    "question": "423,3,812,5",
    "answer": "径一周三",
    "explain": "径一周三"
  },
  {
    "level": 2415,
    "question": "182,617,298,265",
    "answer": "浪静风恬",
    "explain": "浪静风恬"
  },
  {
    "level": 2416,
    "question": "431,49,220,734",
    "answer": "枝布叶分",
    "explain": "枝布叶分"
  },
  {
    "level": 2417,
    "question": "167,579,480,486",
    "answer": "生不如死",
    "explain": "生不如死"
  },
  {
    "level": 2418,
    "question": "481,94,453,426",
    "answer": "乖僻邪谬",
    "explain": "乖僻邪谬"
  },
  {
    "level": 2419,
    "question": "45,193,476,3",
    "answer": "天经地义",
    "explain": "天经地义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2420,
    "question": "407,371,768,648",
    "answer": "囫囵吞枣",
    "explain": "囫囵吞枣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2421,
    "question": "3,365,533,245",
    "answer": "一呼百诺",
    "explain": "一呼百诺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2422,
    "question": "434,434,785,162",
    "answer": "浩浩长空",
    "explain": "浩浩长空"
  },
  {
    "level": 2423,
    "question": "773,109,232,387",
    "answer": "降心相从",
    "explain": "降心相从"
  },
  {
    "level": 2424,
    "question": "584,213,175,463",
    "answer": "寒花晚节",
    "explain": "寒花晚节"
  },
  {
    "level": 2425,
    "question": "167,161,647,318",
    "answer": "生擒活捉",
    "explain": "生擒活捉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2426,
    "question": "182,652,120,230",
    "answer": "水到渠成",
    "explain": "水到渠成"
  },
  {
    "level": 2427,
    "question": "10,249,711,298",
    "answer": "八面威风",
    "explain": "八面威风"
  },
  {
    "level": 2428,
    "question": "94,374,273,502",
    "answer": "千变万化",
    "explain": "千变万化"
  },
  {
    "level": 2429,
    "question": "336,460,245,176",
    "answer": "外宽内明",
    "explain": "外宽内明"
  },
  {
    "level": 2430,
    "question": "106,426,47,754",
    "answer": "问道于盲",
    "explain": "问道于盲"
  },
  {
    "level": 2431,
    "question": "391,423,181,499",
    "answer": "鱼目混珠",
    "explain": "鱼目混珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 2432,
    "question": "3,752,4,36",
    "answer": "一穷二白",
    "explain": "一穷二白"
  },
  {
    "level": 2433,
    "question": "495,47,109,298",
    "answer": "血雨腥风",
    "explain": "血雨腥风"
  },
  {
    "level": 2434,
    "question": "457,579,112,344",
    "answer": "足不出户",
    "explain": "足不出户"
  },
  {
    "level": 2435,
    "question": "391,1,368,389",
    "answer": "鱼帛狐声",
    "explain": "鱼帛狐声"
  },
  {
    "level": 2436,
    "question": "35,389,249,641",
    "answer": "安若磐石",
    "explain": "安若磐石"
  },
  {
    "level": 2437,
    "question": "834,530,276,120",
    "answer": "南去北来",
    "explain": "南去北来"
  },
  {
    "level": 2438,
    "question": "44,173,423,262",
    "answer": "云雾缭绕",
    "explain": "云雾缭绕"
  },
  {
    "level": 2439,
    "question": "11,11,394,3",
    "answer": "九九归一",
    "explain": "九九归一"
  },
  {
    "level": 2440,
    "question": "6,249,466,322",
    "answer": "四面楚歌",
    "explain": "四面楚歌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2441,
    "question": "343,426,344,647",
    "answer": "家喻户晓",
    "explain": "家喻户晓"
  },
  {
    "level": 2442,
    "question": "389,322,389,256",
    "answer": "若隐若现",
    "explain": "若隐若现"
  },
  {
    "level": 2443,
    "question": "423,94,343,616",
    "answer": "金碧辉煌",
    "explain": "金碧辉煌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2444,
    "question": "506,43,43,43",
    "answer": "烈日炎炎",
    "explain": "烈日炎炎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2445,
    "question": "3,480,246,92",
    "answer": "易如翻掌",
    "explain": "易如翻掌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2446,
    "question": "617,480,116,461",
    "answer": "静如处女",
    "explain": "静如处女"
  },
  {
    "level": 2447,
    "question": "176,376,177,495",
    "answer": "夕阳西斜",
    "explain": "夕阳西斜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2448,
    "question": "314,112,655,336",
    "answer": "喜出望外",
    "explain": "喜出望外"
  },
  {
    "level": 2449,
    "question": "283,653,526,412",
    "answer": "单枪匹马",
    "explain": "单枪匹马"
  },
  {
    "level": 2450,
    "question": "476,821,6,147",
    "answer": "炊烟四起",
    "explain": "炊烟四起"
  },
  {
    "level": 2451,
    "question": "480,207,343,495",
    "answer": "如数家珍",
    "explain": "如数家珍"
  },
  {
    "level": 2452,
    "question": "426,74,426,36",
    "answer": "说黑道白",
    "explain": "说黑道白"
  },
  {
    "level": 2453,
    "question": "3,492,232,376",
    "answer": "以沫相濡",
    "explain": "以沫相濡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2454,
    "question": "94,831,369,373",
    "answer": "笔走龙蛇",
    "explain": "笔走龙蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2455,
    "question": "746,130,69,322",
    "answer": "苦中作乐",
    "explain": "苦中作乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2456,
    "question": "6,480,135,457",
    "answer": "势如破竹",
    "explain": "势如破竹"
  },
  {
    "level": 2457,
    "question": "369,469,389,620",
    "answer": "龙跃凤鸣",
    "explain": "龙跃凤鸣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2458,
    "question": "3,772,230,176",
    "answer": "一举成名",
    "explain": "一举成名"
  },
  {
    "level": 2459,
    "question": "641,271,641,392",
    "answer": "使贪使愚",
    "explain": "使贪使愚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2460,
    "question": "696,165,376,94",
    "answer": "山幽路辟",
    "explain": "山幽路辟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2461,
    "question": "381,412,554,474",
    "answer": "犬马之劳",
    "explain": "犬马之劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2462,
    "question": "242,280,651,491",
    "answer": "柔茹刚吐",
    "explain": "柔茹刚吐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2463,
    "question": "369,744,365,469",
    "answer": "龙腾虎跃",
    "explain": "龙腾虎跃"
  },
  {
    "level": 2464,
    "question": "785,470,431,525",
    "answer": "长驱直入",
    "explain": "长驱直入"
  },
  {
    "level": 2465,
    "question": "5,746,409,525",
    "answer": "三顾茅庐",
    "explain": "三顾茅庐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2466,
    "question": "398,391,213,374",
    "answer": "鸟语花香",
    "explain": "鸟语花香"
  },
  {
    "level": 2467,
    "question": "210,833,47,525",
    "answer": "青翠欲滴",
    "explain": "青翠欲滴"
  },
  {
    "level": 2468,
    "question": "324,821,5,565",
    "answer": "垂涎三尺",
    "explain": "垂涎三尺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2469,
    "question": "480,831,501,77",
    "answer": "如履薄冰",
    "explain": "如履薄冰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2470,
    "question": "545,112,273,82",
    "answer": "计出万全",
    "explain": "计出万全"
  },
  {
    "level": 2471,
    "question": "786,786,171,171",
    "answer": "战战兢兢",
    "explain": "战战兢兢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2472,
    "question": "222,174,280,734",
    "answer": "秋色平分",
    "explain": "秋色平分"
  },
  {
    "level": 2473,
    "question": "641,336,237,73",
    "answer": "世外桃源",
    "explain": "世外桃源"
  },
  {
    "level": 2474,
    "question": "3,7,641,116",
    "answer": "一无是处",
    "explain": "一无是处"
  },
  {
    "level": 2475,
    "question": "493,207,408,435",
    "answer": "发愤图强",
    "explain": "发愤图强"
  },
  {
    "level": 2476,
    "question": "641,310,770,491",
    "answer": "食毛践土",
    "explain": "食毛践土"
  },
  {
    "level": 2477,
    "question": "579,722,339,4",
    "answer": "不知其二",
    "explain": "不知其二"
  },
  {
    "level": 2478,
    "question": "36,460,226,369",
    "answer": "白头偕老",
    "explain": "白头偕老"
  },
  {
    "level": 2479,
    "question": "25,463,576,576",
    "answer": "折节读书",
    "explain": "折节读书"
  },
  {
    "level": 2480,
    "question": "87,3,147,304",
    "answer": "坚毅果敢",
    "explain": "坚毅果敢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2481,
    "question": "162,230,579,772",
    "answer": "功成不居",
    "explain": "功成不居"
  },
  {
    "level": 2482,
    "question": "47,460,66,248",
    "answer": "与人方便",
    "explain": "与人方便"
  },
  {
    "level": 2483,
    "question": "182,641,696,522",
    "answer": "海誓山盟",
    "explain": "海誓山盟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2484,
    "question": "218,700,67,167",
    "answer": "故剑情深",
    "explain": "故剑情深"
  },
  {
    "level": 2485,
    "question": "714,236,714,336",
    "answer": "彻里彻外",
    "explain": "彻里彻外"
  },
  {
    "level": 2486,
    "question": "67,380,160,167",
    "answer": "情急智生",
    "explain": "情急智生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2487,
    "question": "841,641,554,652",
    "answer": "稀世之宝",
    "explain": "稀世之宝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2488,
    "question": "131,271,579,193",
    "answer": "荒诞不经",
    "explain": "荒诞不经"
  },
  {
    "level": 2489,
    "question": "412,323,227,641",
    "answer": "马革裹尸",
    "explain": "马革裹尸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2490,
    "question": "169,120,554,7",
    "answer": "傥来之物",
    "explain": "傥来之物"
  },
  {
    "level": 2491,
    "question": "77,470,101,181",
    "answer": "冰魂雪魄",
    "explain": "冰魂雪魄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2492,
    "question": "773,423,560,482",
    "answer": "聚精会神",
    "explain": "聚精会神"
  },
  {
    "level": 2493,
    "question": "579,171,214,170",
    "answer": "不可多得",
    "explain": "不可多得"
  },
  {
    "level": 2494,
    "question": "37,162,161,737",
    "answer": "前功尽弃",
    "explain": "前功尽弃"
  },
  {
    "level": 2495,
    "question": "89,821,8,785",
    "answer": "飞短流长",
    "explain": "飞短流长"
  },
  {
    "level": 2496,
    "question": "3,423,641,831",
    "answer": "一目十行",
    "explain": "一目十行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2497,
    "question": "88,650,480,8",
    "answer": "对答如流",
    "explain": "对答如流"
  },
  {
    "level": 2498,
    "question": "486,433,480,436",
    "answer": "骨瘦如柴",
    "explain": "骨瘦如柴"
  },
  {
    "level": 2499,
    "question": "565,439,648,205",
    "answer": "张王赵李",
    "explain": "张王赵李"
  },
  {
    "level": 2500,
    "question": "641,32,579,391",
    "answer": "始终不渝",
    "explain": "始终不渝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2501,
    "question": "119,831,120,704",
    "answer": "上行下效",
    "explain": "上行下效"
  },
  {
    "level": 2502,
    "question": "7,628,579,165",
    "answer": "无所不有",
    "explain": "无所不有"
  },
  {
    "level": 2503,
    "question": "380,495,3,652",
    "answer": "奇珍异宝",
    "explain": "奇珍异宝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2504,
    "question": "772,463,116,78",
    "answer": "屈节辱命",
    "explain": "屈节辱命"
  },
  {
    "level": 2505,
    "question": "565,298,460,121",
    "answer": "藏锋敛锐",
    "explain": "藏锋敛锐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2506,
    "question": "374,424,554,120",
    "answer": "香铒之下",
    "explain": "香铒之下"
  },
  {
    "level": 2507,
    "question": "130,365,394,696",
    "answer": "纵虎归山",
    "explain": "纵虎归山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2508,
    "question": "10,92,554,620",
    "answer": "八拜之交",
    "explain": "八拜之交"
  },
  {
    "level": 2509,
    "question": "3,567,630,630",
    "answer": "仪表堂堂",
    "explain": "仪表堂堂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2510,
    "question": "481,92,426,620",
    "answer": "昂首嘶鸣",
    "explain": "昂首嘶鸣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2511,
    "question": "6,734,7,506",
    "answer": "四分五裂",
    "explain": "四分五裂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2512,
    "question": "167,336,247,175",
    "answer": "深更半夜",
    "explain": "深更半夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2513,
    "question": "380,380,3,630",
    "answer": "济济一堂",
    "explain": "济济一堂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2514,
    "question": "6,289,493,539",
    "answer": "四季发财",
    "explain": "四季发财"
  },
  {
    "level": 2515,
    "question": "641,819,110,478",
    "answer": "释回增美",
    "explain": "释回增美"
  },
  {
    "level": 2516,
    "question": "147,165,579,380",
    "answer": "过犹不及",
    "explain": "过犹不及"
  },
  {
    "level": 2517,
    "question": "259,821,267,391",
    "answer": "甜言蜜语",
    "explain": "甜言蜜语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2518,
    "question": "11,486,3,167",
    "answer": "九死一生",
    "explain": "九死一生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2519,
    "question": "391,130,67,167",
    "answer": "语重情深",
    "explain": "语重情深"
  },
  {
    "level": 2520,
    "question": "343,135,460,486",
    "answer": "家破人亡",
    "explain": "家破人亡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2521,
    "question": "109,90,232,312",
    "answer": "心手相应",
    "explain": "心手相应"
  },
  {
    "level": 2522,
    "question": "423,162,3,87",
    "answer": "目空一切",
    "explain": "目空一切"
  },
  {
    "level": 2523,
    "question": "43,313,177,495",
    "answer": "日影西斜",
    "explain": "日影西斜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2524,
    "question": "3,767,3,375",
    "answer": "一模一样",
    "explain": "一模一样"
  },
  {
    "level": 2525,
    "question": "773,369,323,365",
    "answer": "降龙伏虎",
    "explain": "降龙伏虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2526,
    "question": "210,696,480,704",
    "answer": "春山如笑",
    "explain": "春山如笑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2527,
    "question": "47,431,7,270",
    "answer": "玉卮无当",
    "explain": "玉卮无当"
  },
  {
    "level": 2528,
    "question": "3,641,4,398",
    "answer": "一石二鸟",
    "explain": "一石二鸟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2529,
    "question": "88,5,820,6",
    "answer": "推三阻四",
    "explain": "推三阻四"
  },
  {
    "level": 2530,
    "question": "180,522,111,162",
    "answer": "彩桥横空",
    "explain": "彩桥横空"
  },
  {
    "level": 2531,
    "question": "433,424,611,146",
    "answer": "抓耳挠腮",
    "explain": "抓耳挠腮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2532,
    "question": "426,785,426,821",
    "answer": "说长道短",
    "explain": "说长道短"
  },
  {
    "level": 2533,
    "question": "431,650,737,377",
    "answer": "趾高气扬",
    "explain": "趾高气扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 2534,
    "question": "650,91,112,90",
    "answer": "大打出手",
    "explain": "大打出手"
  },
  {
    "level": 2535,
    "question": "423,554,94,236",
    "answer": "缪之千里",
    "explain": "缪之千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 2536,
    "question": "112,380,431,482",
    "answer": "出奇制胜",
    "explain": "出奇制胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2537,
    "question": "43,11,555,167",
    "answer": "日久岁深",
    "explain": "日久岁深"
  },
  {
    "level": 2538,
    "question": "819,109,777,356",
    "answer": "开心见诚",
    "explain": "开心见诚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2539,
    "question": "165,97,7,469",
    "answer": "有备无患",
    "explain": "有备无患"
  },
  {
    "level": 2540,
    "question": "109,109,556,556",
    "answer": "心心念念",
    "explain": "心心念念"
  },
  {
    "level": 2541,
    "question": "424,424,10,66",
    "answer": "耳听八方",
    "explain": "耳听八方"
  },
  {
    "level": 2542,
    "question": "423,641,71,819",
    "answer": "金石为开",
    "explain": "金石为开"
  },
  {
    "level": 2543,
    "question": "460,389,584,585",
    "answer": "人声喧哗",
    "explain": "人声喧哗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2544,
    "question": "327,90,171,170",
    "answer": "唾手可得",
    "explain": "唾手可得"
  },
  {
    "level": 2545,
    "question": "112,435,525,232",
    "answer": "出将入相",
    "explain": "出将入相"
  },
  {
    "level": 2546,
    "question": "394,831,394,457",
    "answer": "规行矩步",
    "explain": "规行矩步"
  },
  {
    "level": 2547,
    "question": "69,411,655,45",
    "answer": "坐井观天",
    "explain": "坐井观天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2548,
    "question": "409,423,423,179",
    "answer": "鼠目寸光",
    "explain": "鼠目寸光"
  },
  {
    "level": 2549,
    "question": "460,161,339,436",
    "answer": "人尽其才",
    "explain": "人尽其才"
  },
  {
    "level": 2550,
    "question": "630,280,737,641",
    "answer": "矜平躁释",
    "explain": "矜平躁释"
  },
  {
    "level": 2551,
    "question": "92,415,451,367",
    "answer": "守株待兔",
    "explain": "守株待兔"
  },
  {
    "level": 2552,
    "question": "435,460,628,471",
    "answer": "强人所难",
    "explain": "强人所难"
  },
  {
    "level": 2553,
    "question": "176,368,434,426",
    "answer": "明眸皓齿",
    "explain": "明眸皓齿"
  },
  {
    "level": 2554,
    "question": "71,538,579,460",
    "answer": "为富不仁",
    "explain": "为富不仁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2555,
    "question": "647,576,838,525",
    "answer": "焚书坑儒",
    "explain": "焚书坑儒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2556,
    "question": "248,248,579,696",
    "answer": "绵绵不绝",
    "explain": "绵绵不绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2557,
    "question": "329,336,554,322",
    "answer": "弦外之音",
    "explain": "弦外之音"
  },
  {
    "level": 2558,
    "question": "3,617,476,162",
    "answer": "一扫而空",
    "explain": "一扫而空"
  },
  {
    "level": 2559,
    "question": "340,380,455,641",
    "answer": "干卿底事",
    "explain": "干卿底事"
  },
  {
    "level": 2560,
    "question": "336,242,130,651",
    "answer": "外柔中刚",
    "explain": "外柔中刚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2561,
    "question": "739,389,207,379",
    "answer": "呆若木鸡",
    "explain": "呆若木鸡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2562,
    "question": "9,457,554,436",
    "answer": "七步之才",
    "explain": "七步之才"
  },
  {
    "level": 2563,
    "question": "5,232,11,8",
    "answer": "三教九流",
    "explain": "三教九流"
  },
  {
    "level": 2564,
    "question": "403,403,650,66",
    "answer": "落落大方",
    "explain": "落落大方"
  },
  {
    "level": 2565,
    "question": "424,525,44,45",
    "answer": "耸入云天",
    "explain": "耸入云天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2566,
    "question": "502,653,38,831",
    "answer": "先斩后奏",
    "explain": "先斩后奏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2567,
    "question": "322,92,352,280",
    "answer": "歌舞升平",
    "explain": "歌舞升平"
  },
  {
    "level": 2568,
    "question": "3,722,247,461",
    "answer": "一知半解",
    "explain": "一知半解"
  },
  {
    "level": 2569,
    "question": "394,412,66,363",
    "answer": "归马放牛",
    "explain": "归马放牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2570,
    "question": "389,174,470,528",
    "answer": "声色俱厉",
    "explain": "声色俱厉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2571,
    "question": "307,495,214,436",
    "answer": "博学多才",
    "explain": "博学多才"
  },
  {
    "level": 2572,
    "question": "426,5,426,6",
    "answer": "说三道四",
    "explain": "说三道四"
  },
  {
    "level": 2573,
    "question": "3,495,567,161",
    "answer": "义正词严",
    "explain": "义正词严"
  },
  {
    "level": 2574,
    "question": "463,344,463,167",
    "answer": "润屋润身",
    "explain": "润屋润身"
  },
  {
    "level": 2575,
    "question": "3,423,188,423",
    "answer": "以眼还眼",
    "explain": "以眼还眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2576,
    "question": "82,130,45,476",
    "answer": "壶中天地",
    "explain": "壶中天地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2577,
    "question": "210,179,176,49",
    "answer": "春光明媚",
    "explain": "春光明媚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2578,
    "question": "5,336,247,175",
    "answer": "三更半夜",
    "explain": "三更半夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2579,
    "question": "176,653,3,403",
    "answer": "明枪易躲",
    "explain": "明枪易躲"
  },
  {
    "level": 2580,
    "question": "431,435,579,314",
    "answer": "自强不息",
    "explain": "自强不息"
  },
  {
    "level": 2581,
    "question": "821,94,165,130",
    "answer": "言必有中",
    "explain": "言必有中"
  },
  {
    "level": 2582,
    "question": "130,447,554,426",
    "answer": "中庸之道",
    "explain": "中庸之道"
  },
  {
    "level": 2583,
    "question": "441,73,94,163",
    "answer": "镜圆璧合",
    "explain": "镜圆璧合"
  },
  {
    "level": 2584,
    "question": "67,579,431,161",
    "answer": "情不自禁",
    "explain": "情不自禁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2585,
    "question": "336,66,245,73",
    "answer": "外方内圆",
    "explain": "外方内圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2586,
    "question": "270,69,298,167",
    "answer": "满座风生",
    "explain": "满座风生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2587,
    "question": "249,579,281,174",
    "answer": "面不改色",
    "explain": "面不改色"
  },
  {
    "level": 2588,
    "question": "799,628,579,177",
    "answer": "在所不惜",
    "explain": "在所不惜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2589,
    "question": "432,176,47,177",
    "answer": "争名于朝",
    "explain": "争名于朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2590,
    "question": "307,641,380,130",
    "answer": "博施济众",
    "explain": "博施济众"
  },
  {
    "level": 2591,
    "question": "486,476,38,3",
    "answer": "死而后已",
    "explain": "死而后已"
  },
  {
    "level": 2592,
    "question": "182,476,819,460",
    "answer": "浪子回头",
    "explain": "浪子回头"
  },
  {
    "level": 2593,
    "question": "94,696,273,182",
    "answer": "千山万水",
    "explain": "千山万水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2594,
    "question": "821,821,431,314",
    "answer": "沾沾自喜",
    "explain": "沾沾自喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2595,
    "question": "562,3,173,4",
    "answer": "丁一确二",
    "explain": "丁一确二"
  },
  {
    "level": 2596,
    "question": "120,369,530,218",
    "answer": "来龙去脉",
    "explain": "来龙去脉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2597,
    "question": "737,130,745,720",
    "answer": "气冲霄汉",
    "explain": "气冲霄汉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2598,
    "question": "648,359,389,179",
    "answer": "凿壁偷光",
    "explain": "凿壁偷光"
  },
  {
    "level": 2599,
    "question": "87,577,75,305",
    "answer": "浅斟低唱",
    "explain": "浅斟低唱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2600,
    "question": "219,819,460,78",
    "answer": "草菅人命",
    "explain": "草菅人命"
  },
  {
    "level": 2601,
    "question": "167,579,298,672",
    "answer": "生不逢时",
    "explain": "生不逢时"
  },
  {
    "level": 2602,
    "question": "273,236,7,44",
    "answer": "万里无云",
    "explain": "万里无云"
  },
  {
    "level": 2603,
    "question": "599,431,599,650",
    "answer": "民脂民膏",
    "explain": "民脂民膏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2604,
    "question": "179,176,72,403",
    "answer": "光明磊落",
    "explain": "光明磊落"
  },
  {
    "level": 2605,
    "question": "207,411,501,647",
    "answer": "束请缊火",
    "explain": "束请缊火"
  },
  {
    "level": 2606,
    "question": "218,69,650,167",
    "answer": "故作高深",
    "explain": "故作高深"
  },
  {
    "level": 2607,
    "question": "434,130,480,696",
    "answer": "恩重如山",
    "explain": "恩重如山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2608,
    "question": "533,556,579,525",
    "answer": "百年不遇",
    "explain": "百年不遇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2609,
    "question": "256,821,431,391",
    "answer": "闲言碎语",
    "explain": "闲言碎语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2610,
    "question": "753,469,5,533",
    "answer": "雀跃三百",
    "explain": "雀跃三百"
  },
  {
    "level": 2611,
    "question": "90,579,641,381",
    "answer": "手不释卷",
    "explain": "手不释卷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2612,
    "question": "533,25,579,819",
    "answer": "百折不回",
    "explain": "百折不回"
  },
  {
    "level": 2613,
    "question": "352,696,436,499",
    "answer": "升山采珠",
    "explain": "升山采珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 2614,
    "question": "480,43,130,45",
    "answer": "如日中天",
    "explain": "如日中天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2615,
    "question": "3,423,476,460",
    "answer": "一视同仁",
    "explain": "一视同仁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2616,
    "question": "167,369,647,365",
    "answer": "生龙活虎",
    "explain": "生龙活虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2617,
    "question": "394,495,246,49",
    "answer": "归真反璞",
    "explain": "归真反璞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2618,
    "question": "711,650,579,651",
    "answer": "尾大不掉",
    "explain": "尾大不掉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2619,
    "question": "130,426,471,304",
    "answer": "众口难调",
    "explain": "众口难调"
  },
  {
    "level": 2620,
    "question": "777,378,722,382",
    "answer": "见微知著",
    "explain": "见微知著"
  },
  {
    "level": 2621,
    "question": "620,233,819,426",
    "answer": "鸣锣开道",
    "explain": "鸣锣开道"
  },
  {
    "level": 2622,
    "question": "167,543,533,97",
    "answer": "身价百倍",
    "explain": "身价百倍"
  },
  {
    "level": 2623,
    "question": "373,380,71,460",
    "answer": "舍己为人",
    "explain": "舍己为人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2624,
    "question": "94,380,533,479",
    "answer": "千奇百怪",
    "explain": "千奇百怪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2625,
    "question": "628,384,171,226",
    "answer": "所向克捷",
    "explain": "所向克捷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2626,
    "question": "5,8,11,519",
    "answer": "三六九等",
    "explain": "三六九等"
  },
  {
    "level": 2627,
    "question": "559,423,480,491",
    "answer": "挥金如土",
    "explain": "挥金如土"
  },
  {
    "level": 2628,
    "question": "3,777,480,218",
    "answer": "一见如故",
    "explain": "一见如故"
  },
  {
    "level": 2629,
    "question": "94,523,273,92",
    "answer": "千差万别",
    "explain": "千差万别"
  },
  {
    "level": 2630,
    "question": "265,579,722,431",
    "answer": "恬不知耻",
    "explain": "恬不知耻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2631,
    "question": "647,109,305,283",
    "answer": "卧薪尝胆",
    "explain": "卧薪尝胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2632,
    "question": "463,363,629,641",
    "answer": "节衣缩食",
    "explain": "节衣缩食"
  },
  {
    "level": 2633,
    "question": "721,389,271,737",
    "answer": "唉声叹气",
    "explain": "唉声叹气"
  },
  {
    "level": 2634,
    "question": "389,829,389,236",
    "answer": "若即若离",
    "explain": "若即若离"
  },
  {
    "level": 2635,
    "question": "641,556,207,207",
    "answer": "十年树木",
    "explain": "十年树木"
  },
  {
    "level": 2636,
    "question": "3,109,3,3",
    "answer": "一心一意",
    "explain": "一心一意"
  },
  {
    "level": 2637,
    "question": "562,457,476,5",
    "answer": "鼎足而三",
    "explain": "鼎足而三"
  },
  {
    "level": 2638,
    "question": "344,176,579,617",
    "answer": "窗明几静",
    "explain": "窗明几静"
  },
  {
    "level": 2639,
    "question": "67,563,127,819",
    "answer": "情窦初开",
    "explain": "情窦初开"
  },
  {
    "level": 2640,
    "question": "103,403,165,431",
    "answer": "错落有致",
    "explain": "错落有致"
  },
  {
    "level": 2641,
    "question": "176,296,641,389",
    "answer": "明辨是非",
    "explain": "明辨是非"
  },
  {
    "level": 2642,
    "question": "480,43,66,352",
    "answer": "如日方升",
    "explain": "如日方升"
  },
  {
    "level": 2643,
    "question": "94,423,542,486",
    "answer": "千金买骨",
    "explain": "千金买骨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2644,
    "question": "298,47,480,120",
    "answer": "风雨如晦",
    "explain": "风雨如晦"
  },
  {
    "level": 2645,
    "question": "343,408,6,359",
    "answer": "家徒四壁",
    "explain": "家徒四壁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2646,
    "question": "821,90,600,655",
    "answer": "袖手傍观",
    "explain": "袖手傍观"
  },
  {
    "level": 2647,
    "question": "628,384,95,542",
    "answer": "所向披靡",
    "explain": "所向披靡"
  },
  {
    "level": 2648,
    "question": "182,647,7,67",
    "answer": "水火无情",
    "explain": "水火无情"
  },
  {
    "level": 2649,
    "question": "213,821,522,391",
    "answer": "花言巧语",
    "explain": "花言巧语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2650,
    "question": "479,432,433,92",
    "answer": "摩拳擦掌",
    "explain": "摩拳擦掌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2651,
    "question": "525,182,579,355",
    "answer": "滴水不漏",
    "explain": "滴水不漏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2652,
    "question": "363,310,314,47",
    "answer": "牛毛细雨",
    "explain": "牛毛细雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2653,
    "question": "435,545,11,545",
    "answer": "将计就计",
    "explain": "将计就计"
  },
  {
    "level": 2654,
    "question": "367,738,167,482",
    "answer": "涂炭生灵",
    "explain": "涂炭生灵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2655,
    "question": "167,478,486,501",
    "answer": "生荣死哀",
    "explain": "生荣死哀"
  },
  {
    "level": 2656,
    "question": "3,207,45,734",
    "answer": "义愤填胸",
    "explain": "义愤填胸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2657,
    "question": "3,533,367,476",
    "answer": "一败涂地",
    "explain": "一败涂地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2658,
    "question": "533,493,533,130",
    "answer": "百发百中",
    "explain": "百发百中"
  },
  {
    "level": 2659,
    "question": "650,47,411,82",
    "answer": "大雨倾盆",
    "explain": "大雨倾盆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2660,
    "question": "312,799,579,120",
    "answer": "应接不暇",
    "explain": "应接不暇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2661,
    "question": "752,696,370,182",
    "answer": "穷山恶水",
    "explain": "穷山恶水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2662,
    "question": "67,319,3,812",
    "answer": "情投意和",
    "explain": "情投意和"
  },
  {
    "level": 2663,
    "question": "45,495,492,633",
    "answer": "通达谙练",
    "explain": "通达谙练"
  },
  {
    "level": 2664,
    "question": "560,343,579,769",
    "answer": "会家不忙",
    "explain": "会家不忙"
  },
  {
    "level": 2665,
    "question": "7,3,746,773",
    "answer": "物以类聚",
    "explain": "物以类聚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2666,
    "question": "478,89,174,92",
    "answer": "眉飞色舞",
    "explain": "眉飞色舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2667,
    "question": "210,174,270,73",
    "answer": "春色满圆",
    "explain": "春色满圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2668,
    "question": "373,167,116,476",
    "answer": "设身处地",
    "explain": "设身处地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2669,
    "question": "213,172,5,457",
    "answer": "华封三足",
    "explain": "华封三足"
  },
  {
    "level": 2670,
    "question": "170,426,214,382",
    "answer": "得道多助",
    "explain": "得道多助"
  },
  {
    "level": 2671,
    "question": "650,392,554,476",
    "answer": "膏腴之地",
    "explain": "膏腴之地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2672,
    "question": "377,423,362,121",
    "answer": "养精畜锐",
    "explain": "养精畜锐"
  },
  {
    "level": 2673,
    "question": "276,45,202,460",
    "answer": "悲天悯人",
    "explain": "悲天悯人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2674,
    "question": "47,10,579,143",
    "answer": "欲罢不能",
    "explain": "欲罢不能"
  },
  {
    "level": 2675,
    "question": "481,752,533,112",
    "answer": "丑态百出",
    "explain": "丑态百出"
  },
  {
    "level": 2676,
    "question": "94,236,489,489",
    "answer": "千里迢迢",
    "explain": "千里迢迢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2677,
    "question": "35,772,322,93",
    "answer": "安居乐业",
    "explain": "安居乐业"
  },
  {
    "level": 2678,
    "question": "44,819,173,641",
    "answer": "云开雾释",
    "explain": "云开雾释"
  },
  {
    "level": 2679,
    "question": "71,599,411,78",
    "answer": "为民请命",
    "explain": "为民请命"
  },
  {
    "level": 2680,
    "question": "426,426,389,389",
    "answer": "口口声声",
    "explain": "口口声声"
  },
  {
    "level": 2681,
    "question": "434,92,752,193",
    "answer": "皓首穷经",
    "explain": "皓首穷经"
  },
  {
    "level": 2682,
    "question": "499,503,359,163",
    "answer": "珠连壁合",
    "explain": "珠连壁合"
  },
  {
    "level": 2683,
    "question": "71,450,110,167",
    "answer": "黄袍加身",
    "explain": "黄袍加身"
  },
  {
    "level": 2684,
    "question": "460,3,380,533",
    "answer": "人一己百",
    "explain": "人一己百"
  },
  {
    "level": 2685,
    "question": "821,101,232,799",
    "answer": "短兵相接",
    "explain": "短兵相接"
  },
  {
    "level": 2686,
    "question": "486,737,495,495",
    "answer": "死气沉沉",
    "explain": "死气沉沉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2687,
    "question": "325,161,73,696",
    "answer": "弹尽援绝",
    "explain": "弹尽援绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2688,
    "question": "432,734,281,33",
    "answer": "争分夺秒",
    "explain": "争分夺秒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2689,
    "question": "482,317,26,496",
    "answer": "灵丹妙药",
    "explain": "灵丹妙药"
  },
  {
    "level": 2690,
    "question": "336,641,32,43",
    "answer": "饱食终日",
    "explain": "饱食终日"
  },
  {
    "level": 2691,
    "question": "162,501,696,3",
    "answer": "功薄蝉翼",
    "explain": "功薄蝉翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2692,
    "question": "486,165,47,746",
    "answer": "死有余辜",
    "explain": "死有余辜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2693,
    "question": "374,213,789,377",
    "answer": "香花供养",
    "explain": "香花供养"
  },
  {
    "level": 2694,
    "question": "363,579,246,436",
    "answer": "衣不完采",
    "explain": "衣不完采"
  },
  {
    "level": 2695,
    "question": "109,579,4,342",
    "answer": "心不二用",
    "explain": "心不二用"
  },
  {
    "level": 2696,
    "question": "408,397,71,82",
    "answer": "社稷为墟",
    "explain": "社稷为墟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2697,
    "question": "474,398,734,89",
    "answer": "劳燕分飞",
    "explain": "劳燕分飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2698,
    "question": "275,94,339,278",
    "answer": "怀璧其罪",
    "explain": "怀璧其罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2699,
    "question": "737,130,363,146",
    "answer": "气冲牛斗",
    "explain": "气冲牛斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2700,
    "question": "398,298,232,432",
    "answer": "鹬蚌相争",
    "explain": "鹬蚌相争"
  },
  {
    "level": 2701,
    "question": "620,460,799,424",
    "answer": "交头接耳",
    "explain": "交头接耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2702,
    "question": "655,269,248,246",
    "answer": "看菜吃饭",
    "explain": "看菜吃饭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2703,
    "question": "97,43,262,831",
    "answer": "倍日并行",
    "explain": "倍日并行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2704,
    "question": "4,460,476,109",
    "answer": "二人同心",
    "explain": "二人同心"
  },
  {
    "level": 2705,
    "question": "94,162,480,821",
    "answer": "碧空如洗",
    "explain": "碧空如洗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2706,
    "question": "5,786,387,4",
    "answer": "三占从二",
    "explain": "三占从二"
  },
  {
    "level": 2707,
    "question": "647,161,109,600",
    "answer": "火尽薪传",
    "explain": "火尽薪传"
  },
  {
    "level": 2708,
    "question": "314,641,776,460",
    "answer": "息事宁人",
    "explain": "息事宁人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2709,
    "question": "365,276,419,496",
    "answer": "虎背熊腰",
    "explain": "虎背熊腰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2710,
    "question": "496,460,193,460",
    "answer": "摇头晃脑",
    "explain": "摇头晃脑"
  },
  {
    "level": 2711,
    "question": "366,460,409,812",
    "answer": "抱头鼠窜",
    "explain": "抱头鼠窜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2712,
    "question": "76,94,423,161",
    "answer": "裘弊金尽",
    "explain": "裘弊金尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 2713,
    "question": "379,381,352,45",
    "answer": "鸡犬升天",
    "explain": "鸡犬升天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2714,
    "question": "304,298,478,555",
    "answer": "调风弄月",
    "explain": "调风弄月"
  },
  {
    "level": 2715,
    "question": "170,528,3,565",
    "answer": "得礼一尺",
    "explain": "得礼一尺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2716,
    "question": "533,294,451,772",
    "answer": "百端待举",
    "explain": "百端待举"
  },
  {
    "level": 2717,
    "question": "431,542,258,47",
    "answer": "碎琼乱玉",
    "explain": "碎琼乱玉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2718,
    "question": "426,167,543,377",
    "answer": "娇生惯养",
    "explain": "娇生惯养"
  },
  {
    "level": 2719,
    "question": "205,80,842,209",
    "answer": "粟红贯朽",
    "explain": "粟红贯朽"
  },
  {
    "level": 2720,
    "question": "470,554,7,161",
    "answer": "取之无禁",
    "explain": "取之无禁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2721,
    "question": "45,629,579,37",
    "answer": "畏缩不前",
    "explain": "畏缩不前"
  },
  {
    "level": 2722,
    "question": "423,651,734,423",
    "answer": "金刚怒目",
    "explain": "金刚怒目"
  },
  {
    "level": 2723,
    "question": "630,528,273,801",
    "answer": "螳臂挡车",
    "explain": "螳臂挡车"
  },
  {
    "level": 2724,
    "question": "641,476,436,468",
    "answer": "食子徇君",
    "explain": "食子徇君"
  },
  {
    "level": 2725,
    "question": "746,773,445,734",
    "answer": "类聚群分",
    "explain": "类聚群分"
  },
  {
    "level": 2726,
    "question": "468,78,7,4",
    "answer": "君命无二",
    "explain": "君命无二"
  },
  {
    "level": 2727,
    "question": "213,519,127,119",
    "answer": "华灯初上",
    "explain": "华灯初上"
  },
  {
    "level": 2728,
    "question": "495,109,356,3",
    "answer": "真心诚意",
    "explain": "真心诚意"
  },
  {
    "level": 2729,
    "question": "502,528,38,101",
    "answer": "先礼后兵",
    "explain": "先礼后兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2730,
    "question": "305,721,565,371",
    "answer": "唱筹量沙",
    "explain": "唱筹量沙"
  },
  {
    "level": 2731,
    "question": "173,641,67,371",
    "answer": "雾似轻纱",
    "explain": "雾似轻纱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2732,
    "question": "502,476,71,49",
    "answer": "画地为牢",
    "explain": "画地为牢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2733,
    "question": "242,218,812,179",
    "answer": "浑俗和光",
    "explain": "浑俗和光"
  },
  {
    "level": 2734,
    "question": "71,821,71,831",
    "answer": "危言危行",
    "explain": "危言危行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2735,
    "question": "460,67,641,218",
    "answer": "人情世故",
    "explain": "人情世故"
  },
  {
    "level": 2736,
    "question": "298,44,374,499",
    "answer": "风云变幻",
    "explain": "风云变幻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2737,
    "question": "426,641,480,482",
    "answer": "料事如神",
    "explain": "料事如神"
  },
  {
    "level": 2738,
    "question": "412,412,365,365",
    "answer": "马马虎虎",
    "explain": "马马虎虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 2739,
    "question": "101,446,177,652",
    "answer": "东扶西倒",
    "explain": "东扶西倒"
  },
  {
    "level": 2740,
    "question": "177,369,630,280",
    "answer": "惜老怜贫",
    "explain": "惜老怜贫"
  },
  {
    "level": 2741,
    "question": "222,434,7,269",
    "answer": "秋毫无犯",
    "explain": "秋毫无犯"
  },
  {
    "level": 2742,
    "question": "88,380,380,460",
    "answer": "推己及人",
    "explain": "推己及人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2743,
    "question": "423,476,579,777",
    "answer": "视而不见",
    "explain": "视而不见"
  },
  {
    "level": 2744,
    "question": "579,5,579,6",
    "answer": "不三不四",
    "explain": "不三不四"
  },
  {
    "level": 2745,
    "question": "232,495,232,785",
    "answer": "教学相长",
    "explain": "教学相长"
  },
  {
    "level": 2746,
    "question": "116,554,752,647",
    "answer": "处之泰然",
    "explain": "处之泰然"
  },
  {
    "level": 2747,
    "question": "278,165,312,170",
    "answer": "罪有应得",
    "explain": "罪有应得"
  },
  {
    "level": 2748,
    "question": "412,249,363,460",
    "answer": "马面牛头",
    "explain": "马面牛头"
  },
  {
    "level": 2749,
    "question": "821,90,171,270",
    "answer": "炙手可热",
    "explain": "炙手可热"
  },
  {
    "level": 2750,
    "question": "4,496,746,426",
    "answer": "良药苦口",
    "explain": "良药苦口"
  },
  {
    "level": 2751,
    "question": "579,71,476,82",
    "answer": "不为瓦全",
    "explain": "不为瓦全"
  },
  {
    "level": 2752,
    "question": "3,650,579,45",
    "answer": "一窍不通",
    "explain": "一窍不通"
  },
  {
    "level": 2753,
    "question": "423,489,478,391",
    "answer": "目挑眉语",
    "explain": "目挑眉语"
  },
  {
    "level": 2754,
    "question": "204,389,799,491",
    "answer": "膘肥体壮",
    "explain": "膘肥体壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2755,
    "question": "374,647,322,73",
    "answer": "香火因缘",
    "explain": "香火因缘"
  },
  {
    "level": 2756,
    "question": "711,298,696,696",
    "answer": "威风凛凛",
    "explain": "威风凛凛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2757,
    "question": "398,653,248,534",
    "answer": "鸟枪换炮",
    "explain": "鸟枪换炮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2758,
    "question": "495,93,165,230",
    "answer": "学业有成",
    "explain": "学业有成"
  },
  {
    "level": 2759,
    "question": "476,167,304,486",
    "answer": "同生共死",
    "explain": "同生共死"
  },
  {
    "level": 2760,
    "question": "298,460,426,605",
    "answer": "逢人说项",
    "explain": "逢人说项"
  },
  {
    "level": 2761,
    "question": "831,412,655,213",
    "answer": "走马看花",
    "explain": "走马看花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2762,
    "question": "650,90,650,457",
    "answer": "大手大脚",
    "explain": "大手大脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 2763,
    "question": "37,628,580,165",
    "answer": "前所未有",
    "explain": "前所未有"
  },
  {
    "level": 2764,
    "question": "5,88,8,106",
    "answer": "三推六问",
    "explain": "三推六问"
  },
  {
    "level": 2765,
    "question": "8,8,650,316",
    "answer": "六六大顺",
    "explain": "六六大顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2766,
    "question": "457,366,280,35",
    "answer": "竹报平安",
    "explain": "竹报平安"
  },
  {
    "level": 2767,
    "question": "479,767,479,375",
    "answer": "怪模怪样",
    "explain": "怪模怪样"
  },
  {
    "level": 2768,
    "question": "776,71,379,92",
    "answer": "宁为鸡首",
    "explain": "宁为鸡首"
  },
  {
    "level": 2769,
    "question": "436,135,591,496",
    "answer": "采兰赠药",
    "explain": "采兰赠药"
  },
  {
    "level": 2770,
    "question": "283,425,218,557",
    "answer": "单文孤证",
    "explain": "单文孤证"
  },
  {
    "level": 2771,
    "question": "486,236,652,167",
    "answer": "死里逃生",
    "explain": "死里逃生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2772,
    "question": "247,88,247,11",
    "answer": "半推半就",
    "explain": "半推半就"
  },
  {
    "level": 2773,
    "question": "73,322,398,92",
    "answer": "莺歌燕舞",
    "explain": "莺歌燕舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2774,
    "question": "47,365,468,546",
    "answer": "与虎谋皮",
    "explain": "与虎谋皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2775,
    "question": "131,207,273,471",
    "answer": "排除万难",
    "explain": "排除万难"
  },
  {
    "level": 2776,
    "question": "821,579,165,130",
    "answer": "言不由衷",
    "explain": "言不由衷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2777,
    "question": "772,91,230,177",
    "answer": "屈打成招",
    "explain": "屈打成招"
  },
  {
    "level": 2778,
    "question": "641,434,389,434",
    "answer": "似懂非懂",
    "explain": "似懂非懂"
  },
  {
    "level": 2779,
    "question": "230,45,426,476",
    "answer": "局天扣地",
    "explain": "局天扣地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2780,
    "question": "476,442,72,620",
    "answer": "瓦釜雷鸣",
    "explain": "瓦釜雷鸣"
  },
  {
    "level": 2781,
    "question": "167,486,165,78",
    "answer": "生死有命",
    "explain": "生死有命"
  },
  {
    "level": 2782,
    "question": "376,777,579,280",
    "answer": "路见不平",
    "explain": "路见不平"
  },
  {
    "level": 2783,
    "question": "342,101,480,482",
    "answer": "用兵如神",
    "explain": "用兵如神"
  },
  {
    "level": 2784,
    "question": "389,161,109,380",
    "answer": "费尽心机",
    "explain": "费尽心机"
  },
  {
    "level": 2785,
    "question": "652,179,700,313",
    "answer": "刀光剑影",
    "explain": "刀光剑影"
  },
  {
    "level": 2786,
    "question": "270,696,80,220",
    "answer": "满山红叶",
    "explain": "满山红叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 2787,
    "question": "461,213,256,776",
    "answer": "借花献佛",
    "explain": "借花献佛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2788,
    "question": "696,344,476,746",
    "answer": "善贾而沽",
    "explain": "善贾而沽"
  },
  {
    "level": 2789,
    "question": "554,147,94,323",
    "answer": "此起彼伏",
    "explain": "此起彼伏"
  },
  {
    "level": 2790,
    "question": "258,446,398,89",
    "answer": "卵覆鸟飞",
    "explain": "卵覆鸟飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 2791,
    "question": "91,230,3,221",
    "answer": "打成一片",
    "explain": "打成一片"
  },
  {
    "level": 2792,
    "question": "90,457,7,426",
    "answer": "手足无措",
    "explain": "手足无措"
  },
  {
    "level": 2793,
    "question": "3,280,480,821",
    "answer": "一贫如洗",
    "explain": "一贫如洗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2794,
    "question": "460,78,655,45",
    "answer": "人命关天",
    "explain": "人命关天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2795,
    "question": "3,556,554,523",
    "answer": "一念之差",
    "explain": "一念之差"
  },
  {
    "level": 2796,
    "question": "304,412,641,829",
    "answer": "驽马十驾",
    "explain": "驽马十驾"
  },
  {
    "level": 2797,
    "question": "170,49,5,247",
    "answer": "得失参半",
    "explain": "得失参半"
  },
  {
    "level": 2798,
    "question": "533,273,542,183",
    "answer": "百万买宅",
    "explain": "百万买宅"
  },
  {
    "level": 2799,
    "question": "342,799,3,177",
    "answer": "用在一朝",
    "explain": "用在一朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2800,
    "question": "3,43,67,389",
    "answer": "意惹情牵",
    "explain": "意惹情牵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2801,
    "question": "207,599,476,278",
    "answer": "庶民同罪",
    "explain": "庶民同罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2802,
    "question": "3,482,3,481",
    "answer": "疑神疑鬼",
    "explain": "疑神疑鬼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2803,
    "question": "630,381,227,696",
    "answer": "螳螂捕蝉",
    "explain": "螳螂捕蝉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2804,
    "question": "230,3,146,813",
    "answer": "星移斗转",
    "explain": "星移斗转"
  },
  {
    "level": 2805,
    "question": "279,283,466,197",
    "answer": "肝胆楚越",
    "explain": "肝胆楚越"
  },
  {
    "level": 2806,
    "question": "655,553,480,44",
    "answer": "观者如云",
    "explain": "观者如云"
  },
  {
    "level": 2807,
    "question": "71,753,6,696",
    "answer": "黄雀伺蝉",
    "explain": "黄雀伺蝉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2808,
    "question": "3,460,205,120",
    "answer": "依人篱下",
    "explain": "依人篱下"
  },
  {
    "level": 2809,
    "question": "458,579,283,831",
    "answer": "祸不单行",
    "explain": "祸不单行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2810,
    "question": "468,468,165,528",
    "answer": "彬彬有礼",
    "explain": "彬彬有礼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2811,
    "question": "499,73,47,463",
    "answer": "珠圆玉润",
    "explain": "珠圆玉润"
  },
  {
    "level": 2812,
    "question": "478,3,821,556",
    "answer": "美意延年",
    "explain": "美意延年"
  },
  {
    "level": 2813,
    "question": "188,647,389,49",
    "answer": "惘然若失",
    "explain": "惘然若失"
  },
  {
    "level": 2814,
    "question": "232,170,3,390",
    "answer": "相得益彰",
    "explain": "相得益彰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2815,
    "question": "754,460,754,412",
    "answer": "盲人瞎马",
    "explain": "盲人瞎马"
  },
  {
    "level": 2816,
    "question": "176,36,398,270",
    "answer": "明白了当",
    "explain": "明白了当"
  },
  {
    "level": 2817,
    "question": "746,554,49,94",
    "answer": "顾此失彼",
    "explain": "顾此失彼"
  },
  {
    "level": 2818,
    "question": "555,554,230,530",
    "answer": "月章星句",
    "explain": "月章星句"
  },
  {
    "level": 2819,
    "question": "6,786,554,476",
    "answer": "四战之地",
    "explain": "四战之地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2820,
    "question": "71,147,73,772",
    "answer": "为国捐躯",
    "explain": "为国捐躯"
  },
  {
    "level": 2821,
    "question": "812,162,630,143",
    "answer": "伐功矜能",
    "explain": "伐功矜能"
  },
  {
    "level": 2822,
    "question": "170,3,655,203",
    "answer": "得意忘形",
    "explain": "得意忘形"
  },
  {
    "level": 2823,
    "question": "67,130,652,431",
    "answer": "轻重倒置",
    "explain": "轻重倒置"
  },
  {
    "level": 2824,
    "question": "426,3,579,4",
    "answer": "说一不二",
    "explain": "说一不二"
  },
  {
    "level": 2825,
    "question": "426,161,298,752",
    "answer": "道尽途穷",
    "explain": "道尽途穷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2826,
    "question": "93,248,87,342",
    "answer": "省吃俭用",
    "explain": "省吃俭用"
  },
  {
    "level": 2827,
    "question": "336,435,130,340",
    "answer": "外强中干",
    "explain": "外强中干"
  },
  {
    "level": 2828,
    "question": "426,431,109,374",
    "answer": "嘴直心快",
    "explain": "嘴直心快"
  },
  {
    "level": 2829,
    "question": "89,71,744,495",
    "answer": "飞黄腾达",
    "explain": "飞黄腾达"
  },
  {
    "level": 2830,
    "question": "423,3,333,423",
    "answer": "精益求精",
    "explain": "精益求精"
  },
  {
    "level": 2831,
    "question": "94,365,273,469",
    "answer": "千呼万唤",
    "explain": "千呼万唤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2832,
    "question": "146,379,831,381",
    "answer": "斗鸡走狗",
    "explain": "斗鸡走狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2833,
    "question": "369,339,323,236",
    "answer": "老骤伏枥",
    "explain": "老骤伏枥"
  },
  {
    "level": 2834,
    "question": "387,410,11,3",
    "answer": "从容就义",
    "explain": "从容就义"
  },
  {
    "level": 2835,
    "question": "304,787,273,94",
    "answer": "感慨万千",
    "explain": "感慨万千"
  },
  {
    "level": 2836,
    "question": "279,283,232,177",
    "answer": "肝胆相照",
    "explain": "肝胆相照"
  },
  {
    "level": 2837,
    "question": "696,209,533,463",
    "answer": "悬鹑百结",
    "explain": "悬鹑百结"
  },
  {
    "level": 2838,
    "question": "221,821,25,47",
    "answer": "片言折狱",
    "explain": "片言折狱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2839,
    "question": "704,236,565,652",
    "answer": "笑里藏刀",
    "explain": "笑里藏刀"
  },
  {
    "level": 2840,
    "question": "207,579,482,207",
    "answer": "数不胜数",
    "explain": "数不胜数"
  },
  {
    "level": 2841,
    "question": "584,746,503,45",
    "answer": "叫苦连天",
    "explain": "叫苦连天"
  },
  {
    "level": 2842,
    "question": "167,435,236,491",
    "answer": "身强力壮",
    "explain": "身强力壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2843,
    "question": "3,94,94,236",
    "answer": "一碧千里",
    "explain": "一碧千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 2844,
    "question": "279,460,367,476",
    "answer": "肝脑涂地",
    "explain": "肝脑涂地"
  },
  {
    "level": 2845,
    "question": "630,630,495,495",
    "answer": "堂堂正正",
    "explain": "堂堂正正"
  },
  {
    "level": 2846,
    "question": "480,213,641,47",
    "answer": "如花似玉",
    "explain": "如花似玉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2847,
    "question": "641,433,11,501",
    "answer": "十拿九稳",
    "explain": "十拿九稳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2848,
    "question": "94,236,554,340",
    "answer": "千里之堤",
    "explain": "千里之堤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2849,
    "question": "172,457,785,373",
    "answer": "封豕长蛇",
    "explain": "封豕长蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2850,
    "question": "374,412,110,339",
    "answer": "快马加鞭",
    "explain": "快马加鞭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2851,
    "question": "377,460,425,314",
    "answer": "仰人鼻息",
    "explain": "仰人鼻息"
  },
  {
    "level": 2852,
    "question": "431,821,579,580",
    "answer": "直言不讳",
    "explain": "直言不讳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2853,
    "question": "73,821,460,426",
    "answer": "脍炙人口",
    "explain": "脍炙人口"
  },
  {
    "level": 2854,
    "question": "298,470,111,167",
    "answer": "风趣横生",
    "explain": "风趣横生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2855,
    "question": "658,658,696,762",
    "answer": "循循善诱",
    "explain": "循循善诱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2856,
    "question": "392,476,3,696",
    "answer": "愚公移山",
    "explain": "愚公移山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2857,
    "question": "478,26,696,827",
    "answer": "美妙绝伦",
    "explain": "美妙绝伦"
  },
  {
    "level": 2858,
    "question": "476,476,165,482",
    "answer": "炯炯有神",
    "explain": "炯炯有神"
  },
  {
    "level": 2859,
    "question": "731,478,579,786",
    "answer": "愁眉不展",
    "explain": "愁眉不展"
  },
  {
    "level": 2860,
    "question": "171,579,410,188",
    "answer": "刻不容缓",
    "explain": "刻不容缓"
  },
  {
    "level": 2861,
    "question": "579,468,339,110",
    "answer": "不谋其政",
    "explain": "不谋其政"
  },
  {
    "level": 2862,
    "question": "170,579,305,49",
    "answer": "得不偿失",
    "explain": "得不偿失"
  },
  {
    "level": 2863,
    "question": "460,752,431,821",
    "answer": "人穷志短",
    "explain": "人穷志短"
  },
  {
    "level": 2864,
    "question": "501,480,752,696",
    "answer": "稳如泰山",
    "explain": "稳如泰山"
  },
  {
    "level": 2865,
    "question": "2,651,431,91",
    "answer": "零敲碎打",
    "explain": "零敲碎打"
  },
  {
    "level": 2866,
    "question": "131,696,93,630",
    "answer": "荒山野岭",
    "explain": "荒山野岭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2867,
    "question": "368,3,579,696",
    "answer": "狐疑不决",
    "explain": "狐疑不决"
  },
  {
    "level": 2868,
    "question": "8,565,554,218",
    "answer": "六尺之孤",
    "explain": "六尺之孤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2869,
    "question": "377,785,476,530",
    "answer": "扬长而去",
    "explain": "扬长而去"
  },
  {
    "level": 2870,
    "question": "45,461,47,213",
    "answer": "天女散花",
    "explain": "天女散花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2871,
    "question": "182,336,380,743",
    "answer": "海外奇谈",
    "explain": "海外奇谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2872,
    "question": "314,314,232,45",
    "answer": "息息相通",
    "explain": "息息相通"
  },
  {
    "level": 2873,
    "question": "45,495,663,831",
    "answer": "天真烂漫",
    "explain": "天真烂漫"
  },
  {
    "level": 2874,
    "question": "71,365,69,565",
    "answer": "为虎作伥",
    "explain": "为虎作伥"
  },
  {
    "level": 2875,
    "question": "528,101,322,412",
    "answer": "厉兵秣马",
    "explain": "厉兵秣马"
  },
  {
    "level": 2876,
    "question": "833,528,3,423",
    "answer": "让礼一寸",
    "explain": "让礼一寸"
  },
  {
    "level": 2877,
    "question": "650,389,270,69",
    "answer": "高朋满座",
    "explain": "高朋满座"
  },
  {
    "level": 2878,
    "question": "737,491,696,182",
    "answer": "气壮山河",
    "explain": "气壮山河"
  },
  {
    "level": 2879,
    "question": "777,367,66,323",
    "answer": "见兔放鹰",
    "explain": "见兔放鹰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2880,
    "question": "298,324,173,47",
    "answer": "风吹雾散",
    "explain": "风吹雾散"
  },
  {
    "level": 2881,
    "question": "834,435,276,304",
    "answer": "南腔北调",
    "explain": "南腔北调"
  },
  {
    "level": 2882,
    "question": "650,47,535,812",
    "answer": "大雨滂沱",
    "explain": "大雨滂沱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2883,
    "question": "161,799,423,37",
    "answer": "近在眼前",
    "explain": "近在眼前"
  },
  {
    "level": 2884,
    "question": "112,426,230,554",
    "answer": "出口成章",
    "explain": "出口成章"
  },
  {
    "level": 2885,
    "question": "94,819,273,344",
    "answer": "千门万户",
    "explain": "千门万户"
  },
  {
    "level": 2886,
    "question": "230,94,119,273",
    "answer": "成千上万",
    "explain": "成千上万"
  },
  {
    "level": 2887,
    "question": "424,425,423,423",
    "answer": "耳闻目睹",
    "explain": "耳闻目睹"
  },
  {
    "level": 2888,
    "question": "501,220,118,381",
    "answer": "稳操左卷",
    "explain": "稳操左卷"
  },
  {
    "level": 2889,
    "question": "423,457,471,831",
    "answer": "寸步难行",
    "explain": "寸步难行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2890,
    "question": "45,242,476,35",
    "answer": "天昏地暗",
    "explain": "天昏地暗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2891,
    "question": "165,7,3,460",
    "answer": "尤物移人",
    "explain": "尤物移人"
  },
  {
    "level": 2892,
    "question": "662,704,47,380",
    "answer": "虹销雨霁",
    "explain": "虹销雨霁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2893,
    "question": "7,487,294,182",
    "answer": "污泥浊水",
    "explain": "污泥浊水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2894,
    "question": "2,831,480,8",
    "answer": "令行如流",
    "explain": "令行如流"
  },
  {
    "level": 2895,
    "question": "785,78,533,555",
    "answer": "长命百岁",
    "explain": "长命百岁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2896,
    "question": "218,218,4,380",
    "answer": "麦穗两歧",
    "explain": "麦穗两歧"
  },
  {
    "level": 2897,
    "question": "167,167,641,641",
    "answer": "生生世世",
    "explain": "生生世世"
  },
  {
    "level": 2898,
    "question": "4,369,314,499",
    "answer": "二龙戏珠",
    "explain": "二龙戏珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 2899,
    "question": "325,161,246,696",
    "answer": "弹尽粮绝",
    "explain": "弹尽粮绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 2900,
    "question": "411,82,650,47",
    "answer": "倾盆大雨",
    "explain": "倾盆大雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2901,
    "question": "73,89,821,103",
    "answer": "灰飞烟灭",
    "explain": "灰飞烟灭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2902,
    "question": "248,3,831,641",
    "answer": "便宜行事",
    "explain": "便宜行事"
  },
  {
    "level": 2903,
    "question": "819,283,344,501",
    "answer": "门单户薄",
    "explain": "门单户薄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2904,
    "question": "821,795,44,47",
    "answer": "烟消云散",
    "explain": "烟消云散"
  },
  {
    "level": 2905,
    "question": "213,245,249,457",
    "answer": "花团锦簇",
    "explain": "花团锦簇"
  },
  {
    "level": 2906,
    "question": "7,628,746,161",
    "answer": "无所顾忌",
    "explain": "无所顾忌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2907,
    "question": "197,486,648,534",
    "answer": "越古超今",
    "explain": "越古超今"
  },
  {
    "level": 2908,
    "question": "77,172,101,438",
    "answer": "冰封雪盖",
    "explain": "冰封雪盖"
  },
  {
    "level": 2909,
    "question": "389,538,7,66",
    "answer": "立贤无方",
    "explain": "立贤无方"
  },
  {
    "level": 2910,
    "question": "220,476,435,369",
    "answer": "叶公好龙",
    "explain": "叶公好龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 2911,
    "question": "87,305,798,431",
    "answer": "浅尝辄止",
    "explain": "浅尝辄止"
  },
  {
    "level": 2912,
    "question": "101,130,591,738",
    "answer": "雪中送炭",
    "explain": "雪中送炭"
  },
  {
    "level": 2913,
    "question": "43,819,821,376",
    "answer": "广开言路",
    "explain": "广开言路"
  },
  {
    "level": 2914,
    "question": "258,9,10,176",
    "answer": "乱七八糟",
    "explain": "乱七八糟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2915,
    "question": "439,819,3,249",
    "answer": "网开一面",
    "explain": "网开一面"
  },
  {
    "level": 2916,
    "question": "389,460,650,424",
    "answer": "肥头大耳",
    "explain": "肥头大耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2917,
    "question": "121,69,737,628",
    "answer": "锐挫气索",
    "explain": "锐挫气索"
  },
  {
    "level": 2918,
    "question": "641,94,66,521",
    "answer": "食必方丈",
    "explain": "食必方丈"
  },
  {
    "level": 2919,
    "question": "423,579,813,411",
    "answer": "目不转睛",
    "explain": "目不转睛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2920,
    "question": "491,461,409,344",
    "answer": "土阶茅屋",
    "explain": "土阶茅屋"
  },
  {
    "level": 2921,
    "question": "476,650,7,307",
    "answer": "地大物博",
    "explain": "地大物博"
  },
  {
    "level": 2922,
    "question": "476,461,67,785",
    "answer": "儿女情长",
    "explain": "儿女情长"
  },
  {
    "level": 2923,
    "question": "45,785,43,11",
    "answer": "天长日久",
    "explain": "天长日久"
  },
  {
    "level": 2924,
    "question": "7,426,470,82",
    "answer": "五脏俱全",
    "explain": "五脏俱全"
  },
  {
    "level": 2925,
    "question": "641,789,584,344",
    "answer": "十载寒窗",
    "explain": "十载寒窗"
  },
  {
    "level": 2926,
    "question": "101,460,109,329",
    "answer": "动人心弦",
    "explain": "动人心弦"
  },
  {
    "level": 2927,
    "question": "493,130,431,641",
    "answer": "发踪指示",
    "explain": "发踪指示"
  },
  {
    "level": 2928,
    "question": "3,90,3,457",
    "answer": "一手一足",
    "explain": "一手一足"
  },
  {
    "level": 2929,
    "question": "3,617,476,179",
    "answer": "一扫而光",
    "explain": "一扫而光"
  },
  {
    "level": 2930,
    "question": "283,705,480,409",
    "answer": "胆小如鼠",
    "explain": "胆小如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 2931,
    "question": "377,344,382,576",
    "answer": "仰屋著书",
    "explain": "仰屋著书"
  },
  {
    "level": 2932,
    "question": "249,119,108,213",
    "answer": "锦上添花",
    "explain": "锦上添花"
  },
  {
    "level": 2933,
    "question": "734,7,356,358",
    "answer": "胸无城府",
    "explain": "胸无城府"
  },
  {
    "level": 2934,
    "question": "672,812,556,223",
    "answer": "时和年丰",
    "explain": "时和年丰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2935,
    "question": "336,73,245,66",
    "answer": "外圆内方",
    "explain": "外圆内方"
  },
  {
    "level": 2936,
    "question": "495,391,403,398",
    "answer": "沉鱼落雁",
    "explain": "沉鱼落雁"
  },
  {
    "level": 2937,
    "question": "480,398,92,47",
    "answer": "如鸟兽散",
    "explain": "如鸟兽散"
  },
  {
    "level": 2938,
    "question": "36,249,576,167",
    "answer": "白面书生",
    "explain": "白面书生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2939,
    "question": "270,423,565,3",
    "answer": "满目疮痍",
    "explain": "满目疮痍"
  },
  {
    "level": 2940,
    "question": "734,203,304,737",
    "answer": "分形共气",
    "explain": "分形共气"
  },
  {
    "level": 2941,
    "question": "92,119,655,425",
    "answer": "掌上观文",
    "explain": "掌上观文"
  },
  {
    "level": 2942,
    "question": "324,183,258,459",
    "answer": "欢蹦乱跳",
    "explain": "欢蹦乱跳"
  },
  {
    "level": 2943,
    "question": "380,182,647,812",
    "answer": "济河焚舟",
    "explain": "济河焚舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 2944,
    "question": "176,423,565,283",
    "answer": "明目张胆",
    "explain": "明目张胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 2945,
    "question": "298,47,620,110",
    "answer": "风雨交加",
    "explain": "风雨交加"
  },
  {
    "level": 2946,
    "question": "69,49,4,380",
    "answer": "坐失良机",
    "explain": "坐失良机"
  },
  {
    "level": 2947,
    "question": "486,377,389,49",
    "answer": "亡羊补牢",
    "explain": "亡羊补牢"
  },
  {
    "level": 2948,
    "question": "66,248,554,819",
    "answer": "方便之门",
    "explain": "方便之门"
  },
  {
    "level": 2949,
    "question": "3,571,273,528",
    "answer": "一本万利",
    "explain": "一本万利"
  },
  {
    "level": 2950,
    "question": "651,305,380,370",
    "answer": "刚肠嫉恶",
    "explain": "刚肠嫉恶"
  },
  {
    "level": 2951,
    "question": "641,43,3,182",
    "answer": "十日一水",
    "explain": "十日一水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2952,
    "question": "182,696,451,528",
    "answer": "河山带砺",
    "explain": "河山带砺"
  },
  {
    "level": 2953,
    "question": "245,463,86,109",
    "answer": "团结友爱",
    "explain": "团结友爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 2954,
    "question": "641,556,344,120",
    "answer": "十年窗下",
    "explain": "十年窗下"
  },
  {
    "level": 2955,
    "question": "177,479,480,423",
    "answer": "惜墨如金",
    "explain": "惜墨如金"
  },
  {
    "level": 2956,
    "question": "3,43,94,236",
    "answer": "一日千里",
    "explain": "一日千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 2957,
    "question": "398,480,431,92",
    "answer": "了如指掌",
    "explain": "了如指掌"
  },
  {
    "level": 2958,
    "question": "210,182,696,819",
    "answer": "清水衙门",
    "explain": "清水衙门"
  },
  {
    "level": 2959,
    "question": "460,460,641,426",
    "answer": "头头是道",
    "explain": "头头是道"
  },
  {
    "level": 2960,
    "question": "270,554,7,558",
    "answer": "当之无愧",
    "explain": "当之无愧"
  },
  {
    "level": 2961,
    "question": "167,343,704,78",
    "answer": "身家性命",
    "explain": "身家性命"
  },
  {
    "level": 2962,
    "question": "5,6,476,831",
    "answer": "三思而行",
    "explain": "三思而行"
  },
  {
    "level": 2963,
    "question": "641,579,640,486",
    "answer": "事不师古",
    "explain": "事不师古"
  },
  {
    "level": 2964,
    "question": "744,650,147,389",
    "answer": "腾蛟起凤",
    "explain": "腾蛟起凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 2965,
    "question": "94,819,6,147",
    "answer": "闭门思过",
    "explain": "闭门思过"
  },
  {
    "level": 2966,
    "question": "37,365,38,432",
    "answer": "前呼后拥",
    "explain": "前呼后拥"
  },
  {
    "level": 2967,
    "question": "533,500,394,182",
    "answer": "百川归海",
    "explain": "百川归海"
  },
  {
    "level": 2968,
    "question": "459,722,458,722",
    "answer": "你知我知",
    "explain": "你知我知"
  },
  {
    "level": 2969,
    "question": "7,73,554,182",
    "answer": "无源之水",
    "explain": "无源之水"
  },
  {
    "level": 2970,
    "question": "461,460,651,711",
    "answer": "街头巷尾",
    "explain": "街头巷尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 2971,
    "question": "384,67,349,528",
    "answer": "详情度理",
    "explain": "详情度理"
  },
  {
    "level": 2972,
    "question": "37,628,580,425",
    "answer": "前所未闻",
    "explain": "前所未闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 2973,
    "question": "322,47,503,248",
    "answer": "阴雨连绵",
    "explain": "阴雨连绵"
  },
  {
    "level": 2974,
    "question": "342,90,435,256",
    "answer": "游手好闲",
    "explain": "游手好闲"
  },
  {
    "level": 2975,
    "question": "44,44,130,167",
    "answer": "芸芸众生",
    "explain": "芸芸众生"
  },
  {
    "level": 2976,
    "question": "3,330,403,831",
    "answer": "遗簪堕履",
    "explain": "遗簪堕履"
  },
  {
    "level": 2977,
    "question": "278,493,379,546",
    "answer": "鹤发鸡皮",
    "explain": "鹤发鸡皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 2978,
    "question": "66,455,73,438",
    "answer": "方底圆盖",
    "explain": "方底圆盖"
  },
  {
    "level": 2979,
    "question": "236,188,661,663",
    "answer": "力挽狂澜",
    "explain": "力挽狂澜"
  },
  {
    "level": 2980,
    "question": "207,36,812,71",
    "answer": "数白论黄",
    "explain": "数白论黄"
  },
  {
    "level": 2981,
    "question": "177,2,176,281",
    "answer": "朝令夕改",
    "explain": "朝令夕改"
  },
  {
    "level": 2982,
    "question": "344,480,9,230",
    "answer": "屋如七星",
    "explain": "屋如七星"
  },
  {
    "level": 2983,
    "question": "426,426,426,426",
    "answer": "唠唠叨叨",
    "explain": "唠唠叨叨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2984,
    "question": "460,92,556,223",
    "answer": "人寿年丰",
    "explain": "人寿年丰"
  },
  {
    "level": 2985,
    "question": "651,109,431,431",
    "answer": "专心致志",
    "explain": "专心致志"
  },
  {
    "level": 2986,
    "question": "109,333,11,763",
    "answer": "新仇旧恨",
    "explain": "新仇旧恨"
  },
  {
    "level": 2987,
    "question": "7,313,7,130",
    "answer": "无影无踪",
    "explain": "无影无踪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2988,
    "question": "365,554,47,112",
    "answer": "呼之欲出",
    "explain": "呼之欲出"
  },
  {
    "level": 2989,
    "question": "143,565,6,503",
    "answer": "藕断丝连",
    "explain": "藕断丝连"
  },
  {
    "level": 2990,
    "question": "275,94,339,278",
    "answer": "怀碧其罪",
    "explain": "怀碧其罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 2991,
    "question": "439,476,269,493",
    "answer": "王子犯法",
    "explain": "王子犯法"
  },
  {
    "level": 2992,
    "question": "336,3,32,43",
    "answer": "饱以终日",
    "explain": "饱以终日"
  },
  {
    "level": 2993,
    "question": "218,495,650,349",
    "answer": "豁达大度",
    "explain": "豁达大度"
  },
  {
    "level": 2994,
    "question": "67,476,486,242",
    "answer": "情同骨肉",
    "explain": "情同骨肉"
  },
  {
    "level": 2995,
    "question": "579,431,120,106",
    "answer": "不耻下问",
    "explain": "不耻下问"
  },
  {
    "level": 2996,
    "question": "342,460,165,47",
    "answer": "游刃有余",
    "explain": "游刃有余"
  },
  {
    "level": 2997,
    "question": "432,368,799,363",
    "answer": "争猫丢牛",
    "explain": "争猫丢牛"
  },
  {
    "level": 2998,
    "question": "94,460,3,249",
    "answer": "千人一面",
    "explain": "千人一面"
  },
  {
    "level": 2999,
    "question": "411,93,322,445",
    "answer": "敬业乐群",
    "explain": "敬业乐群"
  },
  {
    "level": 3000,
    "question": "559,833,308,10",
    "answer": "苍翠挺拔",
    "explain": "苍翠挺拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3001,
    "question": "565,182,3,205",
    "answer": "沧海一粟",
    "explain": "沧海一粟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3002,
    "question": "87,461,554,476",
    "answer": "切肤之痛",
    "explain": "切肤之痛"
  },
  {
    "level": 3003,
    "question": "652,543,188,543",
    "answer": "讨价还价",
    "explain": "讨价还价"
  },
  {
    "level": 3004,
    "question": "229,229,339,743",
    "answer": "夸夸其谈",
    "explain": "夸夸其谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3005,
    "question": "382,497,434,426",
    "answer": "朱唇皓齿",
    "explain": "朱唇皓齿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3006,
    "question": "486,484,209,415",
    "answer": "枯枿朽株",
    "explain": "枯枿朽株"
  },
  {
    "level": 3007,
    "question": "277,177,276,298",
    "answer": "喝西北风",
    "explain": "喝西北风"
  },
  {
    "level": 3008,
    "question": "298,47,125,496",
    "answer": "风雨飘摇",
    "explain": "风雨飘摇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3009,
    "question": "207,366,35,4",
    "answer": "除暴安良",
    "explain": "除暴安良"
  },
  {
    "level": 3010,
    "question": "391,369,181,623",
    "answer": "鱼龙混杂",
    "explain": "鱼龙混杂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3011,
    "question": "74,36,734,176",
    "answer": "黑白分明",
    "explain": "黑白分明"
  },
  {
    "level": 3012,
    "question": "3,501,44,45",
    "answer": "义薄云天",
    "explain": "义薄云天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3013,
    "question": "37,188,38,88",
    "answer": "前挽后推",
    "explain": "前挽后推"
  },
  {
    "level": 3014,
    "question": "533,7,3,49",
    "answer": "百无一失",
    "explain": "百无一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 3015,
    "question": "345,579,482,345",
    "answer": "防不胜防",
    "explain": "防不胜防"
  },
  {
    "level": 3016,
    "question": "659,742,579,35",
    "answer": "惶恐不安",
    "explain": "惶恐不安"
  },
  {
    "level": 3017,
    "question": "3,555,94,423",
    "answer": "一字千金",
    "explain": "一字千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 3018,
    "question": "469,471,47,304",
    "answer": "患难与共",
    "explain": "患难与共"
  },
  {
    "level": 3019,
    "question": "722,471,476,88",
    "answer": "知难而推",
    "explain": "知难而推"
  },
  {
    "level": 3020,
    "question": "119,812,734,176",
    "answer": "赏罚分明",
    "explain": "赏罚分明"
  },
  {
    "level": 3021,
    "question": "120,6,734,734",
    "answer": "来势汹汹",
    "explain": "来势汹汹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3022,
    "question": "702,101,554,700",
    "answer": "隙穴之窥",
    "explain": "隙穴之窥"
  },
  {
    "level": 3023,
    "question": "4,734,176,555",
    "answer": "二分明月",
    "explain": "二分明月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3024,
    "question": "469,469,47,486",
    "answer": "跃跃欲试",
    "explain": "跃跃欲试"
  },
  {
    "level": 3025,
    "question": "460,480,648,182",
    "answer": "人如潮涌",
    "explain": "人如潮涌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3026,
    "question": "343,600,344,591",
    "answer": "家传户诵",
    "explain": "家传户诵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3027,
    "question": "230,175,704,277",
    "answer": "成也萧何",
    "explain": "成也萧何"
  },
  {
    "level": 3028,
    "question": "476,47,374,232",
    "answer": "地狱变相",
    "explain": "地狱变相"
  },
  {
    "level": 3029,
    "question": "753,419,554,314",
    "answer": "梦熊之喜",
    "explain": "梦熊之喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3030,
    "question": "273,460,162,651",
    "answer": "万人空巷",
    "explain": "万人空巷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3031,
    "question": "213,435,555,73",
    "answer": "花好月圆",
    "explain": "花好月圆"
  },
  {
    "level": 3032,
    "question": "476,415,554,3",
    "answer": "地主之仪",
    "explain": "地主之仪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3033,
    "question": "502,478,772,492",
    "answer": "画眉举案",
    "explain": "画眉举案"
  },
  {
    "level": 3034,
    "question": "165,773,66,269",
    "answer": "有的放矢",
    "explain": "有的放矢"
  },
  {
    "level": 3035,
    "question": "280,316,522,460",
    "answer": "贫贱骄人",
    "explain": "贫贱骄人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3036,
    "question": "273,92,7,435",
    "answer": "万寿无疆",
    "explain": "万寿无疆"
  },
  {
    "level": 3037,
    "question": "365,381,554,6",
    "answer": "虎狼之势",
    "explain": "虎狼之势"
  },
  {
    "level": 3038,
    "question": "434,821,491,391",
    "answer": "豪言壮语",
    "explain": "豪言壮语"
  },
  {
    "level": 3039,
    "question": "120,412,655,213",
    "answer": "下马看花",
    "explain": "下马看花"
  },
  {
    "level": 3040,
    "question": "460,460,431,71",
    "answer": "人人自危",
    "explain": "人人自危"
  },
  {
    "level": 3041,
    "question": "197,493,5,554",
    "answer": "约法三章",
    "explain": "约法三章"
  },
  {
    "level": 3042,
    "question": "468,468,336,336",
    "answer": "病病歪歪",
    "explain": "病病歪歪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3043,
    "question": "711,7,579,772",
    "answer": "威武不屈",
    "explain": "威武不屈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3044,
    "question": "389,3,576,539",
    "answer": "仗义疏财",
    "explain": "仗义疏财"
  },
  {
    "level": 3045,
    "question": "389,101,380,177",
    "answer": "声东击西",
    "explain": "声东击西"
  },
  {
    "level": 3046,
    "question": "298,248,45,373",
    "answer": "风驰电掣",
    "explain": "风驰电掣"
  },
  {
    "level": 3047,
    "question": "546,236,210,222",
    "answer": "皮里春秋",
    "explain": "皮里春秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3048,
    "question": "3,656,476,11",
    "answer": "一蹴而就",
    "explain": "一蹴而就"
  },
  {
    "level": 3049,
    "question": "5,2,7,167",
    "answer": "三令五申",
    "explain": "三令五申"
  },
  {
    "level": 3050,
    "question": "641,722,3,203",
    "answer": "释知遗形",
    "explain": "释知遗形"
  },
  {
    "level": 3051,
    "question": "8,725,579,460",
    "answer": "六亲不认",
    "explain": "六亲不认"
  },
  {
    "level": 3052,
    "question": "696,210,182,762",
    "answer": "山清水秀",
    "explain": "山清水秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3053,
    "question": "831,314,620,103",
    "answer": "履舄交错",
    "explain": "履舄交错"
  },
  {
    "level": 3054,
    "question": "579,431,579,831",
    "answer": "不止不行",
    "explain": "不止不行"
  },
  {
    "level": 3055,
    "question": "389,389,479,479",
    "answer": "偷偷摸摸",
    "explain": "偷偷摸摸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3056,
    "question": "380,380,554,436",
    "answer": "济济之才",
    "explain": "济济之才"
  },
  {
    "level": 3057,
    "question": "495,7,431,624",
    "answer": "学无止境",
    "explain": "学无止境"
  },
  {
    "level": 3058,
    "question": "67,777,6,772",
    "answer": "情见势屈",
    "explain": "情见势屈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3059,
    "question": "478,32,812,746",
    "answer": "撞钟伐鼓",
    "explain": "撞钟伐鼓"
  },
  {
    "level": 3060,
    "question": "7,180,468,506",
    "answer": "五彩缤纷",
    "explain": "五彩缤纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3061,
    "question": "579,478,478,423",
    "answer": "挤眉弄眼",
    "explain": "挤眉弄眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3062,
    "question": "38,460,781,298",
    "answer": "后人乘凉",
    "explain": "后人乘凉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3063,
    "question": "460,336,165,460",
    "answer": "人外有人",
    "explain": "人外有人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3064,
    "question": "533,556,650,545",
    "answer": "百年大计",
    "explain": "百年大计"
  },
  {
    "level": 3065,
    "question": "502,493,431,460",
    "answer": "先发制人",
    "explain": "先发制人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3066,
    "question": "125,125,47,482",
    "answer": "飘飘欲仙",
    "explain": "飘飘欲仙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3067,
    "question": "101,101,210,210",
    "answer": "冷冷清清",
    "explain": "冷冷清清"
  },
  {
    "level": 3068,
    "question": "438,710,380,120",
    "answer": "双管齐下",
    "explain": "双管齐下"
  },
  {
    "level": 3069,
    "question": "373,94,230,470",
    "answer": "涉笔成趣",
    "explain": "涉笔成趣"
  },
  {
    "level": 3070,
    "question": "256,47,407,777",
    "answer": "瑕瑜互见",
    "explain": "瑕瑜互见"
  },
  {
    "level": 3071,
    "question": "273,461,579,446",
    "answer": "万劫不复",
    "explain": "万劫不复"
  },
  {
    "level": 3072,
    "question": "3,539,579,207",
    "answer": "一钱不值",
    "explain": "一钱不值"
  },
  {
    "level": 3073,
    "question": "294,389,246,641",
    "answer": "浊质凡姿",
    "explain": "浊质凡姿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3074,
    "question": "82,236,3,446",
    "answer": "全力以赴",
    "explain": "全力以赴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3075,
    "question": "831,167,439,486",
    "answer": "根深蒂固",
    "explain": "根深蒂固"
  },
  {
    "level": 3076,
    "question": "89,818,129,101",
    "answer": "飞鸿印雪",
    "explain": "飞鸿印雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3077,
    "question": "82,242,68,378",
    "answer": "温柔敦厚",
    "explain": "温柔敦厚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3078,
    "question": "705,109,3,3",
    "answer": "小心翼翼",
    "explain": "小心翼翼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3079,
    "question": "4,5,339,186",
    "answer": "二三其德",
    "explain": "二三其德"
  },
  {
    "level": 3080,
    "question": "450,696,554,370",
    "answer": "褒善贬恶",
    "explain": "褒善贬恶"
  },
  {
    "level": 3081,
    "question": "403,220,394,831",
    "answer": "落叶归根",
    "explain": "落叶归根"
  },
  {
    "level": 3082,
    "question": "82,90,82,457",
    "answer": "笨手笨脚",
    "explain": "笨手笨脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3083,
    "question": "495,436,641,495",
    "answer": "真才实学",
    "explain": "真才实学"
  },
  {
    "level": 3084,
    "question": "553,119,743,101",
    "answer": "纸上谈兵",
    "explain": "纸上谈兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3085,
    "question": "146,431,481,377",
    "answer": "斗志昂扬",
    "explain": "斗志昂扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 3086,
    "question": "6,576,7,193",
    "answer": "四书五经",
    "explain": "四书五经"
  },
  {
    "level": 3087,
    "question": "35,457,270,801",
    "answer": "安步当车",
    "explain": "安步当车"
  },
  {
    "level": 3088,
    "question": "379,381,579,423",
    "answer": "鸡犬不惊",
    "explain": "鸡犬不惊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3089,
    "question": "6,650,399,162",
    "answer": "四大皆空",
    "explain": "四大皆空"
  },
  {
    "level": 3090,
    "question": "363,562,647,379",
    "answer": "牛鼎烹鸡",
    "explain": "牛鼎烹鸡"
  },
  {
    "level": 3091,
    "question": "43,528,273,380",
    "answer": "日理万机",
    "explain": "日理万机"
  },
  {
    "level": 3092,
    "question": "236,161,423,546",
    "answer": "力尽筋疲",
    "explain": "力尽筋疲"
  },
  {
    "level": 3093,
    "question": "92,94,478,425",
    "answer": "舞笔弄文",
    "explain": "舞笔弄文"
  },
  {
    "level": 3094,
    "question": "426,424,554,495",
    "answer": "口耳之学",
    "explain": "口耳之学"
  },
  {
    "level": 3095,
    "question": "161,236,476,71",
    "answer": "尽力而为",
    "explain": "尽力而为"
  },
  {
    "level": 3096,
    "question": "378,470,339,378",
    "answer": "微乎其微",
    "explain": "微乎其微"
  },
  {
    "level": 3097,
    "question": "647,125,171,109",
    "answer": "活泼可爱",
    "explain": "活泼可爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3098,
    "question": "67,457,67,90",
    "answer": "轻脚轻手",
    "explain": "轻脚轻手"
  },
  {
    "level": 3099,
    "question": "94,222,273,451",
    "answer": "千秋万代",
    "explain": "千秋万代"
  },
  {
    "level": 3100,
    "question": "8,182,7,67",
    "answer": "流水无情",
    "explain": "流水无情"
  },
  {
    "level": 3101,
    "question": "144,144,101,424",
    "answer": "娓娓动听",
    "explain": "娓娓动听"
  },
  {
    "level": 3102,
    "question": "104,461,77,641",
    "answer": "冻解冰释",
    "explain": "冻解冰释"
  },
  {
    "level": 3103,
    "question": "376,210,36,101",
    "answer": "阳春白雪",
    "explain": "阳春白雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3104,
    "question": "147,486,819,167",
    "answer": "起死回生",
    "explain": "起死回生"
  },
  {
    "level": 3105,
    "question": "373,380,11,460",
    "answer": "舍己救人",
    "explain": "舍己救人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3106,
    "question": "207,650,177,298",
    "answer": "树大招风",
    "explain": "树大招风"
  },
  {
    "level": 3107,
    "question": "696,753,7,389",
    "answer": "鸦雀无声",
    "explain": "鸦雀无声"
  },
  {
    "level": 3108,
    "question": "555,176,230,841",
    "answer": "月明星稀",
    "explain": "月明星稀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3109,
    "question": "7,411,45,373",
    "answer": "物竞天择",
    "explain": "物竞天择"
  },
  {
    "level": 3110,
    "question": "384,426,647,167",
    "answer": "象齿焚身",
    "explain": "象齿焚身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3111,
    "question": "389,310,369,566",
    "answer": "凤毛麟角",
    "explain": "凤毛麟角"
  },
  {
    "level": 3112,
    "question": "661,298,366,47",
    "answer": "狂风暴雨",
    "explain": "狂风暴雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3113,
    "question": "641,273,641,696",
    "answer": "十荡十决",
    "explain": "十荡十决"
  },
  {
    "level": 3114,
    "question": "246,647,281,408",
    "answer": "翻然改图",
    "explain": "翻然改图"
  },
  {
    "level": 3115,
    "question": "655,819,650,380",
    "answer": "关门大吉",
    "explain": "关门大吉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3116,
    "question": "495,476,579,821",
    "answer": "学而不厌",
    "explain": "学而不厌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3117,
    "question": "704,457,423,819",
    "answer": "笑逐颜开",
    "explain": "笑逐颜开"
  },
  {
    "level": 3118,
    "question": "696,93,737,160",
    "answer": "绝圣弃智",
    "explain": "绝圣弃智"
  },
  {
    "level": 3119,
    "question": "423,486,125,374",
    "answer": "金桂飘香",
    "explain": "金桂飘香"
  },
  {
    "level": 3120,
    "question": "534,389,647,369",
    "answer": "炮凤烹龙",
    "explain": "炮凤烹龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3121,
    "question": "316,45,553,3",
    "answer": "顺天者逸",
    "explain": "顺天者逸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3122,
    "question": "11,304,130,325",
    "answer": "旧调重弹",
    "explain": "旧调重弹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3123,
    "question": "3,3,177,92",
    "answer": "依依惜别",
    "explain": "依依惜别"
  },
  {
    "level": 3124,
    "question": "641,226,162,97",
    "answer": "事捷功倍",
    "explain": "事捷功倍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3125,
    "question": "821,90,696,431",
    "answer": "洗手奉职",
    "explain": "洗手奉职"
  },
  {
    "level": 3126,
    "question": "3,210,4,36",
    "answer": "一清二白",
    "explain": "一清二白"
  },
  {
    "level": 3127,
    "question": "246,246,412,412",
    "answer": "密密麻麻",
    "explain": "密密麻麻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3128,
    "question": "160,391,630,207",
    "answer": "池鱼林木",
    "explain": "池鱼林木"
  },
  {
    "level": 3129,
    "question": "407,179,182,174",
    "answer": "湖光水色",
    "explain": "湖光水色"
  },
  {
    "level": 3130,
    "question": "370,391,130,428",
    "answer": "恶语中伤",
    "explain": "恶语中伤"
  },
  {
    "level": 3131,
    "question": "533,304,620,380",
    "answer": "百感交集",
    "explain": "百感交集"
  },
  {
    "level": 3132,
    "question": "478,478,650,423",
    "answer": "浓眉大眼",
    "explain": "浓眉大眼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3133,
    "question": "38,493,431,460",
    "answer": "后发制人",
    "explain": "后发制人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3134,
    "question": "246,696,197,630",
    "answer": "翻山越岭",
    "explain": "翻山越岭"
  },
  {
    "level": 3135,
    "question": "7,428,339,746",
    "answer": "物伤其类",
    "explain": "物伤其类"
  },
  {
    "level": 3136,
    "question": "743,704,298,167",
    "answer": "谈笑风生",
    "explain": "谈笑风生"
  },
  {
    "level": 3137,
    "question": "542,579,165,127",
    "answer": "靡不有初",
    "explain": "靡不有初"
  },
  {
    "level": 3138,
    "question": "37,641,579,655",
    "answer": "前事不忘",
    "explain": "前事不忘"
  },
  {
    "level": 3139,
    "question": "3,799,94,502",
    "answer": "意在笔先",
    "explain": "意在笔先"
  },
  {
    "level": 3140,
    "question": "762,47,71,7",
    "answer": "羞与为伍",
    "explain": "羞与为伍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3141,
    "question": "641,298,7,47",
    "answer": "十风五雨",
    "explain": "十风五雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3142,
    "question": "650,207,314,377",
    "answer": "告朔饩羊",
    "explain": "告朔饩羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3143,
    "question": "451,278,389,162",
    "answer": "带罪立功",
    "explain": "带罪立功"
  },
  {
    "level": 3144,
    "question": "381,525,394,476",
    "answer": "涓滴归公",
    "explain": "涓滴归公"
  },
  {
    "level": 3145,
    "question": "47,631,43,821",
    "answer": "雨淋日炙",
    "explain": "雨淋日炙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3146,
    "question": "273,641,716,143",
    "answer": "万事亨能",
    "explain": "万事亨能"
  },
  {
    "level": 3147,
    "question": "376,471,333,3",
    "answer": "鲁难求已",
    "explain": "鲁难求已"
  },
  {
    "level": 3148,
    "question": "167,525,460,109",
    "answer": "深入人心",
    "explain": "深入人心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3149,
    "question": "94,696,298,210",
    "answer": "弊绝风清",
    "explain": "弊绝风清"
  },
  {
    "level": 3150,
    "question": "3,232,67,634",
    "answer": "一相情愿",
    "explain": "一相情愿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3151,
    "question": "479,641,426,426",
    "answer": "怪事咄咄",
    "explain": "怪事咄咄"
  },
  {
    "level": 3152,
    "question": "655,339,628,3",
    "answer": "忘其所以",
    "explain": "忘其所以"
  },
  {
    "level": 3153,
    "question": "528,554,270,647",
    "answer": "理之当然",
    "explain": "理之当然"
  },
  {
    "level": 3154,
    "question": "314,249,342,389",
    "answer": "戏蝶游蜂",
    "explain": "戏蝶游蜂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3155,
    "question": "476,460,807,370",
    "answer": "铜头铁额",
    "explain": "铜头铁额"
  },
  {
    "level": 3156,
    "question": "109,7,4,342",
    "answer": "心无二用",
    "explain": "心无二用"
  },
  {
    "level": 3157,
    "question": "370,486,641,705",
    "answer": "饿死是小",
    "explain": "饿死是小"
  },
  {
    "level": 3158,
    "question": "423,7,6,460",
    "answer": "睹物思人",
    "explain": "睹物思人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3159,
    "question": "322,45,722,78",
    "answer": "乐天知命",
    "explain": "乐天知命"
  },
  {
    "level": 3160,
    "question": "3,43,5,222",
    "answer": "一日三秋",
    "explain": "一日三秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3161,
    "question": "213,431,177,786",
    "answer": "花枝招展",
    "explain": "花枝招展"
  },
  {
    "level": 3162,
    "question": "66,423,3,258",
    "answer": "方寸已乱",
    "explain": "方寸已乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3163,
    "question": "493,130,431,641",
    "answer": "发纵指示",
    "explain": "发纵指示"
  },
  {
    "level": 3164,
    "question": "641,67,502,3",
    "answer": "诗情画意",
    "explain": "诗情画意"
  },
  {
    "level": 3165,
    "question": "381,491,130,120",
    "answer": "卷土重来",
    "explain": "卷土重来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3166,
    "question": "249,748,696,182",
    "answer": "锦绣山河",
    "explain": "锦绣山河"
  },
  {
    "level": 3167,
    "question": "82,398,502,89",
    "answer": "笨鸟先飞",
    "explain": "笨鸟先飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3168,
    "question": "565,3,270,423",
    "answer": "疮痍满目",
    "explain": "疮痍满目"
  },
  {
    "level": 3169,
    "question": "5,78,476,555",
    "answer": "三命而俯",
    "explain": "三命而俯"
  },
  {
    "level": 3170,
    "question": "67,476,90,457",
    "answer": "情同手足",
    "explain": "情同手足"
  },
  {
    "level": 3171,
    "question": "426,376,554,650",
    "answer": "咄嗟之间",
    "explain": "咄嗟之间"
  },
  {
    "level": 3172,
    "question": "502,2,399,767",
    "answer": "画梁雕栋",
    "explain": "画梁雕栋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3173,
    "question": "411,130,423,230",
    "answer": "井中视星",
    "explain": "井中视星"
  },
  {
    "level": 3174,
    "question": "446,801,554,652",
    "answer": "覆车之鉴",
    "explain": "覆车之鉴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3175,
    "question": "762,336,189,130",
    "answer": "秀外慧中",
    "explain": "秀外慧中"
  },
  {
    "level": 3176,
    "question": "722,471,476,501",
    "answer": "知难而进",
    "explain": "知难而进"
  },
  {
    "level": 3177,
    "question": "696,376,298,167",
    "answer": "绝路逢生",
    "explain": "绝路逢生"
  },
  {
    "level": 3178,
    "question": "652,305,314,218",
    "answer": "蹈常袭故",
    "explain": "蹈常袭故"
  },
  {
    "level": 3179,
    "question": "210,213,222,641",
    "answer": "春华秋实",
    "explain": "春华秋实"
  },
  {
    "level": 3180,
    "question": "412,652,230,162",
    "answer": "马到成功",
    "explain": "马到成功"
  },
  {
    "level": 3181,
    "question": "495,657,493,147",
    "answer": "沉滓泛起",
    "explain": "沉滓泛起"
  },
  {
    "level": 3182,
    "question": "431,554,460,38",
    "answer": "置之脑后",
    "explain": "置之脑后"
  },
  {
    "level": 3183,
    "question": "5,696,4,182",
    "answer": "三山二水",
    "explain": "三山二水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3184,
    "question": "704,506,480,647",
    "answer": "性烈如火",
    "explain": "性烈如火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3185,
    "question": "7,831,10,69",
    "answer": "五行八作",
    "explain": "五行八作"
  },
  {
    "level": 3186,
    "question": "182,273,45,162",
    "answer": "海阔天空",
    "explain": "海阔天空"
  },
  {
    "level": 3187,
    "question": "10,258,246,495",
    "answer": "拨乱反正",
    "explain": "拨乱反正"
  },
  {
    "level": 3188,
    "question": "130,73,457,376",
    "answer": "中原逐鹿",
    "explain": "中原逐鹿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3189,
    "question": "3,109,3,186",
    "answer": "一心一德",
    "explain": "一心一德"
  },
  {
    "level": 3190,
    "question": "438,314,630,819",
    "answer": "双喜临门",
    "explain": "双喜临门"
  },
  {
    "level": 3191,
    "question": "128,298,722,246",
    "answer": "迷途知返",
    "explain": "迷途知返"
  },
  {
    "level": 3192,
    "question": "734,203,47,174",
    "answer": "怒形于色",
    "explain": "怒形于色"
  },
  {
    "level": 3193,
    "question": "111,167,431,463",
    "answer": "横生枝节",
    "explain": "横生枝节"
  },
  {
    "level": 3194,
    "question": "407,179,696,174",
    "answer": "湖光山色",
    "explain": "湖光山色"
  },
  {
    "level": 3195,
    "question": "3,553,298,316",
    "answer": "一帆风顺",
    "explain": "一帆风顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 3196,
    "question": "777,579,380,345",
    "answer": "猝不及防",
    "explain": "猝不及防"
  },
  {
    "level": 3197,
    "question": "647,799,576,576",
    "answer": "然荻读书",
    "explain": "然荻读书"
  },
  {
    "level": 3198,
    "question": "734,441,92,4",
    "answer": "分斤掰两",
    "explain": "分斤掰两"
  },
  {
    "level": 3199,
    "question": "403,213,165,3",
    "answer": "落花有意",
    "explain": "落花有意"
  },
  {
    "level": 3200,
    "question": "222,390,579,210",
    "answer": "纠缠不清",
    "explain": "纠缠不清"
  },
  {
    "level": 3201,
    "question": "821,501,434,33",
    "answer": "烟波浩渺",
    "explain": "烟波浩渺"
  },
  {
    "level": 3202,
    "question": "273,641,470,97",
    "answer": "万事俱备",
    "explain": "万事俱备"
  },
  {
    "level": 3203,
    "question": "411,416,554,777",
    "answer": "井蛙之见",
    "explain": "井蛙之见"
  },
  {
    "level": 3204,
    "question": "831,696,527,93",
    "answer": "漫山遍野",
    "explain": "漫山遍野"
  },
  {
    "level": 3205,
    "question": "308,167,476,112",
    "answer": "挺身而出",
    "explain": "挺身而出"
  },
  {
    "level": 3206,
    "question": "819,130,176,3",
    "answer": "开宗明义",
    "explain": "开宗明义"
  },
  {
    "level": 3207,
    "question": "650,125,167,90",
    "answer": "大显身手",
    "explain": "大显身手"
  },
  {
    "level": 3208,
    "question": "87,435,579,772",
    "answer": "坚强不屈",
    "explain": "坚强不屈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3209,
    "question": "650,389,380,365",
    "answer": "大声疾呼",
    "explain": "大声疾呼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3210,
    "question": "249,249,470,652",
    "answer": "面面俱到",
    "explain": "面面俱到"
  },
  {
    "level": 3211,
    "question": "579,522,579,737",
    "answer": "不骄不躁",
    "explain": "不骄不躁"
  },
  {
    "level": 3212,
    "question": "776,71,379,426",
    "answer": "宁为鸡口",
    "explain": "宁为鸡口"
  },
  {
    "level": 3213,
    "question": "377,579,558,45",
    "answer": "仰不愧天",
    "explain": "仰不愧天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3214,
    "question": "423,356,245,463",
    "answer": "精诚团结",
    "explain": "精诚团结"
  },
  {
    "level": 3215,
    "question": "111,9,207,10",
    "answer": "横七竖八",
    "explain": "横七竖八"
  },
  {
    "level": 3216,
    "question": "248,813,197,424",
    "answer": "婉转悦耳",
    "explain": "婉转悦耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3217,
    "question": "92,94,834,696",
    "answer": "寿比南山",
    "explain": "寿比南山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3218,
    "question": "167,167,579,314",
    "answer": "生生不息",
    "explain": "生生不息"
  },
  {
    "level": 3219,
    "question": "432,380,146,821",
    "answer": "争奇斗艳",
    "explain": "争奇斗艳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3220,
    "question": "831,398,812,119",
    "answer": "走了和尚",
    "explain": "走了和尚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3221,
    "question": "696,298,45,647",
    "answer": "煽风点火",
    "explain": "煽风点火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3222,
    "question": "182,476,182,246",
    "answer": "河同水密",
    "explain": "河同水密"
  },
  {
    "level": 3223,
    "question": "831,101,431,188",
    "answer": "行动迟缓",
    "explain": "行动迟缓"
  },
  {
    "level": 3224,
    "question": "528,831,463,197",
    "answer": "厉行节约",
    "explain": "厉行节约"
  },
  {
    "level": 3225,
    "question": "97,37,380,38",
    "answer": "承前启后",
    "explain": "承前启后"
  },
  {
    "level": 3226,
    "question": "650,120,339,90",
    "answer": "高下其手",
    "explain": "高下其手"
  },
  {
    "level": 3227,
    "question": "271,7,555,502",
    "answer": "贪污腐化",
    "explain": "贪污腐化"
  },
  {
    "level": 3228,
    "question": "469,647,394,120",
    "answer": "翩然归来",
    "explain": "翩然归来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3229,
    "question": "579,93,460,641",
    "answer": "不省人事",
    "explain": "不省人事"
  },
  {
    "level": 3230,
    "question": "37,555,38,377",
    "answer": "前俯后仰",
    "explain": "前俯后仰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3231,
    "question": "446,71,380,753",
    "answer": "扶危济困",
    "explain": "扶危济困"
  },
  {
    "level": 3232,
    "question": "247,594,247,3",
    "answer": "半信半疑",
    "explain": "半信半疑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3233,
    "question": "410,179,492,493",
    "answer": "容光焕发",
    "explain": "容光焕发"
  },
  {
    "level": 3234,
    "question": "3,799,97,476",
    "answer": "意在沛公",
    "explain": "意在沛公"
  },
  {
    "level": 3235,
    "question": "486,3,355,273",
    "answer": "挂一漏万",
    "explain": "挂一漏万"
  },
  {
    "level": 3236,
    "question": "409,525,5,746",
    "answer": "茅庐三顾",
    "explain": "茅庐三顾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3237,
    "question": "377,389,365,546",
    "answer": "羊质虎皮",
    "explain": "羊质虎皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 3238,
    "question": "579,183,579,8",
    "answer": "不塞不流",
    "explain": "不塞不流"
  },
  {
    "level": 3239,
    "question": "91,366,579,280",
    "answer": "打抱不平",
    "explain": "打抱不平"
  },
  {
    "level": 3240,
    "question": "4,533,470,428",
    "answer": "两败俱伤",
    "explain": "两败俱伤"
  },
  {
    "level": 3241,
    "question": "273,384,336,109",
    "answer": "万象更新",
    "explain": "万象更新"
  },
  {
    "level": 3242,
    "question": "176,179,436,528",
    "answer": "晨光绚丽",
    "explain": "晨光绚丽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3243,
    "question": "97,696,451,182",
    "answer": "被山带河",
    "explain": "被山带河"
  },
  {
    "level": 3244,
    "question": "336,641,647,363",
    "answer": "饱食暖衣",
    "explain": "饱食暖衣"
  },
  {
    "level": 3245,
    "question": "431,283,130,109",
    "answer": "赤胆忠心",
    "explain": "赤胆忠心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3246,
    "question": "45,734,460,73",
    "answer": "天怒人怨",
    "explain": "天怒人怨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3247,
    "question": "270,305,112,180",
    "answer": "当场出彩",
    "explain": "当场出彩"
  },
  {
    "level": 3248,
    "question": "474,44,246,49",
    "answer": "彤云密布",
    "explain": "彤云密布"
  },
  {
    "level": 3249,
    "question": "522,161,460,431",
    "answer": "绞尽脑汁",
    "explain": "绞尽脑汁"
  },
  {
    "level": 3250,
    "question": "348,672,11,94",
    "answer": "医时救弊",
    "explain": "医时救弊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3251,
    "question": "7,44,246,734",
    "answer": "乌云翻滚",
    "explain": "乌云翻滚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3252,
    "question": "280,457,210,44",
    "answer": "平步青云",
    "explain": "平步青云"
  },
  {
    "level": 3253,
    "question": "5,457,562,389",
    "answer": "三足鼎立",
    "explain": "三足鼎立"
  },
  {
    "level": 3254,
    "question": "322,380,167,276",
    "answer": "乐极生悲",
    "explain": "乐极生悲"
  },
  {
    "level": 3255,
    "question": "831,183,322,458",
    "answer": "幸灾乐祸",
    "explain": "幸灾乐祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3256,
    "question": "181,47,470,89",
    "answer": "魄散魂飞",
    "explain": "魄散魂飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3257,
    "question": "650,436,705,342",
    "answer": "大材小用",
    "explain": "大材小用"
  },
  {
    "level": 3258,
    "question": "161,47,402,380",
    "answer": "严于律己",
    "explain": "严于律己"
  },
  {
    "level": 3259,
    "question": "161,752,380,821",
    "answer": "尽态极妍",
    "explain": "尽态极妍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3260,
    "question": "502,130,165,641",
    "answer": "画中有诗",
    "explain": "画中有诗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3261,
    "question": "471,461,471,734",
    "answer": "难解难分",
    "explain": "难解难分"
  },
  {
    "level": 3262,
    "question": "476,43,460,314",
    "answer": "地广人希",
    "explain": "地广人希"
  },
  {
    "level": 3263,
    "question": "522,369,502,365",
    "answer": "乔龙画虎",
    "explain": "乔龙画虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3264,
    "question": "663,328,130,207",
    "answer": "滥竽充数",
    "explain": "滥竽充数"
  },
  {
    "level": 3265,
    "question": "435,376,480,495",
    "answer": "残阳如血",
    "explain": "残阳如血"
  },
  {
    "level": 3266,
    "question": "170,410,655,207",
    "answer": "得陇望蜀",
    "explain": "得陇望蜀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3267,
    "question": "389,7,339,641",
    "answer": "若无其事",
    "explain": "若无其事"
  },
  {
    "level": 3268,
    "question": "35,245,69,336",
    "answer": "安内攘外",
    "explain": "安内攘外"
  },
  {
    "level": 3269,
    "question": "343,280,725,369",
    "answer": "家贫亲老",
    "explain": "家贫亲老"
  },
  {
    "level": 3270,
    "question": "131,696,652,182",
    "answer": "排山倒海",
    "explain": "排山倒海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3271,
    "question": "236,579,482,460",
    "answer": "力不胜任",
    "explain": "力不胜任"
  },
  {
    "level": 3272,
    "question": "165,3,170,3",
    "answer": "有一得一",
    "explain": "有一得一"
  },
  {
    "level": 3273,
    "question": "47,38,210,476",
    "answer": "雨后春笋",
    "explain": "雨后春笋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3274,
    "question": "109,426,480,3",
    "answer": "心口如一",
    "explain": "心口如一"
  },
  {
    "level": 3275,
    "question": "503,248,579,565",
    "answer": "连绵不断",
    "explain": "连绵不断"
  },
  {
    "level": 3276,
    "question": "500,8,579,314",
    "answer": "川流不息",
    "explain": "川流不息"
  },
  {
    "level": 3277,
    "question": "88,109,431,111",
    "answer": "推心置腹",
    "explain": "推心置腹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3278,
    "question": "43,380,555,746",
    "answer": "日积月累",
    "explain": "日积月累"
  },
  {
    "level": 3279,
    "question": "819,45,554,236",
    "answer": "回天之力",
    "explain": "回天之力"
  },
  {
    "level": 3280,
    "question": "426,426,305,435",
    "answer": "啧啧称赞",
    "explain": "啧啧称赞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3281,
    "question": "714,460,714,711",
    "answer": "彻头彻尾",
    "explain": "彻头彻尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3282,
    "question": "365,563,277,8",
    "answer": "呼幺喝六",
    "explain": "呼幺喝六"
  },
  {
    "level": 3283,
    "question": "111,182,371,207",
    "answer": "恒河沙数",
    "explain": "恒河沙数"
  },
  {
    "level": 3284,
    "question": "652,313,349,203",
    "answer": "鉴影度形",
    "explain": "鉴影度形"
  },
  {
    "level": 3285,
    "question": "7,213,10,819",
    "answer": "五花八门",
    "explain": "五花八门"
  },
  {
    "level": 3286,
    "question": "130,411,3,772",
    "answer": "众擎易举",
    "explain": "众擎易举"
  },
  {
    "level": 3287,
    "question": "380,579,120,373",
    "answer": "急不暇择",
    "explain": "急不暇择"
  },
  {
    "level": 3288,
    "question": "47,322,262,2",
    "answer": "余音绕梁",
    "explain": "余音绕梁"
  },
  {
    "level": 3289,
    "question": "37,772,38,162",
    "answer": "前倨后恭",
    "explain": "前倨后恭"
  },
  {
    "level": 3290,
    "question": "457,160,214,468",
    "answer": "足智多谋",
    "explain": "足智多谋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3291,
    "question": "746,161,279,120",
    "answer": "苦尽甘来",
    "explain": "苦尽甘来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3292,
    "question": "90,652,468,207",
    "answer": "手到病除",
    "explain": "手到病除"
  },
  {
    "level": 3293,
    "question": "630,71,579,407",
    "answer": "临危不惧",
    "explain": "临危不惧"
  },
  {
    "level": 3294,
    "question": "162,230,176,11",
    "answer": "功成名就",
    "explain": "功成名就"
  },
  {
    "level": 3295,
    "question": "314,579,431,482",
    "answer": "喜不自胜",
    "explain": "喜不自胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3296,
    "question": "819,45,7,752",
    "answer": "回味无穷",
    "explain": "回味无穷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3297,
    "question": "819,820,389,641",
    "answer": "门庭若市",
    "explain": "门庭若市"
  },
  {
    "level": 3298,
    "question": "734,165,230,457",
    "answer": "胸有成竹",
    "explain": "胸有成竹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3299,
    "question": "298,210,555,418",
    "answer": "风清月朗",
    "explain": "风清月朗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3300,
    "question": "82,109,82,3",
    "answer": "全心全意",
    "explain": "全心全意"
  },
  {
    "level": 3301,
    "question": "130,109,434,434",
    "answer": "忠心耿耿",
    "explain": "忠心耿耿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3302,
    "question": "431,147,35,599",
    "answer": "治国安民",
    "explain": "治国安民"
  },
  {
    "level": 3303,
    "question": "161,109,58,236",
    "answer": "尽心竭力",
    "explain": "尽心竭力"
  },
  {
    "level": 3304,
    "question": "44,795,173,47",
    "answer": "云消雾散",
    "explain": "云消雾散"
  },
  {
    "level": 3305,
    "question": "278,154,424,270",
    "answer": "酒酣耳热",
    "explain": "酒酣耳热"
  },
  {
    "level": 3306,
    "question": "800,423,476,423",
    "answer": "侧目而视",
    "explain": "侧目而视"
  },
  {
    "level": 3307,
    "question": "73,620,161,316",
    "answer": "远交近攻",
    "explain": "远交近攻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3308,
    "question": "653,630,325,47",
    "answer": "枪林弹雨",
    "explain": "枪林弹雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3309,
    "question": "423,696,837,171",
    "answer": "金蝉脱壳",
    "explain": "金蝉脱壳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3310,
    "question": "45,101,45,435",
    "answer": "天兵天将",
    "explain": "天兵天将"
  },
  {
    "level": 3311,
    "question": "482,380,3,101",
    "answer": "灵机一动",
    "explain": "灵机一动"
  },
  {
    "level": 3312,
    "question": "786,7,579,482",
    "answer": "战无不胜",
    "explain": "战无不胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3313,
    "question": "696,752,182,161",
    "answer": "山穷水尽",
    "explain": "山穷水尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3314,
    "question": "9,468,10,831",
    "answer": "七拼八凑",
    "explain": "七拼八凑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3315,
    "question": "377,478,491,737",
    "answer": "扬眉吐气",
    "explain": "扬眉吐气"
  },
  {
    "level": 3316,
    "question": "630,374,177,47",
    "answer": "怜香惜玉",
    "explain": "怜香惜玉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3317,
    "question": "650,720,631,236",
    "answer": "大汗淋漓",
    "explain": "大汗淋漓"
  },
  {
    "level": 3318,
    "question": "821,600,167,232",
    "answer": "言传身教",
    "explain": "言传身教"
  },
  {
    "level": 3319,
    "question": "49,45,205,182",
    "answer": "瓮天蠡海",
    "explain": "瓮天蠡海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3320,
    "question": "641,579,3,431",
    "answer": "事不宜迟",
    "explain": "事不宜迟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3321,
    "question": "648,36,579,734",
    "answer": "皂白不分",
    "explain": "皂白不分"
  },
  {
    "level": 3322,
    "question": "382,298,476,394",
    "answer": "殊途同归",
    "explain": "殊途同归"
  },
  {
    "level": 3323,
    "question": "5,457,373,182",
    "answer": "三豕涉河",
    "explain": "三豕涉河"
  },
  {
    "level": 3324,
    "question": "389,233,389,344",
    "answer": "牵萝补屋",
    "explain": "牵萝补屋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3325,
    "question": "743,365,174,374",
    "answer": "谈虎色变",
    "explain": "谈虎色变"
  },
  {
    "level": 3326,
    "question": "495,476,579,381",
    "answer": "学而不倦",
    "explain": "学而不倦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3327,
    "question": "415,381,579,480",
    "answer": "猪狗不如",
    "explain": "猪狗不如"
  },
  {
    "level": 3328,
    "question": "831,73,431,370",
    "answer": "行远自迩",
    "explain": "行远自迩"
  },
  {
    "level": 3329,
    "question": "831,230,47,6",
    "answer": "行成于思",
    "explain": "行成于思"
  },
  {
    "level": 3330,
    "question": "807,249,524,160",
    "answer": "铁面御史",
    "explain": "铁面御史"
  },
  {
    "level": 3331,
    "question": "415,503,831,322",
    "answer": "株连蔓引",
    "explain": "株连蔓引"
  },
  {
    "level": 3332,
    "question": "373,161,333,73",
    "answer": "舍近求远",
    "explain": "舍近求远"
  },
  {
    "level": 3333,
    "question": "273,462,579,270",
    "answer": "万夫不当",
    "explain": "万夫不当"
  },
  {
    "level": 3334,
    "question": "5,92,812,182",
    "answer": "三兽渡河",
    "explain": "三兽渡河"
  },
  {
    "level": 3335,
    "question": "831,44,8,182",
    "answer": "行云流水",
    "explain": "行云流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3336,
    "question": "3,376,280,35",
    "answer": "一路平安",
    "explain": "一路平安"
  },
  {
    "level": 3337,
    "question": "336,193,298,101",
    "answer": "饱经风霜",
    "explain": "饱经风霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3338,
    "question": "476,696,6,476",
    "answer": "痛定思痛",
    "explain": "痛定思痛"
  },
  {
    "level": 3339,
    "question": "525,182,82,641",
    "answer": "滴水穿石",
    "explain": "滴水穿石"
  },
  {
    "level": 3340,
    "question": "528,47,436,109",
    "answer": "利欲熏心",
    "explain": "利欲熏心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3341,
    "question": "655,502,424,298",
    "answer": "观化听风",
    "explain": "观化听风"
  },
  {
    "level": 3342,
    "question": "531,525,389,389",
    "answer": "想入非非",
    "explain": "想入非非"
  },
  {
    "level": 3343,
    "question": "2,402,431,752",
    "answer": "黔驴技穷",
    "explain": "黔驴技穷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3344,
    "question": "109,480,431,182",
    "answer": "心如止水",
    "explain": "心如止水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3345,
    "question": "425,628,580,425",
    "answer": "闻所未闻",
    "explain": "闻所未闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3346,
    "question": "281,177,248,451",
    "answer": "改朝换代",
    "explain": "改朝换代"
  },
  {
    "level": 3347,
    "question": "365,298,469,47",
    "answer": "呼风唤雨",
    "explain": "呼风唤雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3348,
    "question": "7,161,339,342",
    "answer": "物尽其用",
    "explain": "物尽其用"
  },
  {
    "level": 3349,
    "question": "647,179,415,45",
    "answer": "火光烛天",
    "explain": "火光烛天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3350,
    "question": "90,769,457,258",
    "answer": "手忙脚乱",
    "explain": "手忙脚乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3351,
    "question": "339,528,565,423",
    "answer": "其利断金",
    "explain": "其利断金"
  },
  {
    "level": 3352,
    "question": "177,177,696,663",
    "answer": "朝霞灿烂",
    "explain": "朝霞灿烂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3353,
    "question": "161,382,553,431",
    "answer": "近朱者赤",
    "explain": "近朱者赤"
  },
  {
    "level": 3354,
    "question": "49,423,91,479",
    "answer": "失惊打怪",
    "explain": "失惊打怪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3355,
    "question": "374,502,7,752",
    "answer": "变化无穷",
    "explain": "变化无穷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3356,
    "question": "160,391,554,458",
    "answer": "池鱼之祸",
    "explain": "池鱼之祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3357,
    "question": "275,436,579,525",
    "answer": "怀才不遇",
    "explain": "怀才不遇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3358,
    "question": "88,480,696,3",
    "answer": "退如山移",
    "explain": "退如山移"
  },
  {
    "level": 3359,
    "question": "3,7,785,7",
    "answer": "一无长物",
    "explain": "一无长物"
  },
  {
    "level": 3360,
    "question": "6,182,71,343",
    "answer": "四海为家",
    "explain": "四海为家"
  },
  {
    "level": 3361,
    "question": "460,436,380,380",
    "answer": "人才济济",
    "explain": "人才济济"
  },
  {
    "level": 3362,
    "question": "101,119,110,101",
    "answer": "雪上加霜",
    "explain": "雪上加霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3363,
    "question": "476,279,304,746",
    "answer": "同甘共苦",
    "explain": "同甘共苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3364,
    "question": "273,82,554,565",
    "answer": "万全之策",
    "explain": "万全之策"
  },
  {
    "level": 3365,
    "question": "641,554,47,450",
    "answer": "示贬于褒",
    "explain": "示贬于褒"
  },
  {
    "level": 3366,
    "question": "460,650,476,47",
    "answer": "人间地狱",
    "explain": "人间地狱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3367,
    "question": "3,94,159,103",
    "answer": "一笔抹杀",
    "explain": "一笔抹杀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3368,
    "question": "527,493,652,528",
    "answer": "奋发蹈厉",
    "explain": "奋发蹈厉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3369,
    "question": "111,130,431,478",
    "answer": "横冲直撞",
    "explain": "横冲直撞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3370,
    "question": "45,183,476,799",
    "answer": "天崩地坼",
    "explain": "天崩地坼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3371,
    "question": "457,457,71,313",
    "answer": "步步为营",
    "explain": "步步为营"
  },
  {
    "level": 3372,
    "question": "390,696,326,370",
    "answer": "彰善瘅恶",
    "explain": "彰善瘅恶"
  },
  {
    "level": 3373,
    "question": "366,77,476,641",
    "answer": "报冰公事",
    "explain": "报冰公事"
  },
  {
    "level": 3374,
    "question": "725,409,269,641",
    "answer": "亲冒矢石",
    "explain": "亲冒矢石"
  },
  {
    "level": 3375,
    "question": "426,3,431,580",
    "answer": "聊以自慰",
    "explain": "聊以自慰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3376,
    "question": "6,283,236,501",
    "answer": "势单力薄",
    "explain": "势单力薄"
  },
  {
    "level": 3377,
    "question": "650,173,128,298",
    "answer": "大雾迷途",
    "explain": "大雾迷途"
  },
  {
    "level": 3378,
    "question": "479,389,49,71",
    "answer": "莫若勿为",
    "explain": "莫若勿为"
  },
  {
    "level": 3379,
    "question": "460,436,275,112",
    "answer": "人才辈出",
    "explain": "人才辈出"
  },
  {
    "level": 3380,
    "question": "276,462,49,412",
    "answer": "北叟失马",
    "explain": "北叟失马"
  },
  {
    "level": 3381,
    "question": "89,799,329,119",
    "answer": "箭在弦上",
    "explain": "箭在弦上"
  },
  {
    "level": 3382,
    "question": "407,6,258,531",
    "answer": "胡思乱想",
    "explain": "胡思乱想"
  },
  {
    "level": 3383,
    "question": "495,448,71,69",
    "answer": "正襟危坐",
    "explain": "正襟危坐"
  },
  {
    "level": 3384,
    "question": "72,80,273,445",
    "answer": "雷霆万钧",
    "explain": "雷霆万钧"
  },
  {
    "level": 3385,
    "question": "207,11,584,45",
    "answer": "数九寒天",
    "explain": "数九寒天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3386,
    "question": "90,457,67,167",
    "answer": "手足情深",
    "explain": "手足情深"
  },
  {
    "level": 3387,
    "question": "565,493,425,167",
    "answer": "断发文身",
    "explain": "断发文身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3388,
    "question": "273,120,470,380",
    "answer": "万籁俱寂",
    "explain": "万籁俱寂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3389,
    "question": "3,696,652,182",
    "answer": "移山倒海",
    "explain": "移山倒海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3390,
    "question": "298,213,101,175",
    "answer": "风花雪夜",
    "explain": "风花雪夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3391,
    "question": "87,562,579,772",
    "answer": "坚贞不屈",
    "explain": "坚贞不屈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3392,
    "question": "167,323,451,271",
    "answer": "枕戈待旦",
    "explain": "枕戈待旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3393,
    "question": "248,236,565,495",
    "answer": "绵里藏针",
    "explain": "绵里藏针"
  },
  {
    "level": 3394,
    "question": "650,799,270,37",
    "answer": "大敌当前",
    "explain": "大敌当前"
  },
  {
    "level": 3395,
    "question": "424,476,579,425",
    "answer": "听而不闻",
    "explain": "听而不闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3396,
    "question": "94,94,399,641",
    "answer": "比比皆是",
    "explain": "比比皆是"
  },
  {
    "level": 3397,
    "question": "322,410,704,407",
    "answer": "音容笑貌",
    "explain": "音容笑貌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3398,
    "question": "306,555,576,576",
    "answer": "映月读书",
    "explain": "映月读书"
  },
  {
    "level": 3399,
    "question": "71,423,672,451",
    "answer": "黄金时代",
    "explain": "黄金时代"
  },
  {
    "level": 3400,
    "question": "171,561,112,167",
    "answer": "科班出身",
    "explain": "科班出身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3401,
    "question": "27,27,7,579",
    "answer": "寥寥无几",
    "explain": "寥寥无几"
  },
  {
    "level": 3402,
    "question": "176,403,476,696",
    "answer": "名落孙山",
    "explain": "名落孙山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3403,
    "question": "278,650,370,380",
    "answer": "罪大恶极",
    "explain": "罪大恶极"
  },
  {
    "level": 3404,
    "question": "641,82,641,478",
    "answer": "十全十美",
    "explain": "十全十美"
  },
  {
    "level": 3405,
    "question": "245,245,503,389",
    "answer": "诺诺连声",
    "explain": "诺诺连声"
  },
  {
    "level": 3406,
    "question": "457,476,222,457",
    "answer": "脚痛灸脚",
    "explain": "脚痛灸脚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3407,
    "question": "641,3,654,71",
    "answer": "姿意妄为",
    "explain": "姿意妄为"
  },
  {
    "level": 3408,
    "question": "527,579,746,167",
    "answer": "奋不顾身",
    "explain": "奋不顾身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3409,
    "question": "499,495,47,431",
    "answer": "珠沉玉碎",
    "explain": "珠沉玉碎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3410,
    "question": "528,2,160,242",
    "answer": "利令智昏",
    "explain": "利令智昏"
  },
  {
    "level": 3411,
    "question": "565,443,273,236",
    "answer": "尺幅万里",
    "explain": "尺幅万里"
  },
  {
    "level": 3412,
    "question": "768,821,821,528",
    "answer": "吞言咽理",
    "explain": "吞言咽理"
  },
  {
    "level": 3413,
    "question": "565,176,11,183",
    "answer": "策名就列",
    "explain": "策名就列"
  },
  {
    "level": 3414,
    "question": "5,376,819,752",
    "answer": "三阳开泰",
    "explain": "三阳开泰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3415,
    "question": "182,245,562,389",
    "answer": "海内鼎沸",
    "explain": "海内鼎沸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3416,
    "question": "120,579,71,183",
    "answer": "下不为例",
    "explain": "下不为例"
  },
  {
    "level": 3417,
    "question": "412,476,369,425",
    "answer": "骥子龙文",
    "explain": "骥子龙文"
  },
  {
    "level": 3418,
    "question": "369,550,365,652",
    "answer": "龙盘虎踞",
    "explain": "龙盘虎踞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3419,
    "question": "7,746,579,734",
    "answer": "五谷不分",
    "explain": "五谷不分"
  },
  {
    "level": 3420,
    "question": "3,523,4,103",
    "answer": "一差二错",
    "explain": "一差二错"
  },
  {
    "level": 3421,
    "question": "425,554,130,162",
    "answer": "文章宗工",
    "explain": "文章宗工"
  },
  {
    "level": 3422,
    "question": "165,737,7,236",
    "answer": "有气无力",
    "explain": "有气无力"
  },
  {
    "level": 3423,
    "question": "90,92,457,652",
    "answer": "手舞足蹈",
    "explain": "手舞足蹈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3424,
    "question": "562,109,323,218",
    "answer": "鼎新革故",
    "explain": "鼎新革故"
  },
  {
    "level": 3425,
    "question": "3,165,580,161",
    "answer": "意犹未尽",
    "explain": "意犹未尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3426,
    "question": "377,305,705,426",
    "answer": "羊肠小道",
    "explain": "羊肠小道"
  },
  {
    "level": 3427,
    "question": "92,7,734,607",
    "answer": "别无分店",
    "explain": "别无分店"
  },
  {
    "level": 3428,
    "question": "3,737,377,377",
    "answer": "意气洋洋",
    "explain": "意气洋洋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3429,
    "question": "249,80,424,431",
    "answer": "面红耳赤",
    "explain": "面红耳赤"
  },
  {
    "level": 3430,
    "question": "109,273,482,496",
    "answer": "心荡神摇",
    "explain": "心荡神摇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3431,
    "question": "3,776,11,232",
    "answer": "移樽就教",
    "explain": "移樽就教"
  },
  {
    "level": 3432,
    "question": "443,280,554,246",
    "answer": "馈贫之粮",
    "explain": "馈贫之粮"
  },
  {
    "level": 3433,
    "question": "3,382,829,493",
    "answer": "一触即发",
    "explain": "一触即发"
  },
  {
    "level": 3434,
    "question": "599,451,7,47",
    "answer": "民胞物与",
    "explain": "民胞物与"
  },
  {
    "level": 3435,
    "question": "737,476,579,373",
    "answer": "锲而不舍",
    "explain": "锲而不舍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3436,
    "question": "161,479,553,74",
    "answer": "近墨者黑",
    "explain": "近墨者黑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3437,
    "question": "49,463,641,650",
    "answer": "失节是大",
    "explain": "失节是大"
  },
  {
    "level": 3438,
    "question": "731,478,746,463",
    "answer": "愁眉苦脸",
    "explain": "愁眉苦脸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3439,
    "question": "242,423,560,478",
    "answer": "肉眼惠眉",
    "explain": "肉眼惠眉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3440,
    "question": "119,3,209,562",
    "answer": "商彝夏鼎",
    "explain": "商彝夏鼎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3441,
    "question": "457,831,580,562",
    "answer": "步履维艰",
    "explain": "步履维艰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3442,
    "question": "366,298,339,47",
    "answer": "暴风骤雨",
    "explain": "暴风骤雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3443,
    "question": "242,501,486,262",
    "answer": "肉薄骨并",
    "explain": "肉薄骨并"
  },
  {
    "level": 3444,
    "question": "821,476,165,594",
    "answer": "言而有信",
    "explain": "言而有信"
  },
  {
    "level": 3445,
    "question": "579,161,460,67",
    "answer": "不近人情",
    "explain": "不近人情"
  },
  {
    "level": 3446,
    "question": "130,109,480,356",
    "answer": "众心如城",
    "explain": "众心如城"
  },
  {
    "level": 3447,
    "question": "565,554,470,3",
    "answer": "断章取义",
    "explain": "断章取义"
  },
  {
    "level": 3448,
    "question": "423,557,75,176",
    "answer": "金榜题名",
    "explain": "金榜题名"
  },
  {
    "level": 3449,
    "question": "624,624,71,176",
    "answer": "察察为明",
    "explain": "察察为明"
  },
  {
    "level": 3450,
    "question": "640,426,776,161",
    "answer": "师道尊严",
    "explain": "师道尊严"
  },
  {
    "level": 3451,
    "question": "641,476,579,502",
    "answer": "食而不化",
    "explain": "食而不化"
  },
  {
    "level": 3452,
    "question": "461,546,426,219",
    "answer": "肤皮潦草",
    "explain": "肤皮潦草"
  },
  {
    "level": 3453,
    "question": "5,553,7,402",
    "answer": "三纸无驴",
    "explain": "三纸无驴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3454,
    "question": "410,460,147,167",
    "answer": "容头过身",
    "explain": "容头过身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3455,
    "question": "324,460,486,737",
    "answer": "垂头丧气",
    "explain": "垂头丧气"
  },
  {
    "level": 3456,
    "question": "7,412,734,641",
    "answer": "五马分尸",
    "explain": "五马分尸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3457,
    "question": "530,3,7,4",
    "answer": "独一无二",
    "explain": "独一无二"
  },
  {
    "level": 3458,
    "question": "109,776,734,176",
    "answer": "爱憎分明",
    "explain": "爱憎分明"
  },
  {
    "level": 3459,
    "question": "423,579,453,423",
    "answer": "目不邪视",
    "explain": "目不邪视"
  },
  {
    "level": 3460,
    "question": "176,43,71,213",
    "answer": "明日黄花",
    "explain": "明日黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 3461,
    "question": "482,771,1,167",
    "answer": "谦虚谨慎",
    "explain": "谦虚谨慎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3462,
    "question": "647,174,650,565",
    "answer": "火伞高张",
    "explain": "火伞高张"
  },
  {
    "level": 3463,
    "question": "167,380,501,501",
    "answer": "生机勃勃",
    "explain": "生机勃勃"
  },
  {
    "level": 3464,
    "question": "402,37,412,38",
    "answer": "驴前马后",
    "explain": "驴前马后"
  },
  {
    "level": 3465,
    "question": "737,182,480,696",
    "answer": "气涌如山",
    "explain": "气涌如山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3466,
    "question": "246,571,188,73",
    "answer": "返本还原",
    "explain": "返本还原"
  },
  {
    "level": 3467,
    "question": "3,579,94,236",
    "answer": "一泻千里",
    "explain": "一泻千里"
  },
  {
    "level": 3468,
    "question": "389,312,737,333",
    "answer": "声应气求",
    "explain": "声应气求"
  },
  {
    "level": 3469,
    "question": "94,162,94,411",
    "answer": "毕恭毕敬",
    "explain": "毕恭毕敬"
  },
  {
    "level": 3470,
    "question": "776,399,7,663",
    "answer": "宁缺毋滥",
    "explain": "宁缺毋滥"
  },
  {
    "level": 3471,
    "question": "343,426,130,403",
    "answer": "家道中落",
    "explain": "家道中落"
  },
  {
    "level": 3472,
    "question": "555,218,555,495",
    "answer": "随俗浮沉",
    "explain": "随俗浮沉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3473,
    "question": "3,47,821,567",
    "answer": "溢于言表",
    "explain": "溢于言表"
  },
  {
    "level": 3474,
    "question": "131,7,460,821",
    "answer": "荒无人烟",
    "explain": "荒无人烟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3475,
    "question": "73,73,579,565",
    "answer": "源源不断",
    "explain": "源源不断"
  },
  {
    "level": 3476,
    "question": "435,306,554,382",
    "answer": "将伯之助",
    "explain": "将伯之助"
  },
  {
    "level": 3477,
    "question": "246,641,650,380",
    "answer": "完事大吉",
    "explain": "完事大吉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3478,
    "question": "734,425,579,470",
    "answer": "分文不取",
    "explain": "分文不取"
  },
  {
    "level": 3479,
    "question": "423,5,486,336",
    "answer": "眼馋肚饱",
    "explain": "眼馋肚饱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3480,
    "question": "106,785,106,821",
    "answer": "问长问短",
    "explain": "问长问短"
  },
  {
    "level": 3481,
    "question": "704,650,436,506",
    "answer": "兴高采烈",
    "explain": "兴高采烈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3482,
    "question": "374,801,652,412",
    "answer": "香车宝马",
    "explain": "香车宝马"
  },
  {
    "level": 3483,
    "question": "101,391,77,460",
    "answer": "冷语冰人",
    "explain": "冷语冰人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3484,
    "question": "821,112,458,387",
    "answer": "言出祸从",
    "explain": "言出祸从"
  },
  {
    "level": 3485,
    "question": "722,147,94,281",
    "answer": "知过必改",
    "explain": "知过必改"
  },
  {
    "level": 3486,
    "question": "431,376,71,412",
    "answer": "指鹿为马",
    "explain": "指鹿为马"
  },
  {
    "level": 3487,
    "question": "650,696,1,831",
    "answer": "高山景行",
    "explain": "高山景行"
  },
  {
    "level": 3488,
    "question": "209,47,423,1",
    "answer": "桑榆暮景",
    "explain": "桑榆暮景"
  },
  {
    "level": 3489,
    "question": "247,175,5,336",
    "answer": "半夜三更",
    "explain": "半夜三更"
  },
  {
    "level": 3490,
    "question": "482,470,339,482",
    "answer": "神乎其神",
    "explain": "神乎其神"
  },
  {
    "level": 3491,
    "question": "3,501,580,280",
    "answer": "一波未平",
    "explain": "一波未平"
  },
  {
    "level": 3492,
    "question": "416,304,25,486",
    "answer": "蟾宫折挂",
    "explain": "蟾宫折挂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3493,
    "question": "89,480,49,647",
    "answer": "飞蛾扑火",
    "explain": "飞蛾扑火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3494,
    "question": "174,389,486,73",
    "answer": "色若死灰",
    "explain": "色若死灰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3495,
    "question": "367,431,159,527",
    "answer": "涂脂抹粉",
    "explain": "涂脂抹粉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3496,
    "question": "165,647,431,170",
    "answer": "悠然自得",
    "explain": "悠然自得"
  },
  {
    "level": 3497,
    "question": "821,705,423,154",
    "answer": "短小精悍",
    "explain": "短小精悍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3498,
    "question": "5,5,4,4",
    "answer": "三三两两",
    "explain": "三三两两"
  },
  {
    "level": 3499,
    "question": "336,242,245,651",
    "answer": "外柔内刚",
    "explain": "外柔内刚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3500,
    "question": "389,543,641,97",
    "answer": "声价十倍",
    "explain": "声价十倍"
  },
  {
    "level": 3501,
    "question": "531,398,113,531",
    "answer": "想了又想",
    "explain": "想了又想"
  },
  {
    "level": 3502,
    "question": "219,207,399,101",
    "answer": "草木皆兵",
    "explain": "草木皆兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3503,
    "question": "3,431,611,389",
    "answer": "以指挠沸",
    "explain": "以指挠沸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3504,
    "question": "45,380,44,249",
    "answer": "天机云锦",
    "explain": "天机云锦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3505,
    "question": "777,380,831,641",
    "answer": "见机行事",
    "explain": "见机行事"
  },
  {
    "level": 3506,
    "question": "841,167,431,435",
    "answer": "洁身自好",
    "explain": "洁身自好"
  },
  {
    "level": 3507,
    "question": "109,423,242,459",
    "answer": "心惊肉跳",
    "explain": "心惊肉跳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3508,
    "question": "47,109,336,641",
    "answer": "洒心更始",
    "explain": "洒心更始"
  },
  {
    "level": 3509,
    "question": "480,425,339,460",
    "answer": "如闻其人",
    "explain": "如闻其人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3510,
    "question": "381,476,93,109",
    "answer": "狼子野心",
    "explain": "狼子野心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3511,
    "question": "3,812,298,493",
    "answer": "议论风发",
    "explain": "议论风发"
  },
  {
    "level": 3512,
    "question": "93,322,562,389",
    "answer": "笙歌鼎沸",
    "explain": "笙歌鼎沸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3513,
    "question": "647,737,258,409",
    "answer": "火气乱冒",
    "explain": "火气乱冒"
  },
  {
    "level": 3514,
    "question": "5,183,10,471",
    "answer": "三灾八难",
    "explain": "三灾八难"
  },
  {
    "level": 3515,
    "question": "647,478,554,380",
    "answer": "燃眉之急",
    "explain": "燃眉之急"
  },
  {
    "level": 3516,
    "question": "232,380,476,101",
    "answer": "相机而动",
    "explain": "相机而动"
  },
  {
    "level": 3517,
    "question": "94,495,317,109",
    "answer": "碧血丹心",
    "explain": "碧血丹心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3518,
    "question": "565,821,423,785",
    "answer": "尺短寸长",
    "explain": "尺短寸长"
  },
  {
    "level": 3519,
    "question": "380,298,366,47",
    "answer": "疾风暴雨",
    "explain": "疾风暴雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3520,
    "question": "777,737,47,460",
    "answer": "见弃于人",
    "explain": "见弃于人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3521,
    "question": "203,160,313,283",
    "answer": "形只影单",
    "explain": "形只影单"
  },
  {
    "level": 3522,
    "question": "460,3,451,460",
    "answer": "宽以待人",
    "explain": "宽以待人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3523,
    "question": "423,737,495,495",
    "answer": "暮气沉沉",
    "explain": "暮气沉沉"
  },
  {
    "level": 3524,
    "question": "409,226,381,652",
    "answer": "鼠窃狗盗",
    "explain": "鼠窃狗盗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3525,
    "question": "276,411,236,306",
    "answer": "背井离乡",
    "explain": "背井离乡"
  },
  {
    "level": 3526,
    "question": "77,45,101,476",
    "answer": "冰天雪地",
    "explain": "冰天雪地"
  },
  {
    "level": 3527,
    "question": "3,559,476,11",
    "answer": "一挥而就",
    "explain": "一挥而就"
  },
  {
    "level": 3528,
    "question": "435,69,461,460",
    "answer": "强作解人",
    "explain": "强作解人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3529,
    "question": "210,109,297,47",
    "answer": "清心寡欲",
    "explain": "清心寡欲"
  },
  {
    "level": 3530,
    "question": "567,236,232,3",
    "answer": "表里相依",
    "explain": "表里相依"
  },
  {
    "level": 3531,
    "question": "213,476,579,641",
    "answer": "华而不实",
    "explain": "华而不实"
  },
  {
    "level": 3532,
    "question": "246,446,7,305",
    "answer": "反复无常",
    "explain": "反复无常"
  },
  {
    "level": 3533,
    "question": "641,47,634,580",
    "answer": "事与愿违",
    "explain": "事与愿违"
  },
  {
    "level": 3534,
    "question": "82,218,722,109",
    "answer": "温故知新",
    "explain": "温故知新"
  },
  {
    "level": 3535,
    "question": "746,111,426,342",
    "answer": "鼓腹含游",
    "explain": "鼓腹含游"
  },
  {
    "level": 3536,
    "question": "650,160,650,182",
    "answer": "大智大勇",
    "explain": "大智大勇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3537,
    "question": "7,628,579,450",
    "answer": "无所不包",
    "explain": "无所不包"
  },
  {
    "level": 3538,
    "question": "411,411,165,45",
    "answer": "津津有味",
    "explain": "津津有味"
  },
  {
    "level": 3539,
    "question": "270,647,177,45",
    "answer": "热火朝天",
    "explain": "热火朝天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3540,
    "question": "832,832,47,389",
    "answer": "亭亭玉立",
    "explain": "亭亭玉立"
  },
  {
    "level": 3541,
    "question": "77,82,222,555",
    "answer": "冰壶秋月",
    "explain": "冰壶秋月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3542,
    "question": "562,25,576,446",
    "answer": "鼎折餗覆",
    "explain": "鼎折餗覆"
  },
  {
    "level": 3543,
    "question": "369,832,365,457",
    "answer": "龙骧虎步",
    "explain": "龙骧虎步"
  },
  {
    "level": 3544,
    "question": "5,177,539,369",
    "answer": "三朝元老",
    "explain": "三朝元老"
  },
  {
    "level": 3545,
    "question": "476,256,460,731",
    "answer": "地狭人稠",
    "explain": "地狭人稠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3546,
    "question": "88,363,325,326",
    "answer": "对牛弹琴",
    "explain": "对牛弹琴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3547,
    "question": "222,97,246,439",
    "answer": "秋荼密网",
    "explain": "秋荼密网"
  },
  {
    "level": 3548,
    "question": "652,389,45,656",
    "answer": "倒凤颠鸾",
    "explain": "倒凤颠鸾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3549,
    "question": "94,460,628,431",
    "answer": "千人所指",
    "explain": "千人所指"
  },
  {
    "level": 3550,
    "question": "82,445,446,103",
    "answer": "全军覆灭",
    "explain": "全军覆灭"
  },
  {
    "level": 3551,
    "question": "176,186,580,65",
    "answer": "明德惟馨",
    "explain": "明德惟馨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3552,
    "question": "423,659,49,426",
    "answer": "惊惶失措",
    "explain": "惊惶失措"
  },
  {
    "level": 3553,
    "question": "408,474,655,246",
    "answer": "徒劳往返",
    "explain": "徒劳往返"
  },
  {
    "level": 3554,
    "question": "213,374,767,460",
    "answer": "花香醉人",
    "explain": "花香醉人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3555,
    "question": "37,322,38,147",
    "answer": "前因后果",
    "explain": "前因后果"
  },
  {
    "level": 3556,
    "question": "460,696,482,45",
    "answer": "人定胜天",
    "explain": "人定胜天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3557,
    "question": "605,276,232,655",
    "answer": "项背相望",
    "explain": "项背相望"
  },
  {
    "level": 3558,
    "question": "641,3,246,230",
    "answer": "事以密成",
    "explain": "事以密成"
  },
  {
    "level": 3559,
    "question": "655,275,97,382",
    "answer": "关怀备注",
    "explain": "关怀备注"
  },
  {
    "level": 3560,
    "question": "426,71,426,74",
    "answer": "说黄道黑",
    "explain": "说黄道黑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3561,
    "question": "478,579,482,92",
    "answer": "美不胜收",
    "explain": "美不胜收"
  },
  {
    "level": 3562,
    "question": "3,246,94,423",
    "answer": "一饭千金",
    "explain": "一饭千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 3563,
    "question": "109,641,249,696",
    "answer": "心慈面善",
    "explain": "心慈面善"
  },
  {
    "level": 3564,
    "question": "527,641,3,109",
    "answer": "粉饰一新",
    "explain": "粉饰一新"
  },
  {
    "level": 3565,
    "question": "3,620,423,460",
    "answer": "一鸣惊人",
    "explain": "一鸣惊人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3566,
    "question": "313,313,318,318",
    "answer": "影影绰绰",
    "explain": "影影绰绰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3567,
    "question": "3,460,409,423",
    "answer": "獐头鼠目",
    "explain": "獐头鼠目"
  },
  {
    "level": 3568,
    "question": "389,425,147,67",
    "answer": "声闻过情",
    "explain": "声闻过情"
  },
  {
    "level": 3569,
    "question": "176,432,35,146",
    "answer": "明争暗斗",
    "explain": "明争暗斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3570,
    "question": "438,641,7,438",
    "answer": "盖世无双",
    "explain": "盖世无双"
  },
  {
    "level": 3571,
    "question": "94,426,533,49",
    "answer": "千娇百媚",
    "explain": "千娇百媚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3572,
    "question": "380,647,230,214",
    "answer": "积少成多",
    "explain": "积少成多"
  },
  {
    "level": 3573,
    "question": "489,486,106,380",
    "answer": "吊死问疾",
    "explain": "吊死问疾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3574,
    "question": "290,460,476,461",
    "answer": "迎刃而解",
    "explain": "迎刃而解"
  },
  {
    "level": 3575,
    "question": "236,88,336,503",
    "answer": "里勾外连",
    "explain": "里勾外连"
  },
  {
    "level": 3576,
    "question": "439,819,5,249",
    "answer": "网开三面",
    "explain": "网开三面"
  },
  {
    "level": 3577,
    "question": "44,487,554,92",
    "answer": "云泥之别",
    "explain": "云泥之别"
  },
  {
    "level": 3578,
    "question": "261,460,812,457",
    "answer": "品头论足",
    "explain": "品头论足"
  },
  {
    "level": 3579,
    "question": "737,35,319,176",
    "answer": "弃暗投明",
    "explain": "弃暗投明"
  },
  {
    "level": 3580,
    "question": "432,785,812,821",
    "answer": "争长论短",
    "explain": "争长论短"
  },
  {
    "level": 3581,
    "question": "197,696,218,230",
    "answer": "约定俗成",
    "explain": "约定俗成"
  },
  {
    "level": 3582,
    "question": "92,443,322,696",
    "answer": "舞衫歌扇",
    "explain": "舞衫歌扇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3583,
    "question": "501,88,49,773",
    "answer": "进退失据",
    "explain": "进退失据"
  },
  {
    "level": 3584,
    "question": "44,635,554,655",
    "answer": "云霓之望",
    "explain": "云霓之望"
  },
  {
    "level": 3585,
    "question": "248,176,130,336",
    "answer": "驰名中外",
    "explain": "驰名中外"
  },
  {
    "level": 3586,
    "question": "162,25,652,161",
    "answer": "弓折刀尽",
    "explain": "弓折刀尽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3587,
    "question": "9,457,230,641",
    "answer": "七步成诗",
    "explain": "七步成诗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3588,
    "question": "8,503,655,246",
    "answer": "流连忘返",
    "explain": "流连忘返"
  },
  {
    "level": 3589,
    "question": "318,480,563,426",
    "answer": "捉贼要脏",
    "explain": "捉贼要脏"
  },
  {
    "level": 3590,
    "question": "652,176,35,641",
    "answer": "盗名暗世",
    "explain": "盗名暗世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3591,
    "question": "381,389,460,6",
    "answer": "狗仗人势",
    "explain": "狗仗人势"
  },
  {
    "level": 3592,
    "question": "431,650,431,650",
    "answer": "自高自大",
    "explain": "自高自大"
  },
  {
    "level": 3593,
    "question": "696,78,45,1",
    "answer": "奉命唯谨",
    "explain": "奉命唯谨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3594,
    "question": "3,249,554,567",
    "answer": "一面之词",
    "explain": "一面之词"
  },
  {
    "level": 3595,
    "question": "523,5,103,6",
    "answer": "差三错四",
    "explain": "差三错四"
  },
  {
    "level": 3596,
    "question": "562,746,318,696",
    "answer": "艰苦卓绝",
    "explain": "艰苦卓绝"
  },
  {
    "level": 3597,
    "question": "821,831,579,3",
    "answer": "言行不一",
    "explain": "言行不一"
  },
  {
    "level": 3598,
    "question": "479,650,3,521",
    "answer": "魔高一丈",
    "explain": "魔高一丈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3599,
    "question": "480,72,842,424",
    "answer": "如雷贯耳",
    "explain": "如雷贯耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3600,
    "question": "556,113,7,722",
    "answer": "年幼无知",
    "explain": "年幼无知"
  },
  {
    "level": 3601,
    "question": "231,7,3,565",
    "answer": "算无遗策",
    "explain": "算无遗策"
  },
  {
    "level": 3602,
    "question": "3,249,480,11",
    "answer": "一面如旧",
    "explain": "一面如旧"
  },
  {
    "level": 3603,
    "question": "370,310,650,101",
    "answer": "鹅毛大雪",
    "explain": "鹅毛大雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3604,
    "question": "269,119,69,258",
    "answer": "犯上作乱",
    "explain": "犯上作乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3605,
    "question": "316,90,389,377",
    "answer": "顺手牵羊",
    "explain": "顺手牵羊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3606,
    "question": "544,737,825,482",
    "answer": "屏气凝神",
    "explain": "屏气凝神"
  },
  {
    "level": 3607,
    "question": "705,651,554,343",
    "answer": "小康之家",
    "explain": "小康之家"
  },
  {
    "level": 3608,
    "question": "528,431,737,491",
    "answer": "理直气壮",
    "explain": "理直气壮"
  },
  {
    "level": 3609,
    "question": "167,47,165,469",
    "answer": "生与忧患",
    "explain": "生与忧患"
  },
  {
    "level": 3610,
    "question": "101,503,458,463",
    "answer": "兵连祸结",
    "explain": "兵连祸结"
  },
  {
    "level": 3611,
    "question": "580,109,554,812",
    "answer": "违心之论",
    "explain": "违心之论"
  },
  {
    "level": 3612,
    "question": "447,130,522,522",
    "answer": "庸中佼佼",
    "explain": "庸中佼佼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3613,
    "question": "94,565,533,162",
    "answer": "千疮百孔",
    "explain": "千疮百孔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3614,
    "question": "827,411,47,696",
    "answer": "纶巾羽扇",
    "explain": "纶巾羽扇"
  },
  {
    "level": 3615,
    "question": "650,476,7,6",
    "answer": "大公无私",
    "explain": "大公无私"
  },
  {
    "level": 3616,
    "question": "704,78,655,45",
    "answer": "性命关天",
    "explain": "性命关天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3617,
    "question": "470,650,812,297",
    "answer": "曲高和寡",
    "explain": "曲高和寡"
  },
  {
    "level": 3618,
    "question": "3,254,205,499",
    "answer": "一串骊珠",
    "explain": "一串骊珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3619,
    "question": "423,486,480,394",
    "answer": "视死如归",
    "explain": "视死如归"
  },
  {
    "level": 3620,
    "question": "95,411,653,380",
    "answer": "披荆斩棘",
    "explain": "披荆斩棘"
  },
  {
    "level": 3621,
    "question": "43,501,177,696",
    "answer": "日薄西山",
    "explain": "日薄西山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3622,
    "question": "435,242,248,565",
    "answer": "好肉剜疮",
    "explain": "好肉剜疮"
  },
  {
    "level": 3623,
    "question": "45,439,73,73",
    "answer": "天网恢恢",
    "explain": "天网恢恢"
  },
  {
    "level": 3624,
    "question": "130,652,446,800",
    "answer": "重蹈覆辙",
    "explain": "重蹈覆辙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3625,
    "question": "44,147,45,162",
    "answer": "云过天空",
    "explain": "云过天空"
  },
  {
    "level": 3626,
    "question": "785,556,746,555",
    "answer": "长年累月",
    "explain": "长年累月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3627,
    "question": "423,91,314,231",
    "answer": "精打细算",
    "explain": "精打细算"
  },
  {
    "level": 3628,
    "question": "389,3,431,821",
    "answer": "仗义执言",
    "explain": "仗义执言"
  },
  {
    "level": 3629,
    "question": "343,280,480,821",
    "answer": "家贫如洗",
    "explain": "家贫如洗"
  },
  {
    "level": 3630,
    "question": "821,554,648,648",
    "answer": "言之凿凿",
    "explain": "言之凿凿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3631,
    "question": "236,112,336,501",
    "answer": "里出外进",
    "explain": "里出外进"
  },
  {
    "level": 3632,
    "question": "411,580,579,734",
    "answer": "泾渭不分",
    "explain": "泾渭不分"
  },
  {
    "level": 3633,
    "question": "533,457,554,130",
    "answer": "百足之虫",
    "explain": "百足之虫"
  },
  {
    "level": 3634,
    "question": "11,813,162,230",
    "answer": "九转功成",
    "explain": "九转功成"
  },
  {
    "level": 3635,
    "question": "496,425,753,555",
    "answer": "咬文嚼字",
    "explain": "咬文嚼字"
  },
  {
    "level": 3636,
    "question": "6,641,799,650",
    "answer": "兹事体大",
    "explain": "兹事体大"
  },
  {
    "level": 3637,
    "question": "435,571,463,342",
    "answer": "强本节用",
    "explain": "强本节用"
  },
  {
    "level": 3638,
    "question": "95,109,232,538",
    "answer": "披心相付",
    "explain": "披心相付"
  },
  {
    "level": 3639,
    "question": "322,579,6,207",
    "answer": "乐不思蜀",
    "explain": "乐不思蜀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3640,
    "question": "476,162,109,6",
    "answer": "挖空心思",
    "explain": "挖空心思"
  },
  {
    "level": 3641,
    "question": "182,647,554,130",
    "answer": "水火之中",
    "explain": "水火之中"
  },
  {
    "level": 3642,
    "question": "458,94,130,120",
    "answer": "祸必重来",
    "explain": "祸必重来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3643,
    "question": "298,125,650,47",
    "answer": "瓢泼大雨",
    "explain": "瓢泼大雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3644,
    "question": "531,170,131,264",
    "answer": "想得荒唐",
    "explain": "想得荒唐"
  },
  {
    "level": 3645,
    "question": "49,423,91,436",
    "answer": "没精打采",
    "explain": "没精打采"
  },
  {
    "level": 3646,
    "question": "176,183,37,409",
    "answer": "名列前茅",
    "explain": "名列前茅"
  },
  {
    "level": 3647,
    "question": "777,696,272,495",
    "answer": "见缝插针",
    "explain": "见缝插针"
  },
  {
    "level": 3648,
    "question": "565,426,463,427",
    "answer": "张口结舌",
    "explain": "张口结舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3649,
    "question": "478,522,230,318",
    "answer": "弄巧成拙",
    "explain": "弄巧成拙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3650,
    "question": "246,641,45,460",
    "answer": "顽石点头",
    "explain": "顽石点头"
  },
  {
    "level": 3651,
    "question": "89,480,319,647",
    "answer": "飞蛾投火",
    "explain": "飞蛾投火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3652,
    "question": "314,737,377,377",
    "answer": "喜气洋洋",
    "explain": "喜气洋洋"
  },
  {
    "level": 3653,
    "question": "401,560,842,45",
    "answer": "融会贯通",
    "explain": "融会贯通"
  },
  {
    "level": 3654,
    "question": "542,722,628,426",
    "answer": "靡知所措",
    "explain": "靡知所措"
  },
  {
    "level": 3655,
    "question": "7,799,319,476",
    "answer": "五体投地",
    "explain": "五体投地"
  },
  {
    "level": 3656,
    "question": "812,579,270,278",
    "answer": "罚不当罪",
    "explain": "罚不当罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3657,
    "question": "103,379,741,378",
    "answer": "杀鸡吓猴",
    "explain": "杀鸡吓猴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3658,
    "question": "379,310,545,546",
    "answer": "鸡毛蒜皮",
    "explain": "鸡毛蒜皮"
  },
  {
    "level": 3659,
    "question": "112,525,460,278",
    "answer": "出入人罪",
    "explain": "出入人罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3660,
    "question": "533,576,579,821",
    "answer": "百读不厌",
    "explain": "百读不厌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3661,
    "question": "229,307,460,734",
    "answer": "瓜剖豆分",
    "explain": "瓜剖豆分"
  },
  {
    "level": 3662,
    "question": "734,275,650,431",
    "answer": "胸怀大志",
    "explain": "胸怀大志"
  },
  {
    "level": 3663,
    "question": "470,554,47,599",
    "answer": "取之于民",
    "explain": "取之于民"
  },
  {
    "level": 3664,
    "question": "411,308,45,182",
    "answer": "蜻蜓点水",
    "explain": "蜻蜓点水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3665,
    "question": "656,605,389,380",
    "answer": "鸾翔凤集",
    "explain": "鸾翔凤集"
  },
  {
    "level": 3666,
    "question": "3,398,533,398",
    "answer": "一了百了",
    "explain": "一了百了"
  },
  {
    "level": 3667,
    "question": "214,436,214,3",
    "answer": "多才多艺",
    "explain": "多才多艺"
  },
  {
    "level": 3668,
    "question": "3,776,112,641",
    "answer": "一佛出世",
    "explain": "一佛出世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3669,
    "question": "129,746,92,389",
    "answer": "印累绶若",
    "explain": "印累绶若"
  },
  {
    "level": 3670,
    "question": "480,767,480,431",
    "answer": "如醉如痴",
    "explain": "如醉如痴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3671,
    "question": "205,205,799,423",
    "answer": "历历在目",
    "explain": "历历在目"
  },
  {
    "level": 3672,
    "question": "43,246,579,482",
    "answer": "冥顽不灵",
    "explain": "冥顽不灵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3673,
    "question": "170,423,501,565",
    "answer": "得寸进尺",
    "explain": "得寸进尺"
  },
  {
    "level": 3674,
    "question": "165,555,476,605",
    "answer": "有福同享",
    "explain": "有福同享"
  },
  {
    "level": 3675,
    "question": "531,170,181,258",
    "answer": "想得混乱",
    "explain": "想得混乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3676,
    "question": "554,530,554,408",
    "answer": "章句之徒",
    "explain": "章句之徒"
  },
  {
    "level": 3677,
    "question": "594,90,834,120",
    "answer": "信手拈来",
    "explain": "信手拈来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3678,
    "question": "411,647,165,173",
    "answer": "井然有序",
    "explain": "井然有序"
  },
  {
    "level": 3679,
    "question": "781,771,476,525",
    "answer": "乘虚而入",
    "explain": "乘虚而入"
  },
  {
    "level": 3680,
    "question": "545,7,628,112",
    "answer": "计无所出",
    "explain": "计无所出"
  },
  {
    "level": 3681,
    "question": "182,495,579,45",
    "answer": "水泄不通",
    "explain": "水泄不通"
  },
  {
    "level": 3682,
    "question": "431,799,6,66",
    "answer": "志在四方",
    "explain": "志在四方"
  },
  {
    "level": 3683,
    "question": "45,834,476,276",
    "answer": "天南地北",
    "explain": "天南地北"
  },
  {
    "level": 3684,
    "question": "47,47,480,167",
    "answer": "栩栩如生",
    "explain": "栩栩如生"
  },
  {
    "level": 3685,
    "question": "387,411,11,460",
    "answer": "从井救人",
    "explain": "从井救人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3686,
    "question": "641,398,554,280",
    "answer": "尸鸠之平",
    "explain": "尸鸠之平"
  },
  {
    "level": 3687,
    "question": "3,470,476,162",
    "answer": "异曲同工",
    "explain": "异曲同工"
  },
  {
    "level": 3688,
    "question": "3,555,3,499",
    "answer": "一字一珠",
    "explain": "一字一珠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3689,
    "question": "773,71,380,165",
    "answer": "据为己有",
    "explain": "据为己有"
  },
  {
    "level": 3690,
    "question": "482,833,479,439",
    "answer": "谦让末遑",
    "explain": "谦让末遑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3691,
    "question": "389,658,620,650",
    "answer": "肥遁鸣高",
    "explain": "肥遁鸣高"
  },
  {
    "level": 3692,
    "question": "36,101,310,310",
    "answer": "白雪皑皑",
    "explain": "白雪皑皑"
  },
  {
    "level": 3693,
    "question": "5,446,339,594",
    "answer": "三复其信",
    "explain": "三复其信"
  },
  {
    "level": 3694,
    "question": "525,411,655,45",
    "answer": "入井望天",
    "explain": "入井望天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3695,
    "question": "3,398,5,246",
    "answer": "一隅三反",
    "explain": "一隅三反"
  },
  {
    "level": 3696,
    "question": "236,75,273,236",
    "answer": "离题万里",
    "explain": "离题万里"
  },
  {
    "level": 3697,
    "question": "298,812,43,528",
    "answer": "风和日丽",
    "explain": "风和日丽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3698,
    "question": "461,506,131,471",
    "answer": "解纷排难",
    "explain": "解纷排难"
  },
  {
    "level": 3699,
    "question": "210,3,495,478",
    "answer": "春意正浓",
    "explain": "春意正浓"
  },
  {
    "level": 3700,
    "question": "173,173,410,410",
    "answer": "朦朦胧胧",
    "explain": "朦朦胧胧"
  },
  {
    "level": 3701,
    "question": "468,387,426,525",
    "answer": "病从口入",
    "explain": "病从口入"
  },
  {
    "level": 3702,
    "question": "73,460,647,182",
    "answer": "源头活水",
    "explain": "源头活水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3703,
    "question": "87,460,579,10",
    "answer": "坚忍不拔",
    "explain": "坚忍不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3704,
    "question": "641,554,10,11",
    "answer": "十之八九",
    "explain": "十之八九"
  },
  {
    "level": 3705,
    "question": "617,6,159,531",
    "answer": "静思默想",
    "explain": "静思默想"
  },
  {
    "level": 3706,
    "question": "655,476,230,369",
    "answer": "望子成龙",
    "explain": "望子成龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3707,
    "question": "376,380,700,380",
    "answer": "屦及剑及",
    "explain": "屦及剑及"
  },
  {
    "level": 3708,
    "question": "119,120,339,90",
    "answer": "上下其手",
    "explain": "上下其手"
  },
  {
    "level": 3709,
    "question": "369,89,389,92",
    "answer": "龙飞凤舞",
    "explain": "龙飞凤舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3710,
    "question": "555,112,101,696",
    "answer": "月出东山",
    "explain": "月出东山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3711,
    "question": "423,7,776,425",
    "answer": "偃武修文",
    "explain": "偃武修文"
  },
  {
    "level": 3712,
    "question": "369,373,89,101",
    "answer": "龙蛇飞动",
    "explain": "龙蛇飞动"
  },
  {
    "level": 3713,
    "question": "236,579,387,109",
    "answer": "力不从心",
    "explain": "力不从心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3714,
    "question": "439,45,38,491",
    "answer": "皇天后土",
    "explain": "皇天后土"
  },
  {
    "level": 3715,
    "question": "210,72,734,734",
    "answer": "春雷滚滚",
    "explain": "春雷滚滚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3716,
    "question": "176,324,38,641",
    "answer": "名垂后世",
    "explain": "名垂后世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3717,
    "question": "559,647,480,380",
    "answer": "苍髯如戟",
    "explain": "苍髯如戟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3718,
    "question": "1,821,167,831",
    "answer": "谨言慎行",
    "explain": "谨言慎行"
  },
  {
    "level": 3719,
    "question": "380,480,230,647",
    "answer": "急如星火",
    "explain": "急如星火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3720,
    "question": "273,312,482,317",
    "answer": "万应灵丹",
    "explain": "万应灵丹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3721,
    "question": "389,389,377,377",
    "answer": "沸沸扬扬",
    "explain": "沸沸扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 3722,
    "question": "495,468,641,773",
    "answer": "真凭实据",
    "explain": "真凭实据"
  },
  {
    "level": 3723,
    "question": "8,66,533,641",
    "answer": "流芳百世",
    "explain": "流芳百世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3724,
    "question": "45,705,495,271",
    "answer": "通宵达旦",
    "explain": "通宵达旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3725,
    "question": "368,409,476,249",
    "answer": "猫鼠同眠",
    "explain": "猫鼠同眠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3726,
    "question": "45,555,209,672",
    "answer": "田月桑时",
    "explain": "田月桑时"
  },
  {
    "level": 3727,
    "question": "3,696,579,3",
    "answer": "一定不易",
    "explain": "一定不易"
  },
  {
    "level": 3728,
    "question": "446,273,652,647",
    "answer": "赴汤蹈火",
    "explain": "赴汤蹈火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3729,
    "question": "118,43,71,213",
    "answer": "昨日黄花",
    "explain": "昨日黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 3730,
    "question": "210,298,4,821",
    "answer": "清风两袖",
    "explain": "清风两袖"
  },
  {
    "level": 3731,
    "question": "3,176,476,641",
    "answer": "异名同实",
    "explain": "异名同实"
  },
  {
    "level": 3732,
    "question": "519,322,696,554",
    "answer": "等因奉此",
    "explain": "等因奉此"
  },
  {
    "level": 3733,
    "question": "812,279,161,831",
    "answer": "论甘忌辛",
    "explain": "论甘忌辛"
  },
  {
    "level": 3734,
    "question": "672,579,799,120",
    "answer": "时不在来",
    "explain": "时不在来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3735,
    "question": "3,457,357,45",
    "answer": "一步登天",
    "explain": "一步登天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3736,
    "question": "772,431,171,207",
    "answer": "屈指可数",
    "explain": "屈指可数"
  },
  {
    "level": 3737,
    "question": "661,183,89,248",
    "answer": "狂奔飞驰",
    "explain": "狂奔飞驰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3738,
    "question": "73,203,94,525",
    "answer": "原形毕露",
    "explain": "原形毕露"
  },
  {
    "level": 3739,
    "question": "175,174,242,478",
    "answer": "夜色柔美",
    "explain": "夜色柔美"
  },
  {
    "level": 3740,
    "question": "533,167,277,576",
    "answer": "百身何赎",
    "explain": "百身何赎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3741,
    "question": "316,339,7,97",
    "answer": "攻其无备",
    "explain": "攻其无备"
  },
  {
    "level": 3742,
    "question": "180,44,270,45",
    "answer": "彩云满天",
    "explain": "彩云满天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3743,
    "question": "476,436,476,655",
    "answer": "公才公望",
    "explain": "公才公望"
  },
  {
    "level": 3744,
    "question": "163,476,71,3",
    "answer": "合而为一",
    "explain": "合而为一"
  },
  {
    "level": 3745,
    "question": "94,471,273,125",
    "answer": "千难万险",
    "explain": "千难万险"
  },
  {
    "level": 3746,
    "question": "451,460,799,7",
    "answer": "待人接物",
    "explain": "待人接物"
  },
  {
    "level": 3747,
    "question": "650,165,171,655",
    "answer": "大有可观",
    "explain": "大有可观"
  },
  {
    "level": 3748,
    "question": "323,476,93,460",
    "answer": "伏地圣人",
    "explain": "伏地圣人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3749,
    "question": "10,66,365,312",
    "answer": "八方呼应",
    "explain": "八方呼应"
  },
  {
    "level": 3750,
    "question": "25,650,426,403",
    "answer": "折槁振落",
    "explain": "折槁振落"
  },
  {
    "level": 3751,
    "question": "108,431,110,220",
    "answer": "添枝加叶",
    "explain": "添枝加叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 3752,
    "question": "130,47,752,696",
    "answer": "重于泰山",
    "explain": "重于泰山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3753,
    "question": "579,772,579,611",
    "answer": "不屈不挠",
    "explain": "不屈不挠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3754,
    "question": "812,298,314,47",
    "answer": "和风细雨",
    "explain": "和风细雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3755,
    "question": "785,167,579,369",
    "answer": "长生不老",
    "explain": "长生不老"
  },
  {
    "level": 3756,
    "question": "73,431,370,35",
    "answer": "远至迩安",
    "explain": "远至迩安"
  },
  {
    "level": 3757,
    "question": "831,251,531,528",
    "answer": "慢条斯理",
    "explain": "慢条斯理"
  },
  {
    "level": 3758,
    "question": "369,167,305,743",
    "answer": "老生常谈",
    "explain": "老生常谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3759,
    "question": "161,480,460,3",
    "answer": "尽如人意",
    "explain": "尽如人意"
  },
  {
    "level": 3760,
    "question": "503,236,441,461",
    "answer": "连里竟街",
    "explain": "连里竟街"
  },
  {
    "level": 3761,
    "question": "230,647,647,73",
    "answer": "星火燎原",
    "explain": "星火燎原"
  },
  {
    "level": 3762,
    "question": "384,45,476,327",
    "answer": "向天而唾",
    "explain": "向天而唾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3763,
    "question": "584,696,389,412",
    "answer": "寒蝉仗马",
    "explain": "寒蝉仗马"
  },
  {
    "level": 3764,
    "question": "565,439,49,426",
    "answer": "张皇失措",
    "explain": "张皇失措"
  },
  {
    "level": 3765,
    "question": "533,641,554,640",
    "answer": "百世之师",
    "explain": "百世之师"
  },
  {
    "level": 3766,
    "question": "556,167,43,11",
    "answer": "年深日久",
    "explain": "年深日久"
  },
  {
    "level": 3767,
    "question": "112,482,525,502",
    "answer": "出神入化",
    "explain": "出神入化"
  },
  {
    "level": 3768,
    "question": "379,2,381,431",
    "answer": "鸡零狗碎",
    "explain": "鸡零狗碎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3769,
    "question": "45,92,45,711",
    "answer": "畏首畏尾",
    "explain": "畏首畏尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3770,
    "question": "319,95,436,365",
    "answer": "投畀豺虎",
    "explain": "投畀豺虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3771,
    "question": "3,90,793,45",
    "answer": "一手遮天",
    "explain": "一手遮天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3772,
    "question": "44,342,6,182",
    "answer": "云游四海",
    "explain": "云游四海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3773,
    "question": "333,147,47,789",
    "answer": "求过于供",
    "explain": "求过于供"
  },
  {
    "level": 3774,
    "question": "11,82,554,120",
    "answer": "九泉之下",
    "explain": "九泉之下"
  },
  {
    "level": 3775,
    "question": "374,571,110,528",
    "answer": "变本加励",
    "explain": "变本加励"
  },
  {
    "level": 3776,
    "question": "101,174,270,298",
    "answer": "冷嘲热讽",
    "explain": "冷嘲热讽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3777,
    "question": "555,174,128,460",
    "answer": "月色迷人",
    "explain": "月色迷人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3778,
    "question": "486,207,298,210",
    "answer": "枯木逢春",
    "explain": "枯木逢春"
  },
  {
    "level": 3779,
    "question": "476,109,476,186",
    "answer": "同心同德",
    "explain": "同心同德"
  },
  {
    "level": 3780,
    "question": "461,538,380,280",
    "answer": "劫富济贫",
    "explain": "劫富济贫"
  },
  {
    "level": 3781,
    "question": "535,812,650,47",
    "answer": "滂沱大雨",
    "explain": "滂沱大雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3782,
    "question": "378,423,7,431",
    "answer": "厚颜无耻",
    "explain": "厚颜无耻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3783,
    "question": "208,222,273,384",
    "answer": "森罗万象",
    "explain": "森罗万象"
  },
  {
    "level": 3784,
    "question": "479,696,66,130",
    "answer": "摩顶放踵",
    "explain": "摩顶放踵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3785,
    "question": "450,222,273,384",
    "answer": "包罗万象",
    "explain": "包罗万象"
  },
  {
    "level": 3786,
    "question": "109,380,480,647",
    "answer": "心急如焚",
    "explain": "心急如焚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3787,
    "question": "799,560,799,73",
    "answer": "敌惠敌怨",
    "explain": "敌惠敌怨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3788,
    "question": "210,80,648,36",
    "answer": "青红皂白",
    "explain": "青红皂白"
  },
  {
    "level": 3789,
    "question": "298,207,554,6",
    "answer": "风木之思",
    "explain": "风木之思"
  },
  {
    "level": 3790,
    "question": "641,111,527,93",
    "answer": "尸横遍野",
    "explain": "尸横遍野"
  },
  {
    "level": 3791,
    "question": "230,556,746,555",
    "answer": "成年累月",
    "explain": "成年累月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3792,
    "question": "3,655,7,396",
    "answer": "一望无际",
    "explain": "一望无际"
  },
  {
    "level": 3793,
    "question": "4,162,109,746",
    "answer": "良工心苦",
    "explain": "良工心苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3794,
    "question": "237,80,8,99",
    "answer": "桃红柳绿",
    "explain": "桃红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3795,
    "question": "8,236,813,460",
    "answer": "流离转徙",
    "explain": "流离转徙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3796,
    "question": "479,304,524,277",
    "answer": "莫敢谁何",
    "explain": "莫敢谁何"
  },
  {
    "level": 3797,
    "question": "478,210,423,762",
    "answer": "眉清目秀",
    "explain": "眉清目秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3798,
    "question": "283,786,109,423",
    "answer": "胆战心惊",
    "explain": "胆战心惊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3799,
    "question": "821,553,7,278",
    "answer": "言者无罪",
    "explain": "言者无罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3800,
    "question": "45,183,460,458",
    "answer": "天灾人祸",
    "explain": "天灾人祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3801,
    "question": "6,186,5,387",
    "answer": "四德三从",
    "explain": "四德三从"
  },
  {
    "level": 3802,
    "question": "387,460,493,403",
    "answer": "从宽发落",
    "explain": "从宽发落"
  },
  {
    "level": 3803,
    "question": "11,7,554,776",
    "answer": "九五之尊",
    "explain": "九五之尊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3804,
    "question": "165,482,426,752",
    "answer": "优胜劣汰",
    "explain": "优胜劣汰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3805,
    "question": "44,342,431,480",
    "answer": "运用自如",
    "explain": "运用自如"
  },
  {
    "level": 3806,
    "question": "567,236,696,182",
    "answer": "表里山河",
    "explain": "表里山河"
  },
  {
    "level": 3807,
    "question": "94,165,3,49",
    "answer": "必有一失",
    "explain": "必有一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 3808,
    "question": "474,640,101,130",
    "answer": "劳师动众",
    "explain": "劳师动众"
  },
  {
    "level": 3809,
    "question": "3,652,4,565",
    "answer": "一刀两断",
    "explain": "一刀两断"
  },
  {
    "level": 3810,
    "question": "566,367,5,703",
    "answer": "狡兔三窟",
    "explain": "狡兔三窟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3811,
    "question": "143,426,560,426",
    "answer": "能说会道",
    "explain": "能说会道"
  },
  {
    "level": 3812,
    "question": "160,705,821,650",
    "answer": "智小言大",
    "explain": "智小言大"
  },
  {
    "level": 3813,
    "question": "3,220,95,423",
    "answer": "一叶蔽目",
    "explain": "一叶蔽目"
  },
  {
    "level": 3814,
    "question": "652,696,647,182",
    "answer": "刀山火海",
    "explain": "刀山火海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3815,
    "question": "389,246,313,45",
    "answer": "沸反盈天",
    "explain": "沸反盈天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3816,
    "question": "326,441,650,696",
    "answer": "秦镜高悬",
    "explain": "秦镜高悬"
  },
  {
    "level": 3817,
    "question": "424,468,531,157",
    "answer": "耳鬓斯磨",
    "explain": "耳鬓斯磨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3818,
    "question": "704,426,305,819",
    "answer": "笑口常开",
    "explain": "笑口常开"
  },
  {
    "level": 3819,
    "question": "425,3,722,641",
    "answer": "闻一知十",
    "explain": "闻一知十"
  },
  {
    "level": 3820,
    "question": "431,246,220,368",
    "answer": "枝繁叶茂",
    "explain": "枝繁叶茂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3821,
    "question": "3,550,47,371",
    "answer": "一盘散沙",
    "explain": "一盘散沙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3822,
    "question": "2,423,232,655",
    "answer": "另眼相看",
    "explain": "另眼相看"
  },
  {
    "level": 3823,
    "question": "565,94,423,322",
    "answer": "尺璧寸阴",
    "explain": "尺璧寸阴"
  },
  {
    "level": 3824,
    "question": "431,468,11,460",
    "answer": "治病救人",
    "explain": "治病救人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3825,
    "question": "432,82,281,528",
    "answer": "争权夺利",
    "explain": "争权夺利"
  },
  {
    "level": 3826,
    "question": "813,786,834,276",
    "answer": "转战南北",
    "explain": "转战南北"
  },
  {
    "level": 3827,
    "question": "3,230,3,68",
    "answer": "一成一旅",
    "explain": "一成一旅"
  },
  {
    "level": 3828,
    "question": "620,87,821,167",
    "answer": "交浅言深",
    "explain": "交浅言深"
  },
  {
    "level": 3829,
    "question": "533,213,380,66",
    "answer": "百花齐放",
    "explain": "百花齐放"
  },
  {
    "level": 3830,
    "question": "633,220,270,160",
    "answer": "莲叶满池",
    "explain": "莲叶满池"
  },
  {
    "level": 3831,
    "question": "647,696,273,182",
    "answer": "火山汤海",
    "explain": "火山汤海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3832,
    "question": "8,819,457,651",
    "answer": "柳门竹巷",
    "explain": "柳门竹巷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3833,
    "question": "620,326,389,182",
    "answer": "交淡若水",
    "explain": "交淡若水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3834,
    "question": "374,37,412,38",
    "answer": "鞍前马后",
    "explain": "鞍前马后"
  },
  {
    "level": 3835,
    "question": "389,162,111,426",
    "answer": "偷工减料",
    "explain": "偷工减料"
  },
  {
    "level": 3836,
    "question": "431,486,579,374",
    "answer": "至死不变",
    "explain": "至死不变"
  },
  {
    "level": 3837,
    "question": "97,819,389,101",
    "answer": "程门立雪",
    "explain": "程门立雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 3838,
    "question": "482,45,43,650",
    "answer": "神通广大",
    "explain": "神通广大"
  },
  {
    "level": 3839,
    "question": "298,44,408,374",
    "answer": "风云突变",
    "explain": "风云突变"
  },
  {
    "level": 3840,
    "question": "167,236,486,92",
    "answer": "生离死别",
    "explain": "生离死别"
  },
  {
    "level": 3841,
    "question": "389,579,161,298",
    "answer": "弱不禁风",
    "explain": "弱不禁风"
  },
  {
    "level": 3842,
    "question": "470,594,47,599",
    "answer": "取信于民",
    "explain": "取信于民"
  },
  {
    "level": 3843,
    "question": "109,480,486,73",
    "answer": "心如死灰",
    "explain": "心如死灰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3844,
    "question": "344,650,460,647",
    "answer": "户告人晓",
    "explain": "户告人晓"
  },
  {
    "level": 3845,
    "question": "38,560,165,9",
    "answer": "后会有期",
    "explain": "后会有期"
  },
  {
    "level": 3846,
    "question": "45,94,641,380",
    "answer": "电劈石击",
    "explain": "电劈石击"
  },
  {
    "level": 3847,
    "question": "298,1,480,502",
    "answer": "风景如画",
    "explain": "风景如画"
  },
  {
    "level": 3848,
    "question": "313,380,160,391",
    "answer": "殃及池鱼",
    "explain": "殃及池鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 3849,
    "question": "130,655,650,176",
    "answer": "重望高名",
    "explain": "重望高名"
  },
  {
    "level": 3850,
    "question": "423,179,480,409",
    "answer": "目光如鼠",
    "explain": "目光如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3851,
    "question": "234,460,812,457",
    "answer": "评头论足",
    "explain": "评头论足"
  },
  {
    "level": 3852,
    "question": "370,363,370,641",
    "answer": "恶衣恶食",
    "explain": "恶衣恶食"
  },
  {
    "level": 3853,
    "question": "130,628,812,722",
    "answer": "众所周知",
    "explain": "众所周知"
  },
  {
    "level": 3854,
    "question": "546,47,183,78",
    "answer": "疲于奔命",
    "explain": "疲于奔命"
  },
  {
    "level": 3855,
    "question": "3,480,81,655",
    "answer": "一如既往",
    "explain": "一如既往"
  },
  {
    "level": 3856,
    "question": "101,389,77,101",
    "answer": "冷若冰霜",
    "explain": "冷若冰霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3857,
    "question": "3,579,18,167",
    "answer": "艺不压身",
    "explain": "艺不压身"
  },
  {
    "level": 3858,
    "question": "403,213,8,182",
    "answer": "落花流水",
    "explain": "落花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3859,
    "question": "641,576,641,3",
    "answer": "世疏事异",
    "explain": "世疏事异"
  },
  {
    "level": 3860,
    "question": "479,378,476,389",
    "answer": "沐猴而冠",
    "explain": "沐猴而冠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3861,
    "question": "75,5,120,6",
    "answer": "低三下四",
    "explain": "低三下四"
  },
  {
    "level": 3862,
    "question": "3,7,246,746",
    "answer": "义无反顾",
    "explain": "义无反顾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3863,
    "question": "270,380,486,565",
    "answer": "当机贵断",
    "explain": "当机贵断"
  },
  {
    "level": 3864,
    "question": "812,374,298,167",
    "answer": "论辩风生",
    "explain": "论辩风生"
  },
  {
    "level": 3865,
    "question": "771,275,389,746",
    "answer": "虚怀若谷",
    "explain": "虚怀若谷"
  },
  {
    "level": 3866,
    "question": "381,423,655,460",
    "answer": "狗眼看人",
    "explain": "狗眼看人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3867,
    "question": "109,579,312,426",
    "answer": "心不应口",
    "explain": "心不应口"
  },
  {
    "level": 3868,
    "question": "746,476,463,125",
    "answer": "累瓦结绳",
    "explain": "累瓦结绳"
  },
  {
    "level": 3869,
    "question": "230,343,389,93",
    "answer": "成家立业",
    "explain": "成家立业"
  },
  {
    "level": 3870,
    "question": "722,67,495,528",
    "answer": "知情达理",
    "explain": "知情达理"
  },
  {
    "level": 3871,
    "question": "117,554,553,486",
    "answer": "逆之者亡",
    "explain": "逆之者亡"
  },
  {
    "level": 3872,
    "question": "143,772,143,167",
    "answer": "能屈能伸",
    "explain": "能屈能伸"
  },
  {
    "level": 3873,
    "question": "47,179,734,460",
    "answer": "余光分人",
    "explain": "余光分人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3874,
    "question": "9,426,10,427",
    "answer": "七嘴八舌",
    "explain": "七嘴八舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 3875,
    "question": "363,652,705,486",
    "answer": "牛刀小试",
    "explain": "牛刀小试"
  },
  {
    "level": 3876,
    "question": "47,47,519,519",
    "answer": "郁郁葱葱",
    "explain": "郁郁葱葱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3877,
    "question": "696,737,290,460",
    "answer": "善气迎人",
    "explain": "善气迎人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3878,
    "question": "651,3,67,109",
    "answer": "掉以轻心",
    "explain": "掉以轻心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3879,
    "question": "434,368,431,94",
    "answer": "董狐直笔",
    "explain": "董狐直笔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3880,
    "question": "527,369,711,389",
    "answer": "祥麟威凤",
    "explain": "祥麟威凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 3881,
    "question": "460,389,631,623",
    "answer": "人声嘈杂",
    "explain": "人声嘈杂"
  },
  {
    "level": 3882,
    "question": "579,171,545,207",
    "answer": "不可计数",
    "explain": "不可计数"
  },
  {
    "level": 3883,
    "question": "147,387,167,246",
    "answer": "过从甚密",
    "explain": "过从甚密"
  },
  {
    "level": 3884,
    "question": "831,831,785,175",
    "answer": "漫漫长夜",
    "explain": "漫漫长夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 3885,
    "question": "160,554,3,343",
    "answer": "只此一家",
    "explain": "只此一家"
  },
  {
    "level": 3886,
    "question": "7,248,230,3",
    "answer": "物换星移",
    "explain": "物换星移"
  },
  {
    "level": 3887,
    "question": "700,314,273,374",
    "answer": "瞬息万变",
    "explain": "瞬息万变"
  },
  {
    "level": 3888,
    "question": "109,539,480,78",
    "answer": "爱钱如命",
    "explain": "爱钱如命"
  },
  {
    "level": 3889,
    "question": "801,412,313,819",
    "answer": "车马盈门",
    "explain": "车马盈门"
  },
  {
    "level": 3890,
    "question": "45,833,696,171",
    "answer": "天壤悬隔",
    "explain": "天壤悬隔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3891,
    "question": "819,356,49,476",
    "answer": "开诚布公",
    "explain": "开诚布公"
  },
  {
    "level": 3892,
    "question": "43,460,314,109",
    "answer": "惹人喜爱",
    "explain": "惹人喜爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 3893,
    "question": "273,462,479,819",
    "answer": "万夫莫开",
    "explain": "万夫莫开"
  },
  {
    "level": 3894,
    "question": "130,230,563,555",
    "answer": "众星捧月",
    "explain": "众星捧月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3895,
    "question": "555,696,458,460",
    "answer": "福善祸淫",
    "explain": "福善祸淫"
  },
  {
    "level": 3896,
    "question": "648,647,389,226",
    "answer": "昭然若揭",
    "explain": "昭然若揭"
  },
  {
    "level": 3897,
    "question": "167,270,269,641",
    "answer": "身当矢石",
    "explain": "身当矢石"
  },
  {
    "level": 3898,
    "question": "271,130,423,230",
    "answer": "旦种暮成",
    "explain": "旦种暮成"
  },
  {
    "level": 3899,
    "question": "424,207,143,384",
    "answer": "耳熟能详",
    "explain": "耳熟能详"
  },
  {
    "level": 3900,
    "question": "32,176,436,160",
    "answer": "聪明才智",
    "explain": "聪明才智"
  },
  {
    "level": 3901,
    "question": "468,387,426,525",
    "answer": "病从口入",
    "explain": "病从口入"
  },
  {
    "level": 3902,
    "question": "73,460,647,182",
    "answer": "源头活水",
    "explain": "源头活水"
  },
  {
    "level": 3903,
    "question": "87,460,579,10",
    "answer": "坚忍不拔",
    "explain": "坚忍不拔"
  },
  {
    "level": 3904,
    "question": "641,554,10,11",
    "answer": "十之八九",
    "explain": "十之八九"
  },
  {
    "level": 3905,
    "question": "617,6,159,531",
    "answer": "静思默想",
    "explain": "静思默想"
  },
  {
    "level": 3906,
    "question": "655,476,230,369",
    "answer": "望子成龙",
    "explain": "望子成龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3907,
    "question": "376,380,700,380",
    "answer": "屦及剑及",
    "explain": "屦及剑及"
  },
  {
    "level": 3908,
    "question": "119,120,339,90",
    "answer": "上下其手",
    "explain": "上下其手"
  },
  {
    "level": 3909,
    "question": "369,89,389,92",
    "answer": "龙飞凤舞",
    "explain": "龙飞凤舞"
  },
  {
    "level": 3910,
    "question": "555,112,101,696",
    "answer": "月出东山",
    "explain": "月出东山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3911,
    "question": "423,7,776,425",
    "answer": "偃武修文",
    "explain": "偃武修文"
  },
  {
    "level": 3912,
    "question": "369,373,89,101",
    "answer": "龙蛇飞动",
    "explain": "龙蛇飞动"
  },
  {
    "level": 3913,
    "question": "236,579,387,109",
    "answer": "力不从心",
    "explain": "力不从心"
  },
  {
    "level": 3914,
    "question": "439,45,38,491",
    "answer": "皇天后土",
    "explain": "皇天后土"
  },
  {
    "level": 3915,
    "question": "210,72,734,734",
    "answer": "春雷滚滚",
    "explain": "春雷滚滚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3916,
    "question": "176,324,38,641",
    "answer": "名垂后世",
    "explain": "名垂后世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3917,
    "question": "559,647,480,380",
    "answer": "苍髯如戟",
    "explain": "苍髯如戟"
  },
  {
    "level": 3918,
    "question": "1,821,167,831",
    "answer": "谨言慎行",
    "explain": "谨言慎行"
  },
  {
    "level": 3919,
    "question": "380,480,230,647",
    "answer": "急如星火",
    "explain": "急如星火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3920,
    "question": "273,312,482,317",
    "answer": "万应灵丹",
    "explain": "万应灵丹"
  },
  {
    "level": 3921,
    "question": "389,389,377,377",
    "answer": "沸沸扬扬",
    "explain": "沸沸扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 3922,
    "question": "495,468,641,773",
    "answer": "真凭实据",
    "explain": "真凭实据"
  },
  {
    "level": 3923,
    "question": "8,66,533,641",
    "answer": "流芳百世",
    "explain": "流芳百世"
  },
  {
    "level": 3924,
    "question": "45,705,495,271",
    "answer": "通宵达旦",
    "explain": "通宵达旦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3925,
    "question": "368,409,476,249",
    "answer": "猫鼠同眠",
    "explain": "猫鼠同眠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3926,
    "question": "45,555,209,672",
    "answer": "田月桑时",
    "explain": "田月桑时"
  },
  {
    "level": 3927,
    "question": "3,696,579,3",
    "answer": "一定不易",
    "explain": "一定不易"
  },
  {
    "level": 3928,
    "question": "446,273,652,647",
    "answer": "赴汤蹈火",
    "explain": "赴汤蹈火"
  },
  {
    "level": 3929,
    "question": "118,43,71,213",
    "answer": "昨日黄花",
    "explain": "昨日黄花"
  },
  {
    "level": 3930,
    "question": "210,298,4,821",
    "answer": "清风两袖",
    "explain": "清风两袖"
  },
  {
    "level": 3931,
    "question": "3,176,476,641",
    "answer": "异名同实",
    "explain": "异名同实"
  },
  {
    "level": 3932,
    "question": "519,322,696,554",
    "answer": "等因奉此",
    "explain": "等因奉此"
  },
  {
    "level": 3933,
    "question": "812,279,161,831",
    "answer": "论甘忌辛",
    "explain": "论甘忌辛"
  },
  {
    "level": 3934,
    "question": "672,579,799,120",
    "answer": "时不在来",
    "explain": "时不在来"
  },
  {
    "level": 3935,
    "question": "3,457,357,45",
    "answer": "一步登天",
    "explain": "一步登天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3936,
    "question": "772,431,171,207",
    "answer": "屈指可数",
    "explain": "屈指可数"
  },
  {
    "level": 3937,
    "question": "661,183,89,248",
    "answer": "狂奔飞驰",
    "explain": "狂奔飞驰"
  },
  {
    "level": 3938,
    "question": "73,203,94,525",
    "answer": "原形毕露",
    "explain": "原形毕露"
  },
  {
    "level": 3939,
    "question": "175,174,242,478",
    "answer": "夜色柔美",
    "explain": "夜色柔美"
  },
  {
    "level": 3940,
    "question": "533,167,277,576",
    "answer": "百身何赎",
    "explain": "百身何赎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3941,
    "question": "316,339,7,97",
    "answer": "攻其无备",
    "explain": "攻其无备"
  },
  {
    "level": 3942,
    "question": "180,44,270,45",
    "answer": "彩云满天",
    "explain": "彩云满天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3943,
    "question": "476,436,476,655",
    "answer": "公才公望",
    "explain": "公才公望"
  },
  {
    "level": 3944,
    "question": "163,476,71,3",
    "answer": "合而为一",
    "explain": "合而为一"
  },
  {
    "level": 3945,
    "question": "94,471,273,125",
    "answer": "千难万险",
    "explain": "千难万险"
  },
  {
    "level": 3946,
    "question": "451,460,799,7",
    "answer": "待人接物",
    "explain": "待人接物"
  },
  {
    "level": 3947,
    "question": "650,165,171,655",
    "answer": "大有可观",
    "explain": "大有可观"
  },
  {
    "level": 3948,
    "question": "323,476,93,460",
    "answer": "伏地圣人",
    "explain": "伏地圣人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3949,
    "question": "10,66,365,312",
    "answer": "八方呼应",
    "explain": "八方呼应"
  },
  {
    "level": 3950,
    "question": "25,650,426,403",
    "answer": "折槁振落",
    "explain": "折槁振落"
  },
  {
    "level": 3951,
    "question": "108,431,110,220",
    "answer": "添枝加叶",
    "explain": "添枝加叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 3952,
    "question": "130,47,752,696",
    "answer": "重于泰山",
    "explain": "重于泰山"
  },
  {
    "level": 3953,
    "question": "579,772,579,611",
    "answer": "不屈不挠",
    "explain": "不屈不挠"
  },
  {
    "level": 3954,
    "question": "812,298,314,47",
    "answer": "和风细雨",
    "explain": "和风细雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3955,
    "question": "785,167,579,369",
    "answer": "长生不老",
    "explain": "长生不老"
  },
  {
    "level": 3956,
    "question": "73,431,370,35",
    "answer": "远至迩安",
    "explain": "远至迩安"
  },
  {
    "level": 3957,
    "question": "831,251,531,528",
    "answer": "慢条斯理",
    "explain": "慢条斯理"
  },
  {
    "level": 3958,
    "question": "369,167,305,743",
    "answer": "老生常谈",
    "explain": "老生常谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 3959,
    "question": "161,480,460,3",
    "answer": "尽如人意",
    "explain": "尽如人意"
  },
  {
    "level": 3960,
    "question": "503,236,441,461",
    "answer": "连里竟街",
    "explain": "连里竟街"
  },
  {
    "level": 3961,
    "question": "230,647,647,73",
    "answer": "星火燎原",
    "explain": "星火燎原"
  },
  {
    "level": 3962,
    "question": "384,45,476,327",
    "answer": "向天而唾",
    "explain": "向天而唾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3963,
    "question": "584,696,389,412",
    "answer": "寒蝉仗马",
    "explain": "寒蝉仗马"
  },
  {
    "level": 3964,
    "question": "565,439,49,426",
    "answer": "张皇失措",
    "explain": "张皇失措"
  },
  {
    "level": 3965,
    "question": "533,641,554,640",
    "answer": "百世之师",
    "explain": "百世之师"
  },
  {
    "level": 3966,
    "question": "556,167,43,11",
    "answer": "年深日久",
    "explain": "年深日久"
  },
  {
    "level": 3967,
    "question": "112,482,525,502",
    "answer": "出神入化",
    "explain": "出神入化"
  },
  {
    "level": 3968,
    "question": "379,2,381,431",
    "answer": "鸡零狗碎",
    "explain": "鸡零狗碎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3969,
    "question": "45,92,45,711",
    "answer": "畏首畏尾",
    "explain": "畏首畏尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 3970,
    "question": "319,95,436,365",
    "answer": "投畀豺虎",
    "explain": "投畀豺虎"
  },
  {
    "level": 3971,
    "question": "3,90,793,45",
    "answer": "一手遮天",
    "explain": "一手遮天"
  },
  {
    "level": 3972,
    "question": "44,342,6,182",
    "answer": "云游四海",
    "explain": "云游四海"
  },
  {
    "level": 3973,
    "question": "333,147,47,789",
    "answer": "求过于供",
    "explain": "求过于供"
  },
  {
    "level": 3974,
    "question": "11,82,554,120",
    "answer": "九泉之下",
    "explain": "九泉之下"
  },
  {
    "level": 3975,
    "question": "374,571,110,528",
    "answer": "变本加励",
    "explain": "变本加励"
  },
  {
    "level": 3976,
    "question": "101,174,270,298",
    "answer": "冷嘲热讽",
    "explain": "冷嘲热讽"
  },
  {
    "level": 3977,
    "question": "555,174,128,460",
    "answer": "月色迷人",
    "explain": "月色迷人"
  },
  {
    "level": 3978,
    "question": "486,207,298,210",
    "answer": "枯木逢春",
    "explain": "枯木逢春"
  },
  {
    "level": 3979,
    "question": "476,109,476,186",
    "answer": "同心同德",
    "explain": "同心同德"
  },
  {
    "level": 3980,
    "question": "461,538,380,280",
    "answer": "劫富济贫",
    "explain": "劫富济贫"
  },
  {
    "level": 3981,
    "question": "535,812,650,47",
    "answer": "滂沱大雨",
    "explain": "滂沱大雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3982,
    "question": "378,423,7,431",
    "answer": "厚颜无耻",
    "explain": "厚颜无耻"
  },
  {
    "level": 3983,
    "question": "208,222,273,384",
    "answer": "森罗万象",
    "explain": "森罗万象"
  },
  {
    "level": 3984,
    "question": "479,696,66,130",
    "answer": "摩顶放踵",
    "explain": "摩顶放踵"
  },
  {
    "level": 3985,
    "question": "450,222,273,384",
    "answer": "包罗万象",
    "explain": "包罗万象"
  },
  {
    "level": 3986,
    "question": "109,380,480,647",
    "answer": "心急如焚",
    "explain": "心急如焚"
  },
  {
    "level": 3987,
    "question": "799,560,799,73",
    "answer": "敌惠敌怨",
    "explain": "敌惠敌怨"
  },
  {
    "level": 3988,
    "question": "210,80,648,36",
    "answer": "青红皂白",
    "explain": "青红皂白"
  },
  {
    "level": 3989,
    "question": "298,207,554,6",
    "answer": "风木之思",
    "explain": "风木之思"
  },
  {
    "level": 3990,
    "question": "641,111,527,93",
    "answer": "尸横遍野",
    "explain": "尸横遍野"
  },
  {
    "level": 3991,
    "question": "230,556,746,555",
    "answer": "成年累月",
    "explain": "成年累月"
  },
  {
    "level": 3992,
    "question": "3,655,7,396",
    "answer": "一望无际",
    "explain": "一望无际"
  },
  {
    "level": 3993,
    "question": "4,162,109,746",
    "answer": "良工心苦",
    "explain": "良工心苦"
  },
  {
    "level": 3994,
    "question": "237,80,8,99",
    "answer": "桃红柳绿",
    "explain": "桃红柳绿"
  },
  {
    "level": 3995,
    "question": "8,236,813,460",
    "answer": "流离转徙",
    "explain": "流离转徙"
  },
  {
    "level": 3996,
    "question": "479,304,524,277",
    "answer": "莫敢谁何",
    "explain": "莫敢谁何"
  },
  {
    "level": 3997,
    "question": "478,210,423,762",
    "answer": "眉清目秀",
    "explain": "眉清目秀"
  },
  {
    "level": 3998,
    "question": "283,786,109,423",
    "answer": "胆战心惊",
    "explain": "胆战心惊"
  },
  {
    "level": 3999,
    "question": "821,553,7,278",
    "answer": "言者无罪",
    "explain": "言者无罪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4000,
    "question": "45,183,460,458",
    "answer": "天灾人祸",
    "explain": "天灾人祸"
  },
  {
    "level": 4001,
    "question": "6,186,5,387",
    "answer": "四德三从",
    "explain": "四德三从"
  },
  {
    "level": 4002,
    "question": "387,460,493,403",
    "answer": "从宽发落",
    "explain": "从宽发落"
  },
  {
    "level": 4003,
    "question": "11,7,554,776",
    "answer": "九五之尊",
    "explain": "九五之尊"
  },
  {
    "level": 4004,
    "question": "165,482,426,752",
    "answer": "优胜劣汰",
    "explain": "优胜劣汰"
  },
  {
    "level": 4005,
    "question": "44,342,431,480",
    "answer": "运用自如",
    "explain": "运用自如"
  },
  {
    "level": 4006,
    "question": "567,236,696,182",
    "answer": "表里山河",
    "explain": "表里山河"
  },
  {
    "level": 4007,
    "question": "94,165,3,49",
    "answer": "必有一失",
    "explain": "必有一失"
  },
  {
    "level": 4008,
    "question": "474,640,101,130",
    "answer": "劳师动众",
    "explain": "劳师动众"
  },
  {
    "level": 4009,
    "question": "3,652,4,565",
    "answer": "一刀两断",
    "explain": "一刀两断"
  },
  {
    "level": 4010,
    "question": "566,367,5,703",
    "answer": "狡兔三窟",
    "explain": "狡兔三窟"
  },
  {
    "level": 4011,
    "question": "143,426,560,426",
    "answer": "能说会道",
    "explain": "能说会道"
  },
  {
    "level": 4012,
    "question": "160,705,821,650",
    "answer": "智小言大",
    "explain": "智小言大"
  },
  {
    "level": 4013,
    "question": "3,220,95,423",
    "answer": "一叶蔽目",
    "explain": "一叶蔽目"
  },
  {
    "level": 4014,
    "question": "652,696,647,182",
    "answer": "刀山火海",
    "explain": "刀山火海"
  },
  {
    "level": 4015,
    "question": "389,246,313,45",
    "answer": "沸反盈天",
    "explain": "沸反盈天"
  },
  {
    "level": 4016,
    "question": "326,441,650,696",
    "answer": "秦镜高悬",
    "explain": "秦镜高悬"
  },
  {
    "level": 4017,
    "question": "424,468,531,157",
    "answer": "耳鬓斯磨",
    "explain": "耳鬓斯磨"
  },
  {
    "level": 4018,
    "question": "704,426,305,819",
    "answer": "笑口常开",
    "explain": "笑口常开"
  },
  {
    "level": 4019,
    "question": "425,3,722,641",
    "answer": "闻一知十",
    "explain": "闻一知十"
  },
  {
    "level": 4020,
    "question": "431,246,220,368",
    "answer": "枝繁叶茂",
    "explain": "枝繁叶茂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4021,
    "question": "3,550,47,371",
    "answer": "一盘散沙",
    "explain": "一盘散沙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4022,
    "question": "2,423,232,655",
    "answer": "另眼相看",
    "explain": "另眼相看"
  },
  {
    "level": 4023,
    "question": "565,94,423,322",
    "answer": "尺璧寸阴",
    "explain": "尺璧寸阴"
  },
  {
    "level": 4024,
    "question": "431,468,11,460",
    "answer": "治病救人",
    "explain": "治病救人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4025,
    "question": "432,82,281,528",
    "answer": "争权夺利",
    "explain": "争权夺利"
  },
  {
    "level": 4026,
    "question": "813,786,834,276",
    "answer": "转战南北",
    "explain": "转战南北"
  },
  {
    "level": 4027,
    "question": "3,230,3,68",
    "answer": "一成一旅",
    "explain": "一成一旅"
  },
  {
    "level": 4028,
    "question": "620,87,821,167",
    "answer": "交浅言深",
    "explain": "交浅言深"
  },
  {
    "level": 4029,
    "question": "533,213,380,66",
    "answer": "百花齐放",
    "explain": "百花齐放"
  },
  {
    "level": 4030,
    "question": "633,220,270,160",
    "answer": "莲叶满池",
    "explain": "莲叶满池"
  },
  {
    "level": 4031,
    "question": "647,696,273,182",
    "answer": "火山汤海",
    "explain": "火山汤海"
  },
  {
    "level": 4032,
    "question": "8,819,457,651",
    "answer": "柳门竹巷",
    "explain": "柳门竹巷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4033,
    "question": "620,326,389,182",
    "answer": "交淡若水",
    "explain": "交淡若水"
  },
  {
    "level": 4034,
    "question": "374,37,412,38",
    "answer": "鞍前马后",
    "explain": "鞍前马后"
  },
  {
    "level": 4035,
    "question": "389,162,111,426",
    "answer": "偷工减料",
    "explain": "偷工减料"
  },
  {
    "level": 4036,
    "question": "431,486,579,374",
    "answer": "至死不变",
    "explain": "至死不变"
  },
  {
    "level": 4037,
    "question": "97,819,389,101",
    "answer": "程门立雪",
    "explain": "程门立雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4038,
    "question": "482,45,43,650",
    "answer": "神通广大",
    "explain": "神通广大"
  },
  {
    "level": 4039,
    "question": "298,44,408,374",
    "answer": "风云突变",
    "explain": "风云突变"
  },
  {
    "level": 4040,
    "question": "167,236,486,92",
    "answer": "生离死别",
    "explain": "生离死别"
  },
  {
    "level": 4041,
    "question": "389,579,161,298",
    "answer": "弱不禁风",
    "explain": "弱不禁风"
  },
  {
    "level": 4042,
    "question": "470,594,47,599",
    "answer": "取信于民",
    "explain": "取信于民"
  },
  {
    "level": 4043,
    "question": "109,480,486,73",
    "answer": "心如死灰",
    "explain": "心如死灰"
  },
  {
    "level": 4044,
    "question": "344,650,460,647",
    "answer": "户告人晓",
    "explain": "户告人晓"
  },
  {
    "level": 4045,
    "question": "38,560,165,9",
    "answer": "后会有期",
    "explain": "后会有期"
  },
  {
    "level": 4046,
    "question": "45,94,641,380",
    "answer": "电劈石击",
    "explain": "电劈石击"
  },
  {
    "level": 4047,
    "question": "298,1,480,502",
    "answer": "风景如画",
    "explain": "风景如画"
  },
  {
    "level": 4048,
    "question": "313,380,160,391",
    "answer": "殃及池鱼",
    "explain": "殃及池鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 4049,
    "question": "130,655,650,176",
    "answer": "重望高名",
    "explain": "重望高名"
  },
  {
    "level": 4050,
    "question": "423,179,480,409",
    "answer": "目光如鼠",
    "explain": "目光如鼠"
  },
  {
    "level": 4051,
    "question": "234,460,812,457",
    "answer": "评头论足",
    "explain": "评头论足"
  },
  {
    "level": 4052,
    "question": "370,363,370,641",
    "answer": "恶衣恶食",
    "explain": "恶衣恶食"
  },
  {
    "level": 4053,
    "question": "130,628,812,722",
    "answer": "众所周知",
    "explain": "众所周知"
  },
  {
    "level": 4054,
    "question": "546,47,183,78",
    "answer": "疲于奔命",
    "explain": "疲于奔命"
  },
  {
    "level": 4055,
    "question": "3,480,81,655",
    "answer": "一如既往",
    "explain": "一如既往"
  },
  {
    "level": 4056,
    "question": "101,389,77,101",
    "answer": "冷若冰霜",
    "explain": "冷若冰霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4057,
    "question": "3,579,18,167",
    "answer": "艺不压身",
    "explain": "艺不压身"
  },
  {
    "level": 4058,
    "question": "403,213,8,182",
    "answer": "落花流水",
    "explain": "落花流水"
  },
  {
    "level": 4059,
    "question": "641,576,641,3",
    "answer": "世疏事异",
    "explain": "世疏事异"
  },
  {
    "level": 4060,
    "question": "479,378,476,389",
    "answer": "沐猴而冠",
    "explain": "沐猴而冠"
  },
  {
    "level": 4061,
    "question": "75,5,120,6",
    "answer": "低三下四",
    "explain": "低三下四"
  },
  {
    "level": 4062,
    "question": "3,7,246,746",
    "answer": "义无反顾",
    "explain": "义无反顾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4063,
    "question": "270,380,486,565",
    "answer": "当机贵断",
    "explain": "当机贵断"
  },
  {
    "level": 4064,
    "question": "812,374,298,167",
    "answer": "论辩风生",
    "explain": "论辩风生"
  },
  {
    "level": 4065,
    "question": "771,275,389,746",
    "answer": "虚怀若谷",
    "explain": "虚怀若谷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4066,
    "question": "381,423,655,460",
    "answer": "狗眼看人",
    "explain": "狗眼看人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4067,
    "question": "109,579,312,426",
    "answer": "心不应口",
    "explain": "心不应口"
  },
  {
    "level": 4068,
    "question": "746,476,463,125",
    "answer": "累瓦结绳",
    "explain": "累瓦结绳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4069,
    "question": "230,343,389,93",
    "answer": "成家立业",
    "explain": "成家立业"
  },
  {
    "level": 4070,
    "question": "722,67,495,528",
    "answer": "知情达理",
    "explain": "知情达理"
  },
  {
    "level": 4071,
    "question": "117,554,553,486",
    "answer": "逆之者亡",
    "explain": "逆之者亡"
  },
  {
    "level": 4072,
    "question": "143,772,143,167",
    "answer": "能屈能伸",
    "explain": "能屈能伸"
  },
  {
    "level": 4073,
    "question": "47,179,734,460",
    "answer": "余光分人",
    "explain": "余光分人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4074,
    "question": "9,426,10,427",
    "answer": "七嘴八舌",
    "explain": "七嘴八舌"
  },
  {
    "level": 4075,
    "question": "363,652,705,486",
    "answer": "牛刀小试",
    "explain": "牛刀小试"
  },
  {
    "level": 4076,
    "question": "47,47,519,519",
    "answer": "郁郁葱葱",
    "explain": "郁郁葱葱"
  },
  {
    "level": 4077,
    "question": "696,737,290,460",
    "answer": "善气迎人",
    "explain": "善气迎人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4078,
    "question": "651,3,67,109",
    "answer": "掉以轻心",
    "explain": "掉以轻心"
  },
  {
    "level": 4079,
    "question": "434,368,431,94",
    "answer": "董狐直笔",
    "explain": "董狐直笔"
  },
  {
    "level": 4080,
    "question": "527,369,711,389",
    "answer": "祥麟威凤",
    "explain": "祥麟威凤"
  },
  {
    "level": 4081,
    "question": "460,389,631,623",
    "answer": "人声嘈杂",
    "explain": "人声嘈杂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4082,
    "question": "579,171,545,207",
    "answer": "不可计数",
    "explain": "不可计数"
  },
  {
    "level": 4083,
    "question": "147,387,167,246",
    "answer": "过从甚密",
    "explain": "过从甚密"
  },
  {
    "level": 4084,
    "question": "831,831,785,175",
    "answer": "漫漫长夜",
    "explain": "漫漫长夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4085,
    "question": "160,554,3,343",
    "answer": "只此一家",
    "explain": "只此一家"
  },
  {
    "level": 4086,
    "question": "7,248,230,3",
    "answer": "物换星移",
    "explain": "物换星移"
  },
  {
    "level": 4087,
    "question": "700,314,273,374",
    "answer": "瞬息万变",
    "explain": "瞬息万变"
  },
  {
    "level": 4088,
    "question": "109,539,480,78",
    "answer": "爱钱如命",
    "explain": "爱钱如命"
  },
  {
    "level": 4089,
    "question": "801,412,313,819",
    "answer": "车马盈门",
    "explain": "车马盈门"
  },
  {
    "level": 4090,
    "question": "45,833,696,171",
    "answer": "天壤悬隔",
    "explain": "天壤悬隔"
  },
  {
    "level": 4091,
    "question": "819,356,49,476",
    "answer": "开诚布公",
    "explain": "开诚布公"
  },
  {
    "level": 4092,
    "question": "43,460,314,109",
    "answer": "惹人喜爱",
    "explain": "惹人喜爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 4093,
    "question": "273,462,479,819",
    "answer": "万夫莫开",
    "explain": "万夫莫开"
  },
  {
    "level": 4094,
    "question": "130,230,563,555",
    "answer": "众星捧月",
    "explain": "众星捧月"
  },
  {
    "level": 4095,
    "question": "555,696,458,460",
    "answer": "福善祸淫",
    "explain": "福善祸淫"
  },
  {
    "level": 4096,
    "question": "648,647,389,226",
    "answer": "昭然若揭",
    "explain": "昭然若揭"
  },
  {
    "level": 4097,
    "question": "167,270,269,641",
    "answer": "身当矢石",
    "explain": "身当矢石"
  },
  {
    "level": 4098,
    "question": "271,130,423,230",
    "answer": "旦种暮成",
    "explain": "旦种暮成"
  },
  {
    "level": 4099,
    "question": "424,207,143,384",
    "answer": "耳熟能详",
    "explain": "耳熟能详"
  },
  {
    "level": 4100,
    "question": "32,176,436,160",
    "answer": "聪明才智",
    "explain": "聪明才智"
  },
  {
    "level": 4101,
    "question": "580,71,650,655",
    "answer": "蔚为大观",
    "explain": "蔚为大观"
  },
  {
    "level": 4102,
    "question": "179,322,641,89",
    "answer": "光阴似箭",
    "explain": "光阴似箭"
  },
  {
    "level": 4103,
    "question": "47,38,180,662",
    "answer": "雨后彩虹",
    "explain": "雨后彩虹"
  },
  {
    "level": 4104,
    "question": "398,753,35,722",
    "answer": "燕雀安知",
    "explain": "燕雀安知"
  },
  {
    "level": 4105,
    "question": "176,423,246,214",
    "answer": "名目繁多",
    "explain": "名目繁多"
  },
  {
    "level": 4106,
    "question": "460,324,412,584",
    "answer": "人欢马叫",
    "explain": "人欢马叫"
  },
  {
    "level": 4107,
    "question": "119,109,197,423",
    "answer": "赏心悦目",
    "explain": "赏心悦目"
  },
  {
    "level": 4108,
    "question": "389,696,300,245",
    "answer": "冠山戴粒",
    "explain": "冠山戴粒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4109,
    "question": "297,67,501,3",
    "answer": "寡情薄意",
    "explain": "寡情薄意"
  },
  {
    "level": 4110,
    "question": "49,554,620,528",
    "answer": "失之交臂",
    "explain": "失之交臂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4111,
    "question": "650,471,579,486",
    "answer": "大难不死",
    "explain": "大难不死"
  },
  {
    "level": 4112,
    "question": "171,92,579,391",
    "answer": "恪守不渝",
    "explain": "恪守不渝"
  },
  {
    "level": 4113,
    "question": "183,562,476,641",
    "answer": "列鼎而食",
    "explain": "列鼎而食"
  },
  {
    "level": 4114,
    "question": "807,207,819,213",
    "answer": "铁树开花",
    "explain": "铁树开花"
  },
  {
    "level": 4115,
    "question": "799,4,503,482",
    "answer": "接二连胜",
    "explain": "接二连胜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4116,
    "question": "94,365,38,432",
    "answer": "千呼后拥",
    "explain": "千呼后拥"
  },
  {
    "level": 4117,
    "question": "270,7,554,380",
    "answer": "当务之急",
    "explain": "当务之急"
  },
  {
    "level": 4118,
    "question": "555,44,476,298",
    "answer": "月晕而风",
    "explain": "月晕而风"
  },
  {
    "level": 4119,
    "question": "476,101,696,496",
    "answer": "地动山摇",
    "explain": "地动山摇"
  },
  {
    "level": 4120,
    "question": "476,812,304,380",
    "answer": "同舟共济",
    "explain": "同舟共济"
  },
  {
    "level": 4121,
    "question": "495,298,232,88",
    "answer": "针锋相对",
    "explain": "针锋相对"
  },
  {
    "level": 4122,
    "question": "380,8,182,88",
    "answer": "急流勇退",
    "explain": "急流勇退"
  },
  {
    "level": 4123,
    "question": "3,94,273,1",
    "answer": "一碧万顷",
    "explain": "一碧万顷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4124,
    "question": "519,460,542,831",
    "answer": "郑人买履",
    "explain": "郑人买履"
  },
  {
    "level": 4125,
    "question": "579,193,579,769",
    "answer": "不慌不忙",
    "explain": "不慌不忙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4126,
    "question": "624,821,655,174",
    "answer": "察言观色",
    "explain": "察言观色"
  },
  {
    "level": 4127,
    "question": "4,821,210,298",
    "answer": "两袖清风",
    "explain": "两袖清风"
  },
  {
    "level": 4128,
    "question": "322,222,431,820",
    "answer": "引咎自责",
    "explain": "引咎自责"
  },
  {
    "level": 4129,
    "question": "821,394,47,435",
    "answer": "言归于好",
    "explain": "言归于好"
  },
  {
    "level": 4130,
    "question": "451,672,476,101",
    "answer": "待时而动",
    "explain": "待时而动"
  },
  {
    "level": 4131,
    "question": "705,434,705,560",
    "answer": "小恩小惠",
    "explain": "小恩小惠"
  },
  {
    "level": 4132,
    "question": "127,525,298,769",
    "answer": "初露锋芒",
    "explain": "初露锋芒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4133,
    "question": "480,213,641,249",
    "answer": "如花似锦",
    "explain": "如花似锦"
  },
  {
    "level": 4134,
    "question": "423,650,90,75",
    "answer": "眼高手低",
    "explain": "眼高手低"
  },
  {
    "level": 4135,
    "question": "502,365,746,381",
    "answer": "画虎类狗",
    "explain": "画虎类狗"
  },
  {
    "level": 4136,
    "question": "503,746,94,7",
    "answer": "连类比物",
    "explain": "连类比物"
  },
  {
    "level": 4137,
    "question": "696,672,523,325",
    "answer": "定时炸弹",
    "explain": "定时炸弹"
  },
  {
    "level": 4138,
    "question": "696,246,11,87",
    "answer": "删繁就简",
    "explain": "删繁就简"
  },
  {
    "level": 4139,
    "question": "424,641,554,743",
    "answer": "耳食之谈",
    "explain": "耳食之谈"
  },
  {
    "level": 4140,
    "question": "700,10,316,565",
    "answer": "剑拔弩张",
    "explain": "剑拔弩张"
  },
  {
    "level": 4141,
    "question": "101,410,177,410",
    "answer": "东鳞西爪",
    "explain": "东鳞西爪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4142,
    "question": "381,380,459,435",
    "answer": "狗急跳墙",
    "explain": "狗急跳墙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4143,
    "question": "246,76,280,219",
    "answer": "饭糗茹草",
    "explain": "饭糗茹草"
  },
  {
    "level": 4144,
    "question": "460,476,167,576",
    "answer": "人地生疏",
    "explain": "人地生疏"
  },
  {
    "level": 4145,
    "question": "377,92,167,478",
    "answer": "仰首伸眉",
    "explain": "仰首伸眉"
  },
  {
    "level": 4146,
    "question": "109,652,482,722",
    "answer": "心到神知",
    "explain": "心到神知"
  },
  {
    "level": 4147,
    "question": "356,109,356,3",
    "answer": "诚心诚意",
    "explain": "诚心诚意"
  },
  {
    "level": 4148,
    "question": "722,576,495,528",
    "answer": "知书达理",
    "explain": "知书达理"
  },
  {
    "level": 4149,
    "question": "7,43,411,496",
    "answer": "五日京兆",
    "explain": "五日京兆"
  },
  {
    "level": 4150,
    "question": "772,425,831,777",
    "answer": "区闻陬见",
    "explain": "区闻陬见"
  },
  {
    "level": 4151,
    "question": "720,412,162,474",
    "answer": "汗马功劳",
    "explain": "汗马功劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4152,
    "question": "3,641,530,389",
    "answer": "遗世独立",
    "explain": "遗世独立"
  },
  {
    "level": 4153,
    "question": "530,431,555,94",
    "answer": "句栉字比",
    "explain": "句栉字比"
  },
  {
    "level": 4154,
    "question": "162,277,479,408",
    "answer": "孔席墨突",
    "explain": "孔席墨突"
  },
  {
    "level": 4155,
    "question": "423,193,49,426",
    "answer": "惊慌失措",
    "explain": "惊慌失措"
  },
  {
    "level": 4156,
    "question": "381,381,314,8",
    "answer": "涓涓细流",
    "explain": "涓涓细流"
  },
  {
    "level": 4157,
    "question": "391,130,109,785",
    "answer": "语重心长",
    "explain": "语重心长"
  },
  {
    "level": 4158,
    "question": "561,389,4,460",
    "answer": "判若两人",
    "explain": "判若两人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4159,
    "question": "460,290,402,461",
    "answer": "刃迎缕解",
    "explain": "刃迎缕解"
  },
  {
    "level": 4160,
    "question": "3,6,3,434",
    "answer": "一丝一毫",
    "explain": "一丝一毫"
  },
  {
    "level": 4161,
    "question": "324,45,314,476",
    "answer": "欢天喜地",
    "explain": "欢天喜地"
  },
  {
    "level": 4162,
    "question": "425,147,820,314",
    "answer": "闻过则喜",
    "explain": "闻过则喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4163,
    "question": "298,47,7,820",
    "answer": "风雨无阻",
    "explain": "风雨无阻"
  },
  {
    "level": 4164,
    "question": "819,376,502,298",
    "answer": "开路先锋",
    "explain": "开路先锋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4165,
    "question": "43,650,5,565",
    "answer": "日高三尺",
    "explain": "日高三尺"
  },
  {
    "level": 4166,
    "question": "210,213,222,555",
    "answer": "春花秋月",
    "explain": "春花秋月"
  },
  {
    "level": 4167,
    "question": "397,120,480,47",
    "answer": "泣下如雨",
    "explain": "泣下如雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 4168,
    "question": "696,476,92,493",
    "answer": "奉公守法",
    "explain": "奉公守法"
  },
  {
    "level": 4169,
    "question": "584,77,456,555",
    "answer": "寒冬腊月",
    "explain": "寒冬腊月"
  },
  {
    "level": 4170,
    "question": "314,734,501,322",
    "answer": "喜怒哀乐",
    "explain": "喜怒哀乐"
  },
  {
    "level": 4171,
    "question": "423,130,366,147",
    "answer": "精忠报国",
    "explain": "精忠报国"
  },
  {
    "level": 4172,
    "question": "426,650,3,565",
    "answer": "道高一尺",
    "explain": "道高一尺"
  },
  {
    "level": 4173,
    "question": "171,380,696,476",
    "answer": "克己奉公",
    "explain": "克己奉公"
  },
  {
    "level": 4174,
    "question": "799,4,503,5",
    "answer": "接二连三",
    "explain": "接二连三"
  },
  {
    "level": 4175,
    "question": "173,43,101,352",
    "answer": "旭日东升",
    "explain": "旭日东升"
  },
  {
    "level": 4176,
    "question": "555,641,399,641",
    "answer": "俯拾皆市",
    "explain": "俯拾皆市"
  },
  {
    "level": 4177,
    "question": "3,431,94,423",
    "answer": "一掷千金",
    "explain": "一掷千金"
  },
  {
    "level": 4178,
    "question": "412,491,460,87",
    "answer": "马壮人坚",
    "explain": "马壮人坚"
  },
  {
    "level": 4179,
    "question": "365,460,373,711",
    "answer": "虎头蛇尾",
    "explain": "虎头蛇尾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4180,
    "question": "103,379,326,378",
    "answer": "杀鸡儆猴",
    "explain": "杀鸡儆猴"
  },
  {
    "level": 4181,
    "question": "653,37,746,38",
    "answer": "瞻前顾后",
    "explain": "瞻前顾后"
  },
  {
    "level": 4182,
    "question": "474,640,314,73",
    "answer": "劳师袭远",
    "explain": "劳师袭远"
  },
  {
    "level": 4183,
    "question": "4,5,339,170",
    "answer": "二三其得",
    "explain": "二三其得"
  },
  {
    "level": 4184,
    "question": "147,641,746,746",
    "answer": "果实累累",
    "explain": "果实累累"
  },
  {
    "level": 4185,
    "question": "600,651,800,380",
    "answer": "旁敲侧击",
    "explain": "旁敲侧击"
  },
  {
    "level": 4186,
    "question": "109,213,734,66",
    "answer": "心花怒放",
    "explain": "心花怒放"
  },
  {
    "level": 4187,
    "question": "119,528,236,432",
    "answer": "拒理力争",
    "explain": "拒理力争"
  },
  {
    "level": 4188,
    "question": "528,772,567,752",
    "answer": "理屈词穷",
    "explain": "理屈词穷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4189,
    "question": "431,641,460,460",
    "answer": "志士仁人",
    "explain": "志士仁人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4190,
    "question": "378,378,377,377",
    "answer": "狒狒扬扬",
    "explain": "狒狒扬扬"
  },
  {
    "level": 4191,
    "question": "130,426,92,423",
    "answer": "众口铄金",
    "explain": "众口铄金"
  },
  {
    "level": 4192,
    "question": "641,236,785,832",
    "answer": "十里长亭",
    "explain": "十里长亭"
  },
  {
    "level": 4193,
    "question": "45,120,650,258",
    "answer": "天下大乱",
    "explain": "天下大乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 4194,
    "question": "538,528,630,439",
    "answer": "富丽堂皇",
    "explain": "富丽堂皇"
  },
  {
    "level": 4195,
    "question": "392,270,7,722",
    "answer": "愚昧无知",
    "explain": "愚昧无知"
  },
  {
    "level": 4196,
    "question": "458,387,45,773",
    "answer": "祸从天降",
    "explain": "祸从天降"
  },
  {
    "level": 4197,
    "question": "380,527,431,431",
    "answer": "吉祥止止",
    "explain": "吉祥止止"
  },
  {
    "level": 4198,
    "question": "281,453,394,495",
    "answer": "改邪归正",
    "explain": "改邪归正"
  },
  {
    "level": 4199,
    "question": "652,460,376,302",
    "answer": "奸淫掳掠",
    "explain": "奸淫掳掠"
  },
  {
    "level": 4200,
    "question": "534,380,554,380",
    "answer": "纤芥之疾",
    "explain": "纤芥之疾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4201,
    "question": "314,120,69,655",
    "answer": "熙来攘往",
    "explain": "熙来攘往"
  },
  {
    "level": 4202,
    "question": "801,182,412,369",
    "answer": "车水马龙",
    "explain": "车水马龙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4203,
    "question": "90,579,308,559",
    "answer": "手不停挥",
    "explain": "手不停挥"
  },
  {
    "level": 4204,
    "question": "599,73,389,744",
    "answer": "民怨沸腾",
    "explain": "民怨沸腾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4205,
    "question": "73,172,579,101",
    "answer": "原封不动",
    "explain": "原封不动"
  },
  {
    "level": 4206,
    "question": "314,457,423,819",
    "answer": "喜逐颜开",
    "explain": "喜逐颜开"
  },
  {
    "level": 4207,
    "question": "777,528,655,3",
    "answer": "见礼忘义",
    "explain": "见礼忘义"
  },
  {
    "level": 4208,
    "question": "3,460,600,771",
    "answer": "一人传虚",
    "explain": "一人传虚"
  },
  {
    "level": 4209,
    "question": "445,579,495,460",
    "answer": "军不血刃",
    "explain": "军不血刃"
  },
  {
    "level": 4210,
    "question": "785,391,821,271",
    "answer": "长吁短叹",
    "explain": "长吁短叹"
  },
  {
    "level": 4211,
    "question": "432,831,314,457",
    "answer": "肘行膝步",
    "explain": "肘行膝步"
  },
  {
    "level": 4212,
    "question": "641,556,584,344",
    "answer": "十年寒窗",
    "explain": "十年寒窗"
  },
  {
    "level": 4213,
    "question": "73,831,650,89",
    "answer": "远走高飞",
    "explain": "远走高飞"
  },
  {
    "level": 4214,
    "question": "460,812,3,525",
    "answer": "人和以堪",
    "explain": "人和以堪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4215,
    "question": "7,426,8,555",
    "answer": "五脏六腑",
    "explain": "五脏六腑"
  },
  {
    "level": 4216,
    "question": "298,769,628,384",
    "answer": "锋芒所向",
    "explain": "锋芒所向"
  },
  {
    "level": 4217,
    "question": "278,486,458,92",
    "answer": "罪魁祸首",
    "explain": "罪魁祸首"
  },
  {
    "level": 4218,
    "question": "470,408,460,109",
    "answer": "曲突徙薪",
    "explain": "曲突徙薪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4219,
    "question": "482,67,651,382",
    "answer": "神情专注",
    "explain": "神情专注"
  },
  {
    "level": 4220,
    "question": "10,696,373,182",
    "answer": "跋山涉水",
    "explain": "跋山涉水"
  },
  {
    "level": 4221,
    "question": "3,43,49,175",
    "answer": "移日卜夜",
    "explain": "移日卜夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4222,
    "question": "167,336,554,7",
    "answer": "身外之物",
    "explain": "身外之物"
  },
  {
    "level": 4223,
    "question": "26,90,162,162",
    "answer": "妙手空空",
    "explain": "妙手空空"
  },
  {
    "level": 4224,
    "question": "167,101,647,125",
    "answer": "生动活泼",
    "explain": "生动活泼"
  },
  {
    "level": 4225,
    "question": "480,391,170,182",
    "answer": "如鱼得水",
    "explain": "如鱼得水"
  },
  {
    "level": 4226,
    "question": "426,426,165,641",
    "answer": "振振有辞",
    "explain": "振振有辞"
  },
  {
    "level": 4227,
    "question": "9,67,8,47",
    "answer": "七情六欲",
    "explain": "七情六欲"
  },
  {
    "level": 4228,
    "question": "37,446,38,380",
    "answer": "前赴后继",
    "explain": "前赴后继"
  },
  {
    "level": 4229,
    "question": "623,219,208,167",
    "answer": "杂草丛生",
    "explain": "杂草丛生"
  },
  {
    "level": 4230,
    "question": "183,744,246,381",
    "answer": "奔腾翻卷",
    "explain": "奔腾翻卷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4231,
    "question": "333,82,554,120",
    "answer": "求全之毁",
    "explain": "求全之毁"
  },
  {
    "level": 4232,
    "question": "3,368,554,175",
    "answer": "一狐之腋",
    "explain": "一狐之腋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4233,
    "question": "746,109,218,160",
    "answer": "苦心孤诣",
    "explain": "苦心孤诣"
  },
  {
    "level": 4234,
    "question": "3,277,554,476",
    "answer": "一席之地",
    "explain": "一席之地"
  },
  {
    "level": 4235,
    "question": "799,624,599,67",
    "answer": "体察民情",
    "explain": "体察民情"
  },
  {
    "level": 4236,
    "question": "167,193,533,786",
    "answer": "身经百战",
    "explain": "身经百战"
  },
  {
    "level": 4237,
    "question": "162,236,177,799",
    "answer": "工力悉敌",
    "explain": "工力悉敌"
  },
  {
    "level": 4238,
    "question": "314,109,821,11",
    "answer": "喜新厌旧",
    "explain": "喜新厌旧"
  },
  {
    "level": 4239,
    "question": "298,298,47,47",
    "answer": "风风雨雨",
    "explain": "风风雨雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 4240,
    "question": "270,45,230,146",
    "answer": "满天星斗",
    "explain": "满天星斗"
  },
  {
    "level": 4241,
    "question": "279,305,423,565",
    "answer": "肝肠寸断",
    "explain": "肝肠寸断"
  },
  {
    "level": 4242,
    "question": "109,87,641,82",
    "answer": "心坚石穿",
    "explain": "心坚石穿"
  },
  {
    "level": 4243,
    "question": "799,130,476,120",
    "answer": "接踵而来",
    "explain": "接踵而来"
  },
  {
    "level": 4244,
    "question": "170,482,819,177",
    "answer": "得胜回朝",
    "explain": "得胜回朝"
  },
  {
    "level": 4245,
    "question": "3,3,451,474",
    "answer": "以逸待劳",
    "explain": "以逸待劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4246,
    "question": "531,475,5,579",
    "answer": "孟母三迁",
    "explain": "孟母三迁"
  },
  {
    "level": 4247,
    "question": "226,226,6,391",
    "answer": "窃窃私语",
    "explain": "窃窃私语"
  },
  {
    "level": 4248,
    "question": "109,480,807,641",
    "answer": "心如铁石",
    "explain": "心如铁石"
  },
  {
    "level": 4249,
    "question": "737,314,821,821",
    "answer": "气息奄奄",
    "explain": "气息奄奄"
  },
  {
    "level": 4250,
    "question": "641,640,11,162",
    "answer": "十室九空",
    "explain": "十室九空"
  },
  {
    "level": 4251,
    "question": "776,71,47,431",
    "answer": "宁为玉碎",
    "explain": "宁为玉碎"
  },
  {
    "level": 4252,
    "question": "182,566,45,696",
    "answer": "海角天涯",
    "explain": "海角天涯"
  },
  {
    "level": 4253,
    "question": "744,44,829,173",
    "answer": "腾云驾雾",
    "explain": "腾云驾雾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4254,
    "question": "101,652,177,336",
    "answer": "东倒西歪",
    "explain": "东倒西歪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4255,
    "question": "496,191,426,655",
    "answer": "咬紧牙关",
    "explain": "咬紧牙关"
  },
  {
    "level": 4256,
    "question": "461,160,460,85",
    "answer": "女织男耕",
    "explain": "女织男耕"
  },
  {
    "level": 4257,
    "question": "457,48,326,246",
    "answer": "粗茶淡饭",
    "explain": "粗茶淡饭"
  },
  {
    "level": 4258,
    "question": "5,577,7,85",
    "answer": "三坟五典",
    "explain": "三坟五典"
  },
  {
    "level": 4259,
    "question": "10,482,147,182",
    "answer": "八仙过海",
    "explain": "八仙过海"
  },
  {
    "level": 4260,
    "question": "73,207,333,391",
    "answer": "缘木求鱼",
    "explain": "缘木求鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 4261,
    "question": "3,431,554,785",
    "answer": "一技之长",
    "explain": "一技之长"
  },
  {
    "level": 4262,
    "question": "5,556,554,501",
    "answer": "三年之艾",
    "explain": "三年之艾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4263,
    "question": "336,392,245,160",
    "answer": "外愚内智",
    "explain": "外愚内智"
  },
  {
    "level": 4264,
    "question": "3,170,554,162",
    "answer": "一得之功",
    "explain": "一得之功"
  },
  {
    "level": 4265,
    "question": "130,426,476,112",
    "answer": "冲口而出",
    "explain": "冲口而出"
  },
  {
    "level": 4266,
    "question": "641,555,461,460",
    "answer": "十字街头",
    "explain": "十字街头"
  },
  {
    "level": 4267,
    "question": "415,408,821,182",
    "answer": "猪突豨勇",
    "explain": "猪突豨勇"
  },
  {
    "level": 4268,
    "question": "3,281,218,800",
    "answer": "一改故辙",
    "explain": "一改故辙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4269,
    "question": "222,298,147,424",
    "answer": "秋风过耳",
    "explain": "秋风过耳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4270,
    "question": "45,67,495,528",
    "answer": "通情达理",
    "explain": "通情达理"
  },
  {
    "level": 4271,
    "question": "3,305,3,812",
    "answer": "一唱一和",
    "explain": "一唱一和"
  },
  {
    "level": 4272,
    "question": "45,462,93,369",
    "answer": "田夫野老",
    "explain": "田夫野老"
  },
  {
    "level": 4273,
    "question": "379,89,521,91",
    "answer": "鸡飞蛋打",
    "explain": "鸡飞蛋打"
  },
  {
    "level": 4274,
    "question": "531,170,812,82",
    "answer": "想得周全",
    "explain": "想得周全"
  },
  {
    "level": 4275,
    "question": "276,277,446,230",
    "answer": "背碑覆局",
    "explain": "背碑覆局"
  },
  {
    "level": 4276,
    "question": "412,119,170,554",
    "answer": "马上得之",
    "explain": "马上得之"
  },
  {
    "level": 4277,
    "question": "3,312,470,82",
    "answer": "一应俱全",
    "explain": "一应俱全"
  },
  {
    "level": 4278,
    "question": "380,579,171,49",
    "answer": "机不可失",
    "explain": "机不可失"
  },
  {
    "level": 4279,
    "question": "273,486,8,66",
    "answer": "万古流芳",
    "explain": "万古流芳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4280,
    "question": "722,525,554,434",
    "answer": "知遇之恩",
    "explain": "知遇之恩"
  },
  {
    "level": 4281,
    "question": "641,641,333,641",
    "answer": "实事求是",
    "explain": "实事求是"
  },
  {
    "level": 4282,
    "question": "696,496,182,73",
    "answer": "山遥水远",
    "explain": "山遥水远"
  },
  {
    "level": 4283,
    "question": "821,821,3,314",
    "answer": "奄奄一息",
    "explain": "奄奄一息"
  },
  {
    "level": 4284,
    "question": "565,182,209,45",
    "answer": "沧海桑田",
    "explain": "沧海桑田"
  },
  {
    "level": 4285,
    "question": "3,426,476,389",
    "answer": "异口同声",
    "explain": "异口同声"
  },
  {
    "level": 4286,
    "question": "527,182,270,502",
    "answer": "奋勇当先",
    "explain": "奋勇当先"
  },
  {
    "level": 4287,
    "question": "204,704,175,238",
    "answer": "夙兴夜寐",
    "explain": "夙兴夜寐"
  },
  {
    "level": 4288,
    "question": "87,480,249,641",
    "answer": "坚如磐石",
    "explain": "坚如磐石"
  },
  {
    "level": 4289,
    "question": "650,101,340,323",
    "answer": "大动干戈",
    "explain": "大动干戈"
  },
  {
    "level": 4290,
    "question": "210,322,222,373",
    "answer": "春蚓秋蛇",
    "explain": "春蚓秋蛇"
  },
  {
    "level": 4291,
    "question": "663,342,431,82",
    "answer": "滥用职权",
    "explain": "滥用职权"
  },
  {
    "level": 4292,
    "question": "412,66,834,696",
    "answer": "马放南山",
    "explain": "马放南山"
  },
  {
    "level": 4293,
    "question": "207,381,414,43",
    "answer": "蜀犬吠日",
    "explain": "蜀犬吠日"
  },
  {
    "level": 4294,
    "question": "426,641,109,389",
    "answer": "口是心非",
    "explain": "口是心非"
  },
  {
    "level": 4295,
    "question": "298,304,47,316",
    "answer": "风调雨顺",
    "explain": "风调雨顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 4296,
    "question": "35,812,176,305",
    "answer": "暗渡陈仓",
    "explain": "暗渡陈仓"
  },
  {
    "level": 4297,
    "question": "431,460,426,753",
    "answer": "痴人说梦",
    "explain": "痴人说梦"
  },
  {
    "level": 4298,
    "question": "704,546,704,463",
    "answer": "嬉皮笑脸",
    "explain": "嬉皮笑脸"
  },
  {
    "level": 4299,
    "question": "403,170,812,119",
    "answer": "躲得和尚",
    "explain": "躲得和尚"
  },
  {
    "level": 4300,
    "question": "333,482,106,49",
    "answer": "求神问卜",
    "explain": "求神问卜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4301,
    "question": "49,426,471,655",
    "answer": "没齿难忘",
    "explain": "没齿难忘"
  },
  {
    "level": 4302,
    "question": "460,120,460,655",
    "answer": "人来人往",
    "explain": "人来人往"
  },
  {
    "level": 4303,
    "question": "672,43,707,486",
    "answer": "时日曷丧",
    "explain": "时日曷丧"
  },
  {
    "level": 4304,
    "question": "389,304,777,313",
    "answer": "立竿见影",
    "explain": "立竿见影"
  },
  {
    "level": 4305,
    "question": "565,389,205,300",
    "answer": "张冠李戴",
    "explain": "张冠李戴"
  },
  {
    "level": 4306,
    "question": "650,6,628,308",
    "answer": "大势所趋",
    "explain": "大势所趋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4307,
    "question": "831,412,655,213",
    "answer": "走马观花",
    "explain": "走马观花"
  },
  {
    "level": 4308,
    "question": "435,579,696,426",
    "answer": "赞不绝口",
    "explain": "赞不绝口"
  },
  {
    "level": 4309,
    "question": "82,3,554,545",
    "answer": "权宜之计",
    "explain": "权宜之计"
  },
  {
    "level": 4310,
    "question": "831,554,165,704",
    "answer": "行之有效",
    "explain": "行之有效"
  },
  {
    "level": 4311,
    "question": "457,431,650,220",
    "answer": "粗枝大叶",
    "explain": "粗枝大叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 4312,
    "question": "486,579,43,423",
    "answer": "死不瞑目",
    "explain": "死不瞑目"
  },
  {
    "level": 4313,
    "question": "210,71,579,799",
    "answer": "青黄不接",
    "explain": "青黄不接"
  },
  {
    "level": 4314,
    "question": "641,3,672,3",
    "answer": "世异时移",
    "explain": "世异时移"
  },
  {
    "level": 4315,
    "question": "389,3,106,471",
    "answer": "质疑问难",
    "explain": "质疑问难"
  },
  {
    "level": 4316,
    "question": "762,762,650,650",
    "answer": "羞羞答答",
    "explain": "羞羞答答"
  },
  {
    "level": 4317,
    "question": "229,207,439,403",
    "answer": "瓜熟蒂落",
    "explain": "瓜熟蒂落"
  },
  {
    "level": 4318,
    "question": "641,182,480,391",
    "answer": "似水如鱼",
    "explain": "似水如鱼"
  },
  {
    "level": 4319,
    "question": "562,647,480,3",
    "answer": "鼎镬如饴",
    "explain": "鼎镬如饴"
  },
  {
    "level": 4320,
    "question": "426,90,579,380",
    "answer": "措手不及",
    "explain": "措手不及"
  },
  {
    "level": 4321,
    "question": "49,554,101,398",
    "answer": "失之东隅",
    "explain": "失之东隅"
  },
  {
    "level": 4322,
    "question": "555,74,298,650",
    "answer": "月黑风高",
    "explain": "月黑风高"
  },
  {
    "level": 4323,
    "question": "434,7,4,431",
    "answer": "毫无二致",
    "explain": "毫无二致"
  },
  {
    "level": 4324,
    "question": "3,457,3,308",
    "answer": "亦步亦趋",
    "explain": "亦步亦趋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4325,
    "question": "162,230,167,88",
    "answer": "功成身退",
    "explain": "功成身退"
  },
  {
    "level": 4326,
    "question": "232,725,232,109",
    "answer": "相亲相爱",
    "explain": "相亲相爱"
  },
  {
    "level": 4327,
    "question": "651,495,579,132",
    "answer": "刚正不阿",
    "explain": "刚正不阿"
  },
  {
    "level": 4328,
    "question": "298,617,403,220",
    "answer": "风扫落叶",
    "explain": "风扫落叶"
  },
  {
    "level": 4329,
    "question": "213,37,555,120",
    "answer": "花前月下",
    "explain": "花前月下"
  },
  {
    "level": 4330,
    "question": "594,476,165,557",
    "answer": "信而有证",
    "explain": "信而有证"
  },
  {
    "level": 4331,
    "question": "7,746,223,357",
    "answer": "五谷丰登",
    "explain": "五谷丰登"
  },
  {
    "level": 4332,
    "question": "468,641,799,460",
    "answer": "谋事在人",
    "explain": "谋事在人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4333,
    "question": "167,502,641,207",
    "answer": "身先士卒",
    "explain": "身先士卒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4334,
    "question": "737,256,376,342",
    "answer": "弃瑕录用",
    "explain": "弃瑕录用"
  },
  {
    "level": 4335,
    "question": "106,109,7,558",
    "answer": "问心无愧",
    "explain": "问心无愧"
  },
  {
    "level": 4336,
    "question": "203,283,313,160",
    "answer": "形单影只",
    "explain": "形单影只"
  },
  {
    "level": 4337,
    "question": "480,630,426,73",
    "answer": "如临探渊",
    "explain": "如临探渊"
  },
  {
    "level": 4338,
    "question": "280,36,7,218",
    "answer": "平白无故",
    "explain": "平白无故"
  },
  {
    "level": 4339,
    "question": "176,567,663,304",
    "answer": "陈词滥调",
    "explain": "陈词滥调"
  },
  {
    "level": 4340,
    "question": "426,177,426,101",
    "answer": "道西说东",
    "explain": "道西说东"
  },
  {
    "level": 4341,
    "question": "772,90,554,474",
    "answer": "举手之劳",
    "explain": "举手之劳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4342,
    "question": "210,3,132,647",
    "answer": "春意盎然",
    "explain": "春意盎然"
  },
  {
    "level": 4343,
    "question": "165,435,486,304",
    "answer": "油腔滑调",
    "explain": "油腔滑调"
  },
  {
    "level": 4344,
    "question": "66,212,73,648",
    "answer": "方枘圆凿",
    "explain": "方枘圆凿"
  },
  {
    "level": 4345,
    "question": "130,82,11,753",
    "answer": "重温旧梦",
    "explain": "重温旧梦"
  },
  {
    "level": 4346,
    "question": "431,78,579,246",
    "answer": "自命不凡",
    "explain": "自命不凡"
  },
  {
    "level": 4347,
    "question": "219,764,92,101",
    "answer": "草率收兵",
    "explain": "草率收兵"
  },
  {
    "level": 4348,
    "question": "109,35,528,170",
    "answer": "心安理得",
    "explain": "心安理得"
  },
  {
    "level": 4349,
    "question": "180,786,180,696",
    "answer": "速战速决",
    "explain": "速战速决"
  },
  {
    "level": 4350,
    "question": "47,460,71,696",
    "answer": "与人为善",
    "explain": "与人为善"
  },
  {
    "level": 4351,
    "question": "652,655,722,120",
    "answer": "鉴往知来",
    "explain": "鉴往知来"
  },
  {
    "level": 4352,
    "question": "834,378,276,800",
    "answer": "南辕北辙",
    "explain": "南辕北辙"
  },
  {
    "level": 4353,
    "question": "92,425,478,479",
    "answer": "舞文弄墨",
    "explain": "舞文弄墨"
  },
  {
    "level": 4354,
    "question": "495,737,696,647",
    "answer": "正气凛然",
    "explain": "正气凛然"
  },
  {
    "level": 4355,
    "question": "5,561,8,343",
    "answer": "三班六房",
    "explain": "三班六房"
  },
  {
    "level": 4356,
    "question": "382,69,519,167",
    "answer": "著作等身",
    "explain": "著作等身"
  },
  {
    "level": 4357,
    "question": "249,213,767,8",
    "answer": "眠花醉柳",
    "explain": "眠花醉柳"
  },
  {
    "level": 4358,
    "question": "777,3,6,579",
    "answer": "见异思迁",
    "explain": "见异思迁"
  },
  {
    "level": 4359,
    "question": "554,6,579,101",
    "answer": "纹丝不动",
    "explain": "纹丝不动"
  },
  {
    "level": 4360,
    "question": "3,73,366,186",
    "answer": "以怨报德",
    "explain": "以怨报德"
  },
  {
    "level": 4361,
    "question": "310,435,35,138",
    "answer": "毛将安傅",
    "explain": "毛将安傅"
  },
  {
    "level": 4362,
    "question": "177,177,423,423",
    "answer": "朝朝暮暮",
    "explain": "朝朝暮暮"
  },
  {
    "level": 4363,
    "question": "533,25,579,611",
    "answer": "百折不挠",
    "explain": "百折不挠"
  },
  {
    "level": 4364,
    "question": "651,711,461,460",
    "answer": "巷尾街头",
    "explain": "巷尾街头"
  },
  {
    "level": 4365,
    "question": "38,380,7,460",
    "answer": "后继无人",
    "explain": "后继无人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4366,
    "question": "436,576,495,87",
    "answer": "才疏学浅",
    "explain": "才疏学浅"
  },
  {
    "level": 4367,
    "question": "737,623,389,6",
    "answer": "倚官仗势",
    "explain": "倚官仗势"
  },
  {
    "level": 4368,
    "question": "154,752,171,230",
    "answer": "憨态可掬",
    "explain": "憨态可掬"
  },
  {
    "level": 4369,
    "question": "182,389,5,445",
    "answer": "勇冠三军",
    "explain": "勇冠三军"
  },
  {
    "level": 4370,
    "question": "87,696,579,3",
    "answer": "坚定不移",
    "explain": "坚定不移"
  },
  {
    "level": 4371,
    "question": "3,220,598,812",
    "answer": "一叶扁舟",
    "explain": "一叶扁舟"
  },
  {
    "level": 4372,
    "question": "305,88,474,314",
    "answer": "唱对台戏",
    "explain": "唱对台戏"
  },
  {
    "level": 4373,
    "question": "67,73,528,539",
    "answer": "情怨理遣",
    "explain": "情怨理遣"
  },
  {
    "level": 4374,
    "question": "207,167,431,435",
    "answer": "束身自好",
    "explain": "束身自好"
  },
  {
    "level": 4375,
    "question": "392,553,94,402",
    "answer": "愚者千虑",
    "explain": "愚者千虑"
  },
  {
    "level": 4376,
    "question": "175,174,128,460",
    "answer": "夜色迷人",
    "explain": "夜色迷人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4377,
    "question": "423,179,480,460",
    "answer": "目光如豆",
    "explain": "目光如豆"
  },
  {
    "level": 4378,
    "question": "423,323,807,412",
    "answer": "金戈铁马",
    "explain": "金戈铁马"
  },
  {
    "level": 4379,
    "question": "591,562,47,651",
    "answer": "松贞玉刚",
    "explain": "松贞玉刚"
  },
  {
    "level": 4380,
    "question": "486,242,232,503",
    "answer": "骨肉相连",
    "explain": "骨肉相连"
  },
  {
    "level": 4381,
    "question": "273,486,94,222",
    "answer": "万古千秋",
    "explain": "万古千秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4382,
    "question": "290,460,476,380",
    "answer": "迎头痛击",
    "explain": "迎头痛击"
  },
  {
    "level": 4383,
    "question": "342,161,109,380",
    "answer": "用尽心机",
    "explain": "用尽心机"
  },
  {
    "level": 4384,
    "question": "711,298,10,249",
    "answer": "威风八面",
    "explain": "威风八面"
  },
  {
    "level": 4385,
    "question": "647,478,554,380",
    "answer": "然眉之急",
    "explain": "然眉之急"
  },
  {
    "level": 4386,
    "question": "555,431,109,482",
    "answer": "福至心灵",
    "explain": "福至心灵"
  },
  {
    "level": 4387,
    "question": "523,435,460,3",
    "answer": "差强人意",
    "explain": "差强人意"
  },
  {
    "level": 4388,
    "question": "120,236,10,460",
    "answer": "下里巴人",
    "explain": "下里巴人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4389,
    "question": "476,651,306,101",
    "answer": "孙康映雪",
    "explain": "孙康映雪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4390,
    "question": "476,696,177,183",
    "answer": "铜山西崩",
    "explain": "铜山西崩"
  },
  {
    "level": 4391,
    "question": "7,579,171,380",
    "answer": "无懈可击",
    "explain": "无懈可击"
  },
  {
    "level": 4392,
    "question": "247,167,579,435",
    "answer": "半身不遂",
    "explain": "半身不遂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4393,
    "question": "367,6,398,218",
    "answer": "兔丝燕麦",
    "explain": "兔丝燕麦"
  },
  {
    "level": 4394,
    "question": "245,165,336,469",
    "answer": "内忧外患",
    "explain": "内忧外患"
  },
  {
    "level": 4395,
    "question": "159,555,95,298",
    "answer": "抹月秕风",
    "explain": "抹月秕风"
  },
  {
    "level": 4396,
    "question": "273,120,7,389",
    "answer": "万籁无声",
    "explain": "万籁无声"
  },
  {
    "level": 4397,
    "question": "387,410,579,135",
    "answer": "从容不迫",
    "explain": "从容不迫"
  },
  {
    "level": 4398,
    "question": "11,476,470,436",
    "answer": "就地取材",
    "explain": "就地取材"
  },
  {
    "level": 4399,
    "question": "431,7,339,567",
    "answer": "支吾其词",
    "explain": "支吾其词"
  },
  {
    "level": 4400,
    "question": "460,226,476,482",
    "answer": "人杰地灵",
    "explain": "人杰地灵"
  },
  {
    "level": 4401,
    "question": "101,579,165,435",
    "answer": "兵不由将",
    "explain": "兵不由将"
  },
  {
    "level": 4402,
    "question": "130,424,579,425",
    "answer": "充耳不闻",
    "explain": "充耳不闻"
  },
  {
    "level": 4403,
    "question": "584,101,314,460",
    "answer": "寒霜袭人",
    "explain": "寒霜袭人"
  },
  {
    "level": 4404,
    "question": "555,584,5,86",
    "answer": "岁寒三友",
    "explain": "岁寒三友"
  },
  {
    "level": 4405,
    "question": "426,415,94,812",
    "answer": "口诛笔伐",
    "explain": "口诛笔伐"
  },
  {
    "level": 4406,
    "question": "298,381,435,44",
    "answer": "风卷残云",
    "explain": "风卷残云"
  },
  {
    "level": 4407,
    "question": "7,555,130,167",
    "answer": "物腐虫生",
    "explain": "物腐虫生"
  },
  {
    "level": 4408,
    "question": "161,737,495,704",
    "answer": "严气正性",
    "explain": "严气正性"
  },
  {
    "level": 4409,
    "question": "269,423,380,87",
    "answer": "犯颜极谏",
    "explain": "犯颜极谏"
  },
  {
    "level": 4410,
    "question": "101,563,77,45",
    "answer": "雪窑冰天",
    "explain": "雪窑冰天"
  },
  {
    "level": 4411,
    "question": "655,239,431,323",
    "answer": "望梅止渴",
    "explain": "望梅止渴"
  },
  {
    "level": 4412,
    "question": "538,554,3,773",
    "answer": "付之一炬",
    "explain": "付之一炬"
  },
  {
    "level": 4413,
    "question": "821,556,3,92",
    "answer": "延年益寿",
    "explain": "延年益寿"
  },
  {
    "level": 4414,
    "question": "641,47,457,120",
    "answer": "始于足下",
    "explain": "始于足下"
  },
  {
    "level": 4415,
    "question": "737,45,232,319",
    "answer": "气味相投",
    "explain": "气味相投"
  },
  {
    "level": 4416,
    "question": "220,403,722,222",
    "answer": "叶落知秋",
    "explain": "叶落知秋"
  },
  {
    "level": 4417,
    "question": "207,3,207,4",
    "answer": "数一数二",
    "explain": "数一数二"
  },
  {
    "level": 4418,
    "question": "555,436,734,641",
    "answer": "随才器使",
    "explain": "随才器使"
  },
  {
    "level": 4419,
    "question": "476,369,45,131",
    "answer": "地老天荒",
    "explain": "地老天荒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4420,
    "question": "772,457,67,130",
    "answer": "举足轻重",
    "explain": "举足轻重"
  },
  {
    "level": 4421,
    "question": "506,647,495,423",
    "answer": "烈火真金",
    "explain": "烈火真金"
  },
  {
    "level": 4422,
    "question": "785,431,11,35",
    "answer": "长治久安",
    "explain": "长治久安"
  },
  {
    "level": 4423,
    "question": "495,528,280,431",
    "answer": "正理平治",
    "explain": "正理平治"
  },
  {
    "level": 4424,
    "question": "746,313,431,630",
    "answer": "顾影自怜",
    "explain": "顾影自怜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4425,
    "question": "167,486,232,3",
    "answer": "生死相依",
    "explain": "生死相依"
  },
  {
    "level": 4426,
    "question": "476,640,220,323",
    "answer": "同室操戈",
    "explain": "同室操戈"
  },
  {
    "level": 4427,
    "question": "411,389,482,176",
    "answer": "敬若神明",
    "explain": "敬若神明"
  },
  {
    "level": 4428,
    "question": "160,182,438,82",
    "answer": "智勇双全",
    "explain": "智勇双全"
  },
  {
    "level": 4429,
    "question": "476,495,7,6",
    "answer": "公正无私",
    "explain": "公正无私"
  },
  {
    "level": 4430,
    "question": "101,525,554,468",
    "answer": "霜露之病",
    "explain": "霜露之病"
  },
  {
    "level": 4431,
    "question": "313,579,236,519",
    "answer": "影不离灯",
    "explain": "影不离灯"
  },
  {
    "level": 4432,
    "question": "530,560,423,495",
    "answer": "去伪存真",
    "explain": "去伪存真"
  },
  {
    "level": 4433,
    "question": "696,183,476,506",
    "answer": "山崩地裂",
    "explain": "山崩地裂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4434,
    "question": "47,647,389,652",
    "answer": "狱货非宝",
    "explain": "狱货非宝"
  },
  {
    "level": 4435,
    "question": "226,457,502,170",
    "answer": "捷足先得",
    "explain": "捷足先得"
  },
  {
    "level": 4436,
    "question": "3,245,812,737",
    "answer": "一团和气",
    "explain": "一团和气"
  },
  {
    "level": 4437,
    "question": "389,476,705,171",
    "answer": "非同小可",
    "explain": "非同小可"
  },
  {
    "level": 4438,
    "question": "67,539,435,641",
    "answer": "轻财好施",
    "explain": "轻财好施"
  },
  {
    "level": 4439,
    "question": "480,118,113,90",
    "answer": "如左右手",
    "explain": "如左右手"
  },
  {
    "level": 4440,
    "question": "313,380,391,160",
    "answer": "殃及鱼池",
    "explain": "殃及鱼池"
  },
  {
    "level": 4441,
    "question": "249,249,232,772",
    "answer": "面面相觑",
    "explain": "面面相觑"
  },
  {
    "level": 4442,
    "question": "5,436,11,641",
    "answer": "三旬九食",
    "explain": "三旬九食"
  },
  {
    "level": 4443,
    "question": "161,696,161,478",
    "answer": "尽善尽美",
    "explain": "尽善尽美"
  },
  {
    "level": 4444,
    "question": "130,279,3,283",
    "answer": "忠肝义胆",
    "explain": "忠肝义胆"
  },
  {
    "level": 4445,
    "question": "3,203,47,174",
    "answer": "义形于色",
    "explain": "义形于色"
  },
  {
    "level": 4446,
    "question": "167,539,165,426",
    "answer": "生财有道",
    "explain": "生财有道"
  },
  {
    "level": 4447,
    "question": "650,461,705,651",
    "answer": "大街小巷",
    "explain": "大街小巷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4448,
    "question": "210,82,480,415",
    "answer": "蠢笨如猪",
    "explain": "蠢笨如猪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4449,
    "question": "38,167,171,45",
    "answer": "后生可畏",
    "explain": "后生可畏"
  },
  {
    "level": 4450,
    "question": "276,594,737,3",
    "answer": "背信弃义",
    "explain": "背信弃义"
  },
  {
    "level": 4451,
    "question": "737,6,734,734",
    "answer": "气势汹汹",
    "explain": "气势汹汹"
  },
  {
    "level": 4452,
    "question": "476,43,460,841",
    "answer": "地广人稀",
    "explain": "地广人稀"
  },
  {
    "level": 4453,
    "question": "3,567,389,246",
    "answer": "一表非凡",
    "explain": "一表非凡"
  },
  {
    "level": 4454,
    "question": "493,579,132,486",
    "answer": "法不阿贵",
    "explain": "法不阿贵"
  },
  {
    "level": 4455,
    "question": "336,819,453,426",
    "answer": "歪门邪道",
    "explain": "歪门邪道"
  },
  {
    "level": 4456,
    "question": "737,47,96,481",
    "answer": "气宇轩昂",
    "explain": "气宇轩昂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4457,
    "question": "480,312,531,585",
    "answer": "如应斯响",
    "explain": "如应斯响"
  },
  {
    "level": 4458,
    "question": "6,457,214,72",
    "answer": "四郊多垒",
    "explain": "四郊多垒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4459,
    "question": "43,273,45,476",
    "answer": "广阔天地",
    "explain": "广阔天地"
  },
  {
    "level": 4460,
    "question": "109,246,3,258",
    "answer": "心烦意乱",
    "explain": "心烦意乱"
  },
  {
    "level": 4461,
    "question": "641,831,470,120",
    "answer": "十行俱下",
    "explain": "十行俱下"
  },
  {
    "level": 4462,
    "question": "433,652,433,438",
    "answer": "拿奸拿双",
    "explain": "拿奸拿双"
  },
  {
    "level": 4463,
    "question": "3,43,579,423",
    "answer": "一瞑不视",
    "explain": "一瞑不视"
  },
  {
    "level": 4464,
    "question": "647,423,423,411",
    "answer": "火眼金睛",
    "explain": "火眼金睛"
  },
  {
    "level": 4465,
    "question": "120,67,119,495",
    "answer": "下情上达",
    "explain": "下情上达"
  },
  {
    "level": 4466,
    "question": "210,298,502,47",
    "answer": "春风化雨",
    "explain": "春风化雨"
  },
  {
    "level": 4467,
    "question": "304,734,304,821",
    "answer": "敢怒敢言",
    "explain": "敢怒敢言"
  },
  {
    "level": 4468,
    "question": "374,571,110,528",
    "answer": "变本加厉",
    "explain": "变本加厉"
  },
  {
    "level": 4469,
    "question": "8,112,468,506",
    "answer": "六出缤纷",
    "explain": "六出缤纷"
  },
  {
    "level": 4470,
    "question": "554,486,542,495",
    "answer": "之死靡它",
    "explain": "之死靡它"
  },
  {
    "level": 4471,
    "question": "655,476,167,45",
    "answer": "望而生畏",
    "explain": "望而生畏"
  },
  {
    "level": 4472,
    "question": "72,528,298,831",
    "answer": "雷厉风行",
    "explain": "雷厉风行"
  },
  {
    "level": 4473,
    "question": "43,43,175,175",
    "answer": "日日夜夜",
    "explain": "日日夜夜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4474,
    "question": "389,324,554,476",
    "answer": "立锥之地",
    "explain": "立锥之地"
  },
  {
    "level": 4475,
    "question": "647,119,478,77",
    "answer": "火上弄冰",
    "explain": "火上弄冰"
  },
  {
    "level": 4476,
    "question": "5,222,8,475",
    "answer": "三姑六婆",
    "explain": "三姑六婆"
  },
  {
    "level": 4477,
    "question": "696,696,704,359",
    "answer": "悬崖峭壁",
    "explain": "悬崖峭壁"
  },
  {
    "level": 4478,
    "question": "97,387,249,92",
    "answer": "层峦叠嶂",
    "explain": "层峦叠嶂"
  },
  {
    "level": 4479,
    "question": "431,431,7,7",
    "answer": "支支吾吾",
    "explain": "支支吾吾"
  },
  {
    "level": 4480,
    "question": "270,460,3,265",
    "answer": "当头一棒",
    "explain": "当头一棒"
  },
  {
    "level": 4481,
    "question": "556,538,236,435",
    "answer": "年富力强",
    "explain": "年富力强"
  },
  {
    "level": 4482,
    "question": "5,376,819,620",
    "answer": "三阳开交",
    "explain": "三阳开交"
  },
  {
    "level": 4483,
    "question": "273,486,785,423",
    "answer": "万古长存",
    "explain": "万古长存"
  },
  {
    "level": 4484,
    "question": "3,270,431,170",
    "answer": "意满志得",
    "explain": "意满志得"
  },
  {
    "level": 4485,
    "question": "45,476,579,410",
    "answer": "天地不容",
    "explain": "天地不容"
  },
  {
    "level": 4486,
    "question": "431,554,349,336",
    "answer": "置之度外",
    "explain": "置之度外"
  },
  {
    "level": 4487,
    "question": "313,6,92,94",
    "answer": "营私舞弊",
    "explain": "营私舞弊"
  },
  {
    "level": 4488,
    "question": "425,387,555,316",
    "answer": "文从字顺",
    "explain": "文从字顺"
  },
  {
    "level": 4489,
    "question": "562,746,49,207",
    "answer": "艰苦朴素",
    "explain": "艰苦朴素"
  },
  {
    "level": 4490,
    "question": "423,652,182,182",
    "answer": "惊涛骇浪",
    "explain": "惊涛骇浪"
  },
  {
    "level": 4491,
    "question": "380,527,480,3",
    "answer": "吉祥如意",
    "explain": "吉祥如意"
  },
  {
    "level": 4492,
    "question": "641,478,696,423",
    "answer": "慈眉善目",
    "explain": "慈眉善目"
  },
  {
    "level": 4493,
    "question": "501,88,4,471",
    "answer": "进退两难",
    "explain": "进退两难"
  },
  {
    "level": 4494,
    "question": "7,407,6,182",
    "answer": "五湖四海",
    "explain": "五湖四海"
  },
  {
    "level": 4495,
    "question": "106,227,821,80",
    "answer": "姹紫嫣红",
    "explain": "姹紫嫣红"
  },
  {
    "level": 4496,
    "question": "8,555,89,101",
    "answer": "六月飞霜",
    "explain": "六月飞霜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4497,
    "question": "432,502,742,38",
    "answer": "争先恐后",
    "explain": "争先恐后"
  },
  {
    "level": 4498,
    "question": "370,842,270,313",
    "answer": "恶贯满盈",
    "explain": "恶贯满盈"
  },
  {
    "level": 4499,
    "question": "777,653,109,314",
    "answer": "见猎心喜",
    "explain": "见猎心喜"
  },
  {
    "level": 4500,
    "question": "617,617,476,531",
    "answer": "静静地想",
    "explain": "静静地想"
  }
]